As drought sends the people's cries to the sky the King is informed of his 8th daughter's
marriageability. He commands the royal groom selection to begin. “ Yeongjo Year 29 “
There's still no rain?
I've held countless rituals for rain,
reduced the dishes on my dining table,
pardoned criminals,
and sent away palace maids
because the yin was too strong.
What more am I supposed to do?
Your Majesty
It is because yin and yang are unbalanced.
To restore the balance,
men and women of age must marry.
Do the royal astronomers agree?
Yes, Your Majesty.
But to serve as a model for the people,
we must hold the wedding for the Princess
that was canceled three years ago.
That has been on my mind as well.
Therefore,
I shall open the royal groom selection...
to all eligible suiters.
Your Majesty,
although the Princess is of royal descent,
she must also devote
herself to her husband.
To marry her off is extremely ill-advised.
I beg you to reconsider!
We beg you to reconsider!
Didn't you just say the Princess must wed
to stop this drought?
The people are desperate.
If the throne is disgraced,
what will you do then?
Regarding the Princess' marriage,
you will do as I wish.
To the selected groom
I will bestow a government position,
and a parcel of land in Ganghwa.
Now go and begin the preparations.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Pay in advance! Get your fortunes read!
And you need to meet a man with a
snake, sheep, dragon, or ox zodiac.
And avoid rabbit, snake, and horse?
Because, out of the five
elements, I'm fire?
Oh my...
This is already my third time.
Don't you remember me?
Meow
Oh, woman!
Why'd you come back?
Two rabbits who meet
in the hot summer will overheat...
- You memorized it?
- But if she meets a diligent ox,
you said they'll eat well
and live well together!
Oh, how glad I was
when I found out you're an ox!
I'm destined to roam about
and am not one to settle down.
What ds that matter?
We've got the luckiest age difference!
Four years!
Time's up!
H-He rang the bell! Next!
Shin-chuk Year, Eul-hae Month
Shin-mi Day, Jung-yoo Hour
Wow I have the same Four Pillars!
Ok, what shall I do for you?
Tell me their harmony as business partners.
P... Pak In?
Alright, let's take a look.
A gifted tongue meets a bright mind...
There's no way this could be a bad match!
I don't need the sweet talk.
Just read the fortune.
What's going on today?
Hey, what's with the attitude?
If you're so great,
why don't you read it yourself?
Earthly branches are Chuk and Hae.
These positions have a watery energy.
But Chuk and Hae, these two waterways,
were once joined together.
Therefore this horoscope belongs to a twin.
- Oh my god
- But Chuk carries a discordant spirit.
And its heavenly stem is gold,
giving it a dark and damp energy.
Unfortunately, one of the twins died.
He even knows big brother died.
And these Four Pillars on the left...
The owner has an astute mind.
He is centered, and is as
lucky as he is clever.
With luck on his side,
he will become a keen civil servant.
- C-Civil servant?
- But with that mind,
he just schemes to amass
more money and property.
Just as fire and metal clash,
and Myo and Yoo are a hostile pair,
these two will be torn
apart by their greed.
Thus, their harmony as business partners...
is very good indeed.
One calls in the customers as the
other swindles their money.
What better conman duo is there?
Who are you?
Me?
I'm the guy who's come to catch you.
Alright, let me just ask you one thing...
How'd you know I'm a twin?
You didn't investigate me?
Teach me your ways!
Make me your disciple!
I'll do whatever you say, Master!
- So can't you tell me your secret?
- Christ, you talk a lot.
You just want to scam more people.
What do you mean "scam"?
I used to be a royal astronomer!
Indeed. I've seen records of your service.
- See?
- I'll tell you just one thing.
You focus heavily on zodiacs,
but reading harmonies is not so simple.
Because your lot can change
based on who you meet.
Even curses change to luck
when you meet the right partner.
So what should I do?
Study.
"Study"
Study...?
It says they're picking the groom.
They're doing whatever they can
to get her married.
Oh, the jinxed Princess who got kicked out?
Who would want to marry her?
I'll take her if no one else will!
What's the commotion?
Oh Master, it's Princess Songhwa.
Songhwa... The name sounds familiar.
There are rumors that
just looking at her face is unlucky...
- It's not like that
- As if you've ever even seen her!
Didn't you hear what I said?
I used to be a royal astronomer!
I've seen her face. And that's not all.
I personally served her,
though it wasn't for long.
It was 13 years ago...
The King suddenly fell ill,
and they said he needed
a relative with the energy of metal.
And so the young Princess
was brought back into the palace.
Why was she being raised
outside the palace?
Oh Master,
you've been listening this whole time!
Now the Princess's mother
was the King's favorite concubine.
But that concubine died
right after giving birth.
They called the Princess cursed from birth
and forced her out of the palace.
The Princess' fate was to be kicked out...
only to be brought back in.
Come closer.
Why is your face covered?
The Princess has a harsh skin condition...
If I can't see her face,
how can I know she's the Princess?
Come back!
To top it off,
they said she and her beloved wet-nurse
were fated to fall into disharmony.
And so they tore the two apart.
My, how sad the Princess was!
Don't go!
Please don't go!
From that day on we went all out
to chase away the jinx.
Know what gingko nuts smell like?
We would press them and use the juice
to bathe the Princess every three days!
We must chase out the bad luck.
Now now. Think of the King's health.
E-Everyone says...
I smell like p-poo...
It's because of the gingko fruit.
Here, a peppermint.
The scent is much stronger than gingko,
so take these wherever you go.
1... 2...
Yin and yang must be balanced
for peace to be restored.
Again
1...
The amazing thing is
that the King was cured.
From then on, His Majesty
believed everything
that came from the royal astronomers.
82...
- 83
- 84
- Your Highness!
- 86
- 87
- 88
- 89
- 90!
Your Highness' groom selection will begin!
Your Highness! Are you okay?
What?
How much land do you get if you're picked?
They're giving land in Ganghwa.
And a government post.
It's the perfect chance to change our luck!
Am I right?
Every Tom, Dick, and
Harry has flocked here.
We need to set a few standards.
First
The groom's age must be
similar to the Princess'.
I really am a bachelor
I have to get married!
Second, the groom must not be a Lee.
Third, the groom must be healthy
on the inside and on the outside.
What? This was a test too?
Wait, wait!
12 candidates have passed preliminaries...
and will compete in the next round.
The situation is extremely urgent.
By the day of the feast,
the final candidates must be selected.
I was so glad when I heard
you were coming, Yeohee.
Are preparations going well?
We are making haste to stay on schedule.
So you're finally getting married too.
Given the situation,
I do feel a bit pushed into things.
But I'm eager to meet my one true love...
and live happily together, just like you.
One true love my butt.
- Yeohee...
- If only that Pak In who read our harmony
hadn't spouted on about one true love...
If I could just get my hands on him...
I'd give him a good whollop.
People talk that we're still childless.
To get a bun in the oven,
you have to knead the dough!
I thought even strangers
could warm to each other in the same bed.
There's no joy in life!
I'm so lonely and miserable!
Know how I feel?
I don't want to have a
paramour like our sisters do!
A paramour?
How naive you are...
No wonder you've been raving on about love.
Love?
You don't even know
what your groom will look like!
I received this as a gift
before my own wedding.
Make sure you read it.
What is this?
If you give this to me, what about you?
Memorize. I memorize.
But what's the point?
It's not like I can use it!
Oh, what am I saying to you...
before your own wedding. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Just don't...
Don't get your hopes up.
I'm saying this all for your own good.
- Bullseye!
- No kidding!
Is that him?
Save me! I'm innocent!
Since it looks like we're both busy,
shall we try to speed things up?
Wait, wait, lower, a little lower
The Chief Royal Astronomer, Pak In...
He took bribes from students
taking the entrance exam.
Actually, I have his old ledger...
You have Pak In's ledger?
Yes, yes
Arrest Royal Astronomer Pak In
and his accomplices in bribery.
What are you doing?
My Queen,
Inspector Yoon Sikyung is here.
Discreetly stop the investigation
and erase every trace of evidence.
If you do this, you will
be rewarded greatly.
I have done as Your Majesty commanded.
I have found one who is keen
and deeply knowledgeable.
And who might that be?
You can stop following me, brother.
You caught me.
Didn't I tell you I don't
like you following me?
Well you keep getting yourself hurt.
Take your medicine.
Taking these won't help me see.
Don't spend your money on these things.
One true love my butt.
If only that Pak In who read our harmony
hadn't spouted on about one true love...
Love?
You don't even know
what your groom will look like.
When did you say your vacation is?
Hm?
Oh, Baeki got better
so I decided not to go.
That's a relief.
Still, it's been a while since you saw her.
You must be disappointed.
Actually, I haven't told the Matron yet.
Really?
Then, let me ask you a favor.
I cannot.
How can I pretend to be Your Highness?
And help you sneak out?
During your royal groom selection?
Mani
My whole life I've never done anything
by my own will.
Shouldn't I at least see the face
of the man I'm going to marry?
That's all I want.
But Your Highness...
If I get caught I'll be in huge trouble.
That's why even if I do this in secret
you're the only person I can rely on.
Inspector Seo Doyoon
You were recommended
as an outstanding astrologist.
If you prove your skills
in contest with Chief Pak,
you will read the marital harmony
for the royal wedding.
Read the marital harmony before you.
These two people are similar,
sharing the nature of wood.
Like the left hand meeting
the right to clap,
their union is quite favorable.
Is that so?
Next
Regretfully, Your Majesty,
I did not read the marital harmony.
What is the reason for this?
In the woman's Four Pillars
I see a high chance that
she will be harmed.
By the discord between Hae and Jin,
she is certain to fall ill this year.
Everyone in the palace is talking about it.
So, he's going to read my marital harmony?
Yes
Inspector Seo Doyoon and Chief Pak In.
Did you look into the groom candidates?
I heard the list of candidates
will be released on the night of the feast.
- Really?
- I also found a eunuch to bribe.
He'll go to the wedding hall that night,
look at the candidate list,
and tell us the names.
- That's great!
- But...
I actually have plans for that night...
It'll be hard for me to
slip away unnoticed.
I will do it.
Did you see his broad shoulders?
How ds he look so good in his uniform?
Who are you talking about?
Yoon Sikyung, Yoon Sikyung
That guy who turned down Princess Songhwa?
- Him?
- Yeah
- He had reason enough.
- Who would dare marry her?
Poor Princess...
Yoon Sikyung?
Sir
Let us go to the wedding hall.
These are the final
candidates' Four Pillars.
Until we begin proceeding in three days,
make sure to guard these well.
Yoon Sikyung
Is this the right place?
So stuffy...
Why isn't he coming?
I saw your name
among the groom candidates.
Things turned out that way.
Princess Songhwa...
Weren't you in marriage talks
with her three years ago?
You should check your facts.
It wasn't a back and forth,
but all one-sided.
I kept hearing that ever since she was born
she was diseased with bad luck.
What man would agree to marry her?
I was young back then.
I was worried I'd be jinxed
if we so much as kissed.
So I rejected their offer.
I'm curious why you entered the selection
after having turned them down.
Let's save that story for later.
There's something
I've been meaning to talk to you about.
His Excellency is looking for you.
One moment.
I was worried I'd be jinxed
if we so much as kissed.
Jinxed?
Inspector Seo Doyoon!
Where are you?
Right here.
What took you so long? I
was about to take off.
I'm sorry.
- Here, take this.
- What is this?
The candidates' horoscopes.
Horoscopes?
I asked you to look at the names!
How could you steal this?
I know! That was my plan.
But... things changed.
- If it makes you that uneasy...
- Take it.
- You can take it back yourself.
- I'm out.
- Hey!
Yoon Sikyung, Nam Chiho,
Kang Hwee, Cho Yoosang
How am I supposed to take this back?
This feast is such a drag.
Let's grab a drink when it ends.
The Violet Pavilion?
No one understands me like you do.
Excuse me.
Let's go
Inspector Seo, coming?
- Your Highness
- Yes
I put everything you need in here.
Okay
Baeki will be waiting for you here.
Thank you
- And...
- What is it now?
I packed it to the brim.
- Please get back safe.
- Don't worry.
Mani
Excuse me.
There wasn't anyone suspicious
at the hall during the feast?
I didn't even see the shadow of an ant.
That's very strange.
Dsn't match up with the maid's story.
M-maid?
The goose. The girl in the goose mask.
If you're not careful,
you're gonna take the fall.
Please forgive me!
I needed the money, I made a mistake.
I did take all the Four Pillars,
but I just snuck them out
for her and that's it.
The girl in the mask. What is her name?
Mani. Chun Mani.
She serves Princess Songhwa.
Proceed
Next
Hey, that's my rice cake!
Wait for me!
Hey!
Goodness, will it rain this year?
If Princess Songhwa gets married,
will it rain then?
- Who knows?
- Big brother, I'm hungry.
Just hold on.
I'm hungry too.
Eat slowly.
But...
Is it always this empty?
It's because of the drought.
Can I have seconds?
Yes, you may.
One more bowl of soup please.
- Yes ma'am
- But
If Princess Songhwa gets
married it might rain.
Hey
She's so ugly she can't get married.
You wanna bet?
She's super ugly.
Have you kids ever seen the Princess?
Yes
For real
She looks like this.
Um...
Look at me.
Princess Songhwa looks like me.
See?
I told you she's ugly.
Super ugly
I heard the young Master Cho
is going to be the groom.
Poor him
Really?
The young master is a final candidate?
Do you know him?
He has a good personality...
and he's good looking too.
He's a manly man!
Really?
Do you know his name by any chance?
Nope, don't know that.
I know where his house is.
Where is it?
Over there
You're amazing!
You make and sell these, and decorate too?
Are you having fun?
Is it easy to take other people's money?
Making a living off of something fun
is still just work.
When I leave the palace,
let's live together, you and Mani and I.
There's something I wanted to tell you.
I know the royal groom candidate
Master Kang Hwee.
He's one of my customers.
He is?
I'll try to arrange for you to meet.
Great
The things you asked for.
Think I'll be alright?
No doubt.
O... Open the gate.
I can't do this.
What are you doing snooping around?
Just gonna give me the cold shoulder?
You think a hat and topcoat make you a man?
- Your walk should be manly too.
- What do you want?
Move out of the way!
Excuse me for a moment.
Hey, look here!
What is this utter disrespect?
Give it back at once!
Where are the Four Pillars?
Not sure what you mean...
You serve the Princess.
Your name is Mani, is it not?
I'm on my way from meeting the eunuch.
He confessed everything.
It is true that I serve the Princess,
but I don't know anything
about these Four Pillars or other.
It looks like you've been misled.
What will you do if they're
false accusations?
How about coming clean
that you lost the Four Pillars!
So now you're threatening me.
The night of the feast
I definitely saw you.
Did we...
Did we leave it at seeing each other?
What are you talking about?
That night I was working myself to death.
Check for yourself!
See what Mani did!
If that's the case,
then what are you doing here?
I'll go to the palace this instant
and tell everyone...
That your sister is in perfect health,
and you're peeping at a stranger's house.
The truth is, the young
master of this house...
Young master?
I've been madly in love
with the young master.
How dare you, as a palace maid!
So...
Can't you see why I disguised myself?
Just once, for the last time,
I wanted to meet him face to face.
Do you know...
just how much this trip means to me?
I risked my life to come here.
Wait here.
Open the gate.
The First Candidate Cho Yoosang
I was a little...
hasty back there.
So let's just forget...
about my earlier impropriety.
But that dsn't mean you're off the hook.
So
This young master...
Just what about him captivated you so?
Why do I have to answer that?
You said you risked your life,
so I'm curious how great he is.
His heroic air and spirit, shall I say?
A man among men. He is a true man.
Have a cup of tea.
Have a cup.
Leave us.
Father is out at the moment.
So I, as his only son,
have come to greet you today.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Cho Yoosang.
I am Inspector Seo Doyoon.
This
is my little brother.
But... what brings you here today?
I was just passing by your home
and thought I would pay
a visit to Lord Cho.
I see.
To pass the time while we wait,
how about I read your fortune?
Your age this year...?
In two days after the
hour of Chuk, I'll be 13.
13 at the hour of Chuk...
Young master, Lord Cho has arrived.
Very well.
Excuse me for a moment.
Certainly.
Isn't he a bit young for you to be in love?
You look at least 10 years older than him.
15 years older?
No. I'm six years older.
- Please
- It's true
That's Jung-sa Year!
Yes, I'm telling you.
- What day in Jung-sa Year?
- April 13
- Hour?
- Hour of Oh...
But why do you ask?
13...
Reading your harmony,
I understand now why you're so in love.
What?
Both tenderhearted, both full of thoughts.
You would embrace one another
in a so-called "commiserating" match.
That's enough.
Did I ask you to read our marital harmony?
I read it as a special favor
since you risked your life.
- But you can forget it.
- Fine.
I will forget it.
Even without things like that...
I know a good person when I see one.
So you can read faces.
Your Highness, lunch is served.
I dropped by unannounced
and yet you treat me to such a fine meal.
Not at all.
It is my honor to meet
such an esteemed guest.
But...
Why ds your sister go
around in men's clothing?
She says she must crossdress...
- or else she will die early.
- Even so.
Who would believe she's a man?
Let's eat.
Brother,
Brother, when did you...
get hair down there?
What a choice of topic.
There isn't a single hair on your chin.
I need to become a man
before I become the royal groom.
I have a lot on my mind.
And no matter how much I
eat, I don't grow taller.
Growing tall and becoming a man
will all happen in time.
I might be short,
but I know a thing or two about girls.
I even have some dirty pictures.
Do you want to take a peek?
I get hives whenever I eat chicken.
How is it that you only
eat chicken like that?
It's because you still
can't use chopsticks.
Sit up straight.
Bent over like that,
no wonder that food gs to your belly
and not your height.
Where are my manners?
I cherish him deeply
and do this all for his own good.
Ever since my wife began
living apart from us
I've had a thousand things to worry about.
I see.
May I ask why?
They said their mother-son harmony
was unfavorable.
We live apart lest harm come Yoosang's way.
Can you become the groom
if you're this soft?
I...
will become the groom.
Father wants me to...
and only then can I see Mother.
But... I'm just such a blockhead!
Goodness
Let go!
This is too embarrassing.
It's not your fault.
What isn't?
Everything
So don't blame yourself for
things you can't help.
You'll become a man among men.
This is a secret,
but I have a fine book of dirty pictures.
I'll give it to you next time.
So focus on your studies
and don't worry over
your father's scoldings.
My, I've been blessed with good friends.
So
You say Inspector Yoon's horoscope
is favorable for our Prince.
Indeed.
Yoon's Pillars hold strategic
ability and boldness...
making up for what the Prince lacks...
and lifting the Prince to the throne.
But they clash with the Princess'.
No matter what I say...
- if Seo Doyoon reads it...
- Enough.
Did I call you here to listen to this?
Apologies.
Put together a horoscope
that will please His Majesty.
I will.
That way, our Inspector Yoon
can become the royal groom.
Isn't that so?
As long as I can assist the Crown Prince...
anything is achievable for me.
Did Her Highness eat?
She finished everything.
One moment.
These clothes won't do.
Everyone stares at me out there.
Then...
How about a chaekbi?
Chaekbi?
So what kind of person is Master Kang Hwee?
He's someone whose one-of-a-kind charm
has everyone falling in love.
And that's not all.
Master Kang Hwee's gayageum playing
truly tugs at the heartstrings.
And not only is he handsome on the outside,
but they say he's also a man of substance.
Very well, it sounds to me
like he's quite the playboy.
But the women who have seen
Master Kang Hwee just never stop smiling.
He's entertaining too.
It's more like...
Just looking at his beautiful face
lifts their cheeks to the skies.
Exactly how harlots would behave.
The Second Candidate Kang Hwee
You're late.
I'm sorry.
I was delayed bringing a new chaekbi
as Okhee is sick.
I see.
So it's you.
Follow me.
Father...
Your grace is immeasurable!
His face!
Let's go!
The royal groom isn't allowed
to have a concubine...
And even if the Princess dies,
he has to grow old and die a widower.
Is it too late to call everything off?
Hey now, be careful what you say.
What do we do
if you really become the royal groom?
The Princess has eyes, too.
I'll come out to meet you,
even if I have to break through walls.
Why don't you help me...
to become the royal groom.
How do you mean?
When the Princess and I
have our harmony read,
make our match unsurpassable.
A royal inspector fabricating
his Four Pillars.
This is quite scandalous indeed.
You've changed.
Don't distance yourself
now that Father has passed away.
When you learned Father enjoyed astrology,
you studied like a dog.
So you wouldn't get
kicked out of our house.
I have not forgotten Uncle's grace...
If you haven't forgotten,
then return the favor.
If I become the royal groom,
won't it be nice having a strong support?
Oh right.
I'm looking into an eye
doctor from the Qing dynasty.
We need to fix Gayoon's eyes, don't we?
I'll be waiting for your response.
In the green mountains an old tiger...
bites the fattened tigress.
His teeth fallen out, he cannot eat.
"He growls..."
That's enough of that.
Come here!
To bad old me!
No, no!
Come with me on my back!
How dare they to Her Highness!
What do I do?
Climb on my back! Climb on!
Why you!
Listen here.
The punishment for treason
is dismemberment.
And those who disobey...
will be severely
punished and sent home.
Do not despair that you will die.
Ch... Chyunhyang...
- shouted
- Stop reading.
I've been waiting for you all night.
Come here!
Who is that?
He's a newcomer to the Violet Pavilion,
a master of the bedroom arts.
"Master of the bedroom arts"
You have a feeble heart,
and you are fearful, making
large tasks difficult.
You like peeping, don't you?
A true master of the bedroom arts!
In your case,
someone with dark skin,
a small and round face,
big eyes,
full hips,
and breasts that are...
not that big is a good match for you.
So...
Yes, it's you.
Alright
- But...
- What?
You'll have to
regain your confidence first.
In here is something
that can lift a man's head right back up.
Now! This right here!
Belonged to a young bride
widowed on her own wedding night.
It is her 30 year old, clandestine...
hair.
Just keep it on your person and you'll...
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Where do you think we are?
Alright then that...
That over there... How much is it?
Is that so?
Well who is this?
So now you're a master of the bedroom arts.
Yes, I was so inspired by what you told me,
that now I'm studying
everything from A to Z.
And where'd you get that widow's hair?
Oh, you saw? How many do you want?
I don't have many left.
Oh, Master.
I have something urgent to tell you,
so please make some time.
Can't you tell me now?
It's not the right time.
- The young master I was with...
- Come quickly!
When I told him about you
he asked that you read his marital harmony.
If you could?
No thanks.
But that's Lord Kang's son.
He might even become the royal groom!
I heard you're gifted in
reading marital harmony.
We'll see about that.
I'm short on time, I'll read one match.
Sure. That's fine.
- Who shall I pick?
- Sir
- Over here, sir
Reading the bedroom arts manual,
the chaekbi was my best match.
Chaekbi
Tell me your Four Pillars.
Eul-myo Year, Gye-mi Month
Gi-myo Day, Eul-sa Hour
Wow, he knows the chaekbi's Four Pillars
just by looking at her.
That's Inspector Seo for you!
Move over.
Looks like you've had a lot to drink.
Let's have a look at your face.
Kang Hwee
Born with ability, talent, and wit.
His fame and popularity bring women
as well as men flocking to him.
Are you home?
After the crisis this brings
these two will enjoy peace and harmony
and will live without incident.
But why ds he keep...
What are you doing?
I asked you to read me and my baby's match.
That woman.
Stay away from her.
Why?
It's so horrible I'm
sorry to even say this.
All the bad spirits in the world are here,
so, ultimately, you'll die early.
In two years.
Also you'll commit treason and be sentenced
- to dismemberment...
- Stop, stop.
You're killing the mood.
Um, but it reads a little
differently to me.
Hey now.
How many times have I said
it's best to read honestly?
My lords
It's time we move the party outside.
What? What? What is this?
Why do you keep following me?
Who on earth are you?
What makes you think you
can act so recklessly?
"Act reckless"?
How dare you
Don't follow me around
reading my marital harmony.
Why do you keep doing that?
Really
I don't know either.
Why you keep making me worried.
It's hot.
Wait... wait...
Your High...
ny!
Are you okay?
Oh my goodness, did you drink?
How much did you have?
Watch where you put your hands!
Tch
How dare he?
Look at how red you are!
What did I do?
I should have come sooner!
Are you okay?
Hey...
Smells nice.
They're peppermints. Want one?
Yes
Here
- But Brother
- Hm?
Don't you usually hate sweets?
A person's tastes can change.
You remember everything.
What are you doing here?
Master, hungry right?
Just wait one second I'm all done.
If you're done eating, head on out.
Why are you being so cold?
He's your very own disciple.
Disciple?
On top of that,
he had a twin brother
who looked exactly like me,
but sadly he passed away.
You look so similar
I almost shouted Brother! when I saw you.
But how old are you, young master?
I'm 18.
We're the same, same zodiac.
Stop with the jibber jabber and go on home.
I said I have something
important to tell you.
Master
Do you really think
I'm the mastermind of that bribery case?
Me, who grew up straight as an arrow,
committing corruption alone?
Contemplate your own crimes
instead of blaming others.
They pinned everything on me!
Who's they?
Inspector Yoon...
He got rid of the evidence.
Behind Inspector Yoon, Pak In.
Behind Pak In...
the Queen.
Watch what you say about the palace!
I had something to show you.
Forget it.
What use are fortunes?
You need to see what's around you.
Reading fortunes is bull
if you're that blind.
- Brother
- Yes
The errand boy said
a woman wanted to give this to you.
Ah
Oh, my head.
Definitely...
He definitely said I make him worry.
What ds that mean?
It must be because of the Four Pillars.
Now that you've returned them,
he won't worry anymore.
Okay
You're probably right.
Men are simple.
If they like you, they say I like you.
They don't beat around the bush.
Is that so?
Your Highness
I think it's time you return to the palace.
I was thinking of going back today.
After I meet one more person.
The scholars continue
to appeal for an end to the drought.
Hasten the preparations
for the royal wedding.
Yes, Your Majesty.
These were seized from smugglers.
They look like normal candles,
but they're powerful hallucinogens.
Why did you call me?
How long will you make me wait?
What are you talking about?
My request must have sounded like a joke.
Shall I ask again?
I'm sorry.
But I won't do it.
That is my will.
These are the Princess's Four Pillars.
As the wedding is approaching,
make haste to read her harmony
with the candidates
and gather your opinions.
Jung-sa Year, Eul-sa Month
Shin-mi Day, Gab-oh Hour
Excuse me.
Are these really the
Princess' Four Pillars?
Yes
Is there a problem?
These are the names of
the palace personnel.
Chun Mani
Gab-shin Year, Jung-myo Month
Eul-chuk Day, Eul-yoo Hour
Jung-sa Year, Eul-sa Month
Shin-mi Day, Gab-oh Hour
- What day in Jung-sa Year?
- April 13
- Hour?
- Hour of Oh...
So Seo Doyoon and Yoon Sikyung are cousins.
Isn't that good for us?
That is true, but...
No matter how loyal he appears,
do not let your guard down.
Why not?
Can you see what Yoon Sikyung is thinking?
I cannot, which is why
we must stay vigilant.
As Your Highness knows...
I am loyal to Your Highness' son,
the Crown Prince.
Why wouldn't I know?
The Prince is the reason...
that you've made it this far.
My son, my son what is it?
Why isn't the medicine working?
It is because of the Princess
who entered the palace days ago.
Tell me more.
When the spirits of two relatives collide,
the side with the weaker
energy will suffer.
It appears the Princess' energy
will break the Crown Prince in one blow.
The problem is...
for the King's health,
the Princess must stay by his side
until she is of age.
There are still 10 years left
until that girl reaches 16.
What is the Prince
supposed to do until then?
First...
Those with favorable
energies for the Princess
must be sent away.
The surest method of all
is to find a groom of an adverse spirit
and suppress her energy.
Then the Prince's spirit will be restored,
and the seat of power will be his.
Your Highness must recover.
I will leave after I see
Your Highness take one bite.
Since when were you left-handed?
How could you...!
Where on earth is the Princess?
Please take your fill.
The Third Candidate Nam Chiho
Sukhyang parted with her parents at
age five, and after roaming about
she reunited with them at the age of 20.
With two sons and one daughter¦
It seems I disturbed you.
My mother used to love this story,
and I too became spellbound.
How did she become this way?
I shouldn't have pried.
Not at all.
My mother is a warm-hearted person,
and when her maid died in an accident
the shock left her like this.
After mother collapsed,
my heart turned towards the less fortunate.
The heavens will certainly
be in awe of your devotion.
I will leave your pay at
the servants' quarters.
I have some business to attend to,
but please take good care of my mother.
Excuse me.
Those children look famished.
One meal a day, and just gruel at that.
How could they not be famished?
Is the storeroom empty?
Empty? More like chock full.
- Only the young master can open that.
- You little rat!
Shut your mouth right now!
Hurry on now.
The Princess has left the palace
to spy on the candidates.
What did you say?
How in hell did you let this happen?
The Princess sneaked out?
How can I expect
to become the groom in this state?
- Inspector Yoon...
- I won't sit back any longer.
Take it back.
Since I bought it, please accept it.
I will talk to Master Nam myself.
- Mom, I'm hungry.
- Mom
Start the fire.
Let's go, let's eat!
It's rice, it's rice!
Nam Chiho, Lee Songhwa
In Nam Chiho's Four
Pillars are broken trees.
Though trees carry life,
one by one they disappear
only to be replaced by dreadful blades.
Eat plenty.
Destruction upon destruction.
Evil thoughts tangle together,
dizzying his mind
Between In and Shin, there is bloodlust.
Only when he slashes his
blade is he satisfied.
Where did you get this? The storeroom?
I'll hack your limbs and sell them off.
The chaekbi. The chaekbi brought it.
Where is she?
Get up.
- What is it?
- Hurry
If you're caught you'll go mad too.
- But still...
- Who made Lady Nam go insane?
- That was an accident...
- Accident my ass.
Lady Nam's foster daughter
opened the storeroom.
So as a punishment that bastard
buried her in the ground up to the neck.
Could anyone have survived
that beating sun?
That's why Lady Nam collapsed.
- What?
- Go out this door and run away.
Hurry!
- Look here...
- Hurry!
Hurry! Go!
Over there!
Get her!
There is no escape from his anger.
The knife in his hand
will ruthlessly cut the Princess.
You must have taken me for a complete fool.
S... Spare my life.
Why would I kill you?
No.
You humiliated me in front of my servants.
I can't just let that go.
Shall I scoop out your eyes?
Or shall I mash your legs
until you can't walk?
How dare you.
Do you know who I am?
If you wish to live then
let me go this instant!
I'll cut your mouth.
Let go!
Put it away.
Why don't you go on your way.
I was just teaching my servant to behave.
Don't stick your nose in.
Go! Go!
Begone
Let me go!
Let go!
Stop!
- Let go!
- Why?
She's not here.
Today...
What happened?
Why didn't you say anything?
It...
- Let me see.
- It's not my blood.
All finished.
Thank you.
Did you make it yourself?
It's the eu-a-ri flower.
That was my wet-nurse's name.
Though we parted when I was young,
I wanted to tell her
that I haven't forgotten her for a second.
They're all wet.
There's something I haven't told you.
- I am...
- At daybreak
I'll take you back to the palace.
You knew this whole time?
If you're going to disguise
yourself, do it properly.
Telling me your Four Pillars...
Popping up
wherever the groom candidates are...
Were you that curious about them?
I intended to return
after seeing who they were.
How reckless.
The groom is selected by the palace anyway.
But rather than sit still,
mustn't one move
in order to bring change?
That's why I tried to be brave.
I want to go somewhere far away...
and live freely.
Let's get some sleep.
Where is Her Highness?
The Princess has a cold
and cannot receive guests.
The Fourth Candidate
Yoon Sikyung
Though it is quite humble,
I am honored to have you in my home,
Your Highness.
You know who I am?
Inspector Seo asked that
I take care of you.
My name is Yoon Sikyung.
Inspector Seo Doyoon?
Your brother asks that
you come home quickly.
Gayoon
Hello
I came to get something
from you, Inspector.
What are you doing? Let
that boy go at once.
Gayoon, don't move!
The young master's life
depends on you, Inspector.
I'll do whatever you want, just let him go.
Start by writing the Four Pillars.
If both Shin and Jin are present,
the groom's Pillars will impress the
ministers, but it may be too much.
I will make him lucky, but lacking.
If he and the Princess
produce children to fill this lack,
this will be a match made in heaven.
Let's go.
Gayoon!
That's the Seo Doyoon I know.
Making up these Four Pillars so quickly.
All that's left is for
you to become the groom.
Seo Doyoon
How about I read your
fortune for a little fun?
What brings you here?
I will return to the palace immediately.
I cannot delay any longer.
In case she asks,
tell her they're candles
we light for special guests.
Yes, Master
Deliver this safely.
Those rat bastards...
Picking the dirtiest things to do
just like their dirty faces.
If only I hadn't been tied up...
Master
Your Highness
Princess!
- What is it?
- Princess!
What has happened?
I don't know why I feel so hot and dizzy.
That's normal.
Yoon Sikyung! Yoon Sikyung!
These were seized from smugglers.
They look like normal candles,
but they're powerful hallucinogens.
You should have listened
when I asked nicely.
Put your sword away.
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Turn around!
Careful now.
Let us go now.
What is this disgrace?
You dare leave the palace to be with a man?
No, never, never.
Silence!
How could you do such a thing at this time?
I don't want to see you. Leave!
Your Majesty, Yoon Sikyung claims
to have lain with Her Highness.
When did they get so close to each other?
I will lay down the death penalty on him.
Your Majesty must consider the people.
If this wedding gs awry,
the cries of the people suffering drought
will only grow louder.
Do not overlook your
greatest task over gossip.
Inspector Yoon, he got rid of the evidence.
Behind Inspector Yoon, Pak In.
Behind Pak In, the Queen.
This is a brand new
divination technique I made.
Eeny meeny miny mo
Eeny meeny miney mo
Mo
Morose
We'll be morose together.
- Let's break up.
- No
Then I'll change my name.
Change it to "Malyeo".
Then¦
Nee"
Need more space.
- Need... Need less space.
- This won't do.
We need less space.
- Need more.
- Need less.
- What is it with you?
- We need less space!
Did you wash your hair?
With iris water!
Smells like dishrag water?
You said you have something to show me.
You should have listened to me sooner.
Take a look.
Tied it so tight.
Ah, this won't budge.
I knew Pak In would cover his tracks
so I set these aside.
These ledgers contain his biggest bribes.
There are also records
that the Queen used witchcraft.
What about Yoon Sikyung?
If you don't put that back,
I'll call the guards.
Seo Doyoon may come to
steal the Four Pillars.
So reinforce the guards.
Inspector Yoon said this to me.
Master Yoon is waiting.
Excluding the criminal Nam Chiho,
the candidates' scores combine
preliminary round results and their
marital harmony with the Princess.
The candidate with the highest score
is Yoon Sikyung.
The wedding is tomorrow.
Your Highness should rest.
Hurry up.
This is heavy.
I'll save you, I'll save you.
Master, over here!
Let's go!
- Catch him!
- Move!
The reading of the marital
harmony will commence.
- Who is that?
- Im-ja Year, Gye-chuk Month, Gab-ja Day, Mu-jin Hour
Jung-sa Year, Eul-sa Month,
Shin-mi Day, Gab-oh Hour!
At ease
Yoon Sikyung has the spirit of wood,
and the Princess has the spirit of metal.
The wood in Yoon Sikyung
reveals his ambition.
His greed will drive him
through fire and water
and he will use the Princess
to take the highest seat possible.
- How dare you!
- Keep going
The ox in Yoon Sikyung's Four Pillars
and the horse in the Princess'
are destined to be at odds.
They will lose people and possessions,
they will be struck with barrenness,
and they will be in constant conflict.
Please kill me.
I, Seo Doyoon,
received Yoon Sikyung's Four Pillars,
and forged his marital harmony.
The words I spoke moments ago
came from Yoon Sikyung's true Four Pillars.
The harmony before Your Majesty
is the one I fabricated.
Therefore...
This marriage must be stopped at all costs.
Is this true?
Your Majesty, why would I do such a thing?
Seo Doyoon is slandering the throne
and accusing me falsely.
Why would he do such a thing?
Because he envies and despises me!
Speak for yourself, Seo Doyoon!
Why have you done this?
I realized that my acts
could bring someone lifelong misery.
"Someone"?
The Princess.
Take them away!
Let go! Let go!
How could this happen?
Seo Doyoon was stripped of his title
and sentenced to exile.
Pardon Seo Doyoon?
Are you in your right mind?
I beg you.
All of this is this girl's fault.
What are you saying?
Rather than a man attracted by my title,
I wanted to meet someone I could love
and spend my life with.
That is why I left the palace.
What?
Always changing and without warning...
That is the world this girl knew.
In my life,
I want the courage to stand up for myself,
I want to love,
and I want to become happy.
Father,
I beg you not to send Seo Doyoon away.
Have you been keeping him in your heart?
He is the only person
who came to my rescue.
He insulted the throne.
He deserved to die, yet I spared his life.
If it were not for this girl
he would not have done any wrong.
Enough, you are the Princess!
If only for the honor of the throne
he must be punished.
Then this girl...
will lay down her title
for Seo Doyoon's forgiveness.
How dare you?
What are you saying before me?
You have royal blood.
There are some things you cannot have!
Watch where you sing so
foolishly about love!
If you take love out of life...
then what is left?
Seo Doyoon has submitted these.
Please forgive my tardiness
in submitting this evidence.
Humbly, I tell Your Majesty
that one who reads fortunes
must also understand people.
Please kill me!
I committed a terrible crime!
I beseech you to forgive the Queen
who acted out of pity
for the sickly Prince.
And I beg you to consider her pain.
When a compassionate
heart reaches the skies,
the doors will open
for heaven and earth to become one.
This is the secret to moving the heavens.
Humbly, I offer this message.
It's lucky rain! Lucky rain!
Are you sure you won't
regret what you said?
What?
If you leave of your own will,
you will not be allowed back.
Will you still go?
Seo Doyoon is on his way to the docks.
I will send you there at once.
Father...
What are you doing just standing there?
The Princess defied the throne
by leaving the palace to travel.
Given the gravity of her offense,
she is hereby dethroned
and expelled from the palace.
Finally, all records of her
are to be completely erased.
How slowly we move....
Stop!
Your Highness!
This is indecent! You mustn't do this!
There's no other way.
Running will be faster.
What are you doing here?
I missed you!
I...
What am I...
to you?
Have I...
ever been a woman to you?
Not a moment has passed by...
that you were not a woman to me.
Subtitles created by Nlle