Earth...
before the war...
Life stretched out...
to every corner of the planet.
It became a world filled
with innovation and opportunity.
Huge leaps in science saw humanity achieve
unimaginable results.
Robotics became the way of the future.
Artificial intelligence
became the new religion.
We were the synthetic messiahs.
But such power...
in the proximity of primitives
only leads to one outcome:
war.
Bombs rained down...
wave after wave after wave.
The world entered a new Dark Age.
From the ash, a great sickness was born:
The Red Fever.
Nations fell. Societies collapsed.
Tribal warlords used us as weapons
against each other.
I was one of the last synthetics
to survive.
In the end, everyone lost.
I wanted life.
The humans wanted death.
I cannot be part of that.
I will not.
Delete entry and purge all memories.
Manual override confirmed.
Initiate hibernation mode.
I'm gonna get you!
No you won't!
Move it up!
Yeah, I got it, boss.
Raiders!
- Raiders!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Up top!
- Go, go!
Where are the children?
- Run, run, run!
- Go, go, go!
Where are the kids?
Get up! Up! Go on!
Food and shelter!
Raiders!
Fly! Now!
Come on!
Up top!
Raiders!
Right now! Right now!
You've got to go!
- Poppy, go! Poppy, please!
- Jack, you okay?
- We're gonna be okay.
- Poppy!
- Get up there as fast as you can!
- What?
- Where do I go?
- Faster! Faster! Come on!
Go back to whatever hellhole
you crawled out of!
Gun?
I ain't seen a gun working since the war!
Go ahead and shoot, old man!
No, Poppy!
Poppy, no!
Help me!
Whoo!
You're sure this is the place?
Yeah, she's here.
I know it.
What was this place?
Place used to be the future.
Now it's just dust.
Hey!
Come here.
This is the one we want.
Where is she?
Come on.
Wake up.
What do you see?
Who are you?
I'm the one who gave you life.
Where am I?
I've been looking for you for a long time.
No.
Come on! Wait up!
Careful, Billy!
Not too close to the water, please!
Hey, Rico!
Rico.
- How you feeling?
- Good.
How's she?
Better.
She just asked about you.
What you got there?
Still believe in that magic, huh?
It can save her.
Paradise Beach ain't real.
I don't know. I guess I just...
have a feeling it's out there.
Go see her.
- Hey.
- Mm.
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Pour me some tea, will you?
Yeah.
I remember when you were just like
those little ones.
You know there's medicine.
Paradise Beach.
I've heard stories about it.
There's no medicine out there.
There's just death and hate.
I can't let you go, Mom.
This oasis saved me
when I was young and broken.
Take care of it after I'm gone.
You're too young to die, Momma.
Wouldn't it be nice
if we could decide that for ourselves?
You'll be a great leader.
I can see it in your eyes.
Mom, I... I'm not really...
If I could do it again,
I would speak more softly.
I would listen longer...
and I would hold you more closely.
Whoo! Woo-hoo!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Hey, old-timer.
Hey.
- How you doing?
- All right.
- Yeah?
- Yup.
Hey, uh...
You ever see this place before?
Yeah, I've been there.
You don't want to go out there.
It's not a good place.
They call it the Temple of Life,
but it's not what it seems.
Yeah, well, I'm going.
I can't stop you.
Do as you will.
This is my new bride!
Her name's Ash.
Who wants to meet her first?
Hold her down. I'll fuck her in the face!
Fuck him.
Oh, shit!
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, man!
My man!
Now show me death.
Murder, murder, murder!
Murder! Yeah!
Yeah.
Good girl.
Mom.
I'm gonna fix this.
Hey!
Hey, you know the queen will die
if you don't tell me.
There's medicine there, right?
Medicine that can save her life.
Of course.
Look, I don't care how dangerous it is,
all right?
You need to tell me where it is.
All right,
it's on the shore of the Dead Ocean.
They can heal any pain there.
- You can almost live forever.
- "Live forever"?
Live forever but it's not a good place.
It's not what you think it is.
Tell me.
All right.
You take the North Star for three days
till you get to the Neon Forest.
When you get to the Neon Forest,
there are people there,
but you gotta be careful.
They'll tell you how to get to the Temple.
When you've reached the Dead Sea,
you've reached the Temple.
Go.
Here.
You're gonna need this.
And take these, too.
Good luck.
Be home soon, Mom.
I knew I'd find you here.
Look, you're not gonna stop me, all right?
That was never the plan.
You need help out there.
Let's go!
Paradise Beach,
a thousand mile ride...
His companion, Rico,
called it "The Road to Death. "
The prince spoke of the smell.
A constant presence in this wasteland...
is the smell of human flesh burning,
fat melting.
Fuel for the raiders.
Two guns, ten bullets.
We're gonna need every one.
The old traveler said
to follow the North Star.
See where it takes us.
Yes, sir!
It's your host with the most.
Welcoming all y'all to Love Town,
aka Titty City.
And from city to city, titty to titty,
we does it the best, baby!
Welcome to Love Town,
where everything goes down.
Are they robots like me?
No, them bitches is real.
They're gonna get old, get ugly,
and they're gonna die.
Not like you,
you gonna stay perfect forever.
Okay, that's the place
the old traveler was talking about.
Let's just get information and get out.
Keep your head down.
What is this place?
People who can't find love,
they buy love here.
Be careful.
Don't fall in love.
Stay close.
Hey!
Yeah.
You boys look a little lost.
What can I get you?
Some whiskey.
Take a seat.
For some info, if you got it.
What are you looking for?
Something called "Paradise Beach. "
Can you point us the right way?
I ain't never heard of it.
But I can ask Big Daddy.
He knows the wasteland
like the back of his hand.
I would be grateful.
Give these guys a round on me.
Have fun.
- Think she's gonna help us?
- Not sure.
Yo, Warlord.
You enjoying that robotic coo-coo?
Some guys down there are asking
about Paradise Beach.
- You seen them before?
- Nope. Not in here.
Them boys showed up on some shiny bikes.
Damn sure ain't from around here.
Yo, ain't you forgetting something?
I'm sorry, Daddy, I was gonna tell you...
You think you slick, don't you, bitch?
I got eyes all around this motherfucker.
Now hand it over.
Now kick rocks and go sell them drinks.
Y'all ready to welcome in the new bitches?
- Yes, sir.
- Well let's get it then.
You a bad girl.
You know, my family died of the fever.
There was nothing I could do.
Just because someone died
doesn't mean they're not with you.
You boys enjoying your beers?
You want a lap dance too, pretty boy?
Nah, we're good, we're good, we're good.
Our hoes ain't pretty enough for you?
Maybe you'd rather have some dick to suck.
Hey, we don't want any trouble!
Usually we charge a no-cover charge,
but you can just give us
the money straight up.
- Hey, leave us alone, all right?
- Shut the fuck up!
Put the knife away!
I find something I want, I take it, okay?
Okay?
The fuck you gonna do about it?
You ain't got no fucking bull...
- Stay back!
- Hey!
Stay back, or I got one for you, too!
Where the fuck did they get ammo?
No one got bullets no more.
Let's get out of here.
You boys sure do know how
to make an introduction.
And I like that shit, man.
But you can put the gun down.
This is a place of peace!
Back to business, everybody!
Not only am I the proprietor
of this fine establishment,
but I'm what you would call
a friendly panderer.
So you're just a pimp?
Ha! You say that like that's
a bad thing or something, man.
Let's go.
Pimp is the loneliest motherfucker
in this wasteland.
I can't trust none of these bitches.
Say, man, y'all trying to get
y'all dicks wet, or what?
We're actually looking for Paradise Beach.
We've heard there's medicine there.
Hm, drug town, I know about it.
Can you get us there?
Look, man, that shit is
a dirty business, kid.
If I help y'all, shoot,
it's like I'm perjuring myself.
Well, what is it worth to you cowboys?
So we basically partners now.
And I know somebody
that can get you there.
If you know what I'm saying.
Hey, you're sure you want to do this?
Let's see what he has to say.
Calm your boy down, and let's roll.
Come on, man. Follow me.
See, man, y'all should feel real special.
See, I never bring nobody back here.
I call this my Bitches Hall of Fame.
You the man, right?
Come in here, follow me.
Got something special for...
Wait a motherfucking minute.
Wait a motherfuck...
Hey, bitches, get the fuck out of here!
The fuck is wrong with y'all?
Can't believe this shit.
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave, too.
The kid needs to stay in my sight.
Say, man, my girl is shy.
If y'all wanna go to Paradise Beach,
he's gonna have to talk to her
all by his self.
Rico...
It's cool.
Hold on to this.
Aw,
you gonna give the little guy a gun, huh?
You got a blanket for him, too?
Oh, you's a flashy cowboy, ain't you?
Did I tell you I like that shit?
Now you, little fella, check it out.
I need you to have a real good time.
Relax, 'cause you in good hands.
Welcome to Paradise.
Oh, yeah, one more thing.
Don't be no stranger to danger.
'Cause it's about to go down.
How can I help you?
I'm looking for Paradise Beach.
Paradise Beach?
Yeah.
Yeah, my mom is very sick.
She's in trouble.
Yeah, and I don't have a lot of time.
I want to help you.
You're very kind.
I can see it in your eyes.
Who are you?
I'm Ash.
Your eyes...
Shut up and get on with it.
Yes.
You're not human?
I'm as human as you are.
What do you see?
I see you.
Can you feel?
I feel you.
Oh, shit! Look at that little old bitch.
Bring him to me!
Shit... I think I want me a robot bitch.
Bring him over here!
- Oh, ho, ho, ho!
- Get the fuck off me!
Get off!
Fuck you!
Come on.
Rico!
- Rico!
- String him up!
Rico!
Why did you kill Rico?
Bring me the gun!
Where'd you get these bullets?
Where are you from, boy?
Pull him up.
- What are you doing?
- Pull him up!
You gonna talk?
Let him down!
Where are you from, boy?
Pull him up!
You better sing, bird!
You better sing!
All right, let him down.
There.
The Oasis.
The Oasis?
- Yeah.
- You got more bullets there?
Yes.
You gonna take us there?
Fuck you.
Pull him up!
You better start singing, little bird!
You're running out of time!
I'll talk.
Let him down!
You're a bad bitch.
- Here you go.
- Ah!
Get up. Get up!
Let's go, baby.
Let's go!
We ride south
to the prince's homeland.
The warlord would rape
and murder everyone in the Oasis.
It was at that moment I became aware
of exactly how different I was.
But first...
I had to set things right.
What are you doing?
Yeah! Going somewhere?
Come back!
Come back, you fucking bitch!
God damn it!
Whoo!
Come on, come on!
Come on!
Down there! Go get her! Go get her!
Stop them!
Over here!
Where the fuck are they?
Fuck!
Come back!
Come back, you fucking robotic bitch!
Fucking come back!
Why did you save me?
I don't know.
You're his robot, right?
Yes.
So then why aren't you listening to him?
Maybe I'm malfunctioning.
What is this place?
I think it's a church.
My mother told me about places like this.
People would come here
when their souls need cleansing.
"Souls"?
What is souls?
Soul?
It's kind of hard to explain actually.
It's something inside you.
It makes you who you are.
All right.
There you go.
People used to come here
to try and talk to God.
Cleanse themselves of their sins.
What is "sins"?
Sin? You'll s...
Bad things that we do to each other.
Like what I did to you.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I don't want to sin.
Do you think I have a soul?
Yeah.
Yeah, I believe you do.
But I'm not human.
You know, one time, a traveler played
guitar for me in the Oasis.
I had never heard anything like it before.
It was...
It was... It was amazing.
It was like from another world.
And I asked him,
"So how do you play this music?"
And he told me his purpose on earth was
to reveal that the guitar had a soul.
Can you teach me how to talk to God?
Yeah.
Let's get on our knees.
And, uh...
close your eyes.
Your head just...
He's going to help us.
Ash?
Ash!
Ash, are you okay?
Ash, get up!
Ash.
Ash!
All right.
It's real.
Ash.
Ash, it's real.
We made it.
Who are you? Get on your knees!
Boo!
Oh...
Did I scare you?
Who are you?
Where's Ash?
You wanna play a little game?
Yeah! Come on!
Boys like to play games, don't they?
- No, I don't. I wanna play...
- Shh.
So here's the rules:
you ask a question,
and I ask a question.
Sounds like fun, no?
So...
Who are you?
I'm Prince.
Wait a minute. Seriously? You're a prince?
I mean, wow!
I'm in the presence of royalty!
- Who are you?
- Well, you know...
This is mi casa and I'm the jefe,
that's who I am.
This is the Temple of Life, isn't it?
Oh, wow!
Oh, man. Wow!
Paradise Beach!
God, it's so fucking pretty!
But unfortunately for you, young man,
this isn't paradise.
This...
is Drug Town!
Mm!
Pretty one.
Oh, what do we got here?
Temple of Life, I have to say,
that works, it really does,
but you know,
this is better than life, man!
I mean, there's no pain here.
It's only bliss!
I mean, where else are you gonna find that
in this fucked up world, right?
So, you're doing the whole tourist thing
of the wasteland or...
is there something else you're after?
Well, I heard you have cures.
Oh, yeah! We have loads of cures.
A lot.
My mom, she's very sick.
- Aw.
- She has the Red Fever.
That's a terrible, terrible sickness.
Wow, I feel for you.
But that particular cure, you know,
it's just a little hard
to come by these days.
So you don't have it.
We do. Come on!
This is it, all right?
This is where you're gonna get
your medicine, Prince.
In here?
Well, look, I know it's a little...
not much to look at, okay?
But we have everything you need.
First.
You have to become one of us!
What?
Hey.
You want the medicine for your mother?
This is how you're gonna get it.
- Why?
- Soon...
- Wait, wait! Wait, wait!
- ... your troubles
will be a thing of the past!
Okay, just hold on one second because...
Are you in?
Welcome to my world.
Feel that medicine flow through you.
Let it take over you, yeah.
Yeah, right? It's so nice.
It's so great, right?
Find out what's up with you.
Uhh!
You are bleeding like a monkey.
Mm! Yeah.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Ahh!
All right.
Oh, yeah.
Ahh!
You feel that, huh?
Yeah?
Yeah, you do.
I'm just gonna look at it right here.
Come on, baby.
Yeah.
Feel the pleasure.
Yeah, it magnifies everything,
that stuff burning
through your bloodstream,
and everything is magnified!
Joy, love, lust.
Jealousy!
Fucking hate!
Hate of the wasteland!
Now the moment of truth.
Hello?
You register?
Where am I?
Don't worry. You're in a safe space.
Yeah, um...
Sorry about that,
that stuff's hard to come by,
and you were bleeding like a pig.
You saved me.
Well, yeah, yeah, sort of.
Thank you.
Are you a prisoner?
I wouldn't call myself that.
So you can leave whenever you want?
You wouldn't understand.
But if I had a choice,
I'd stay where I'm at.
The wasteland's full of awful people.
I do understand.
That's how I got this.
What do you think?
This is all I've ever wanted.
This...
more than anything in Oasis.
Oasis? What's that, sweetie?
Oasis?
It's alive.
My mother didn't want me to leave.
She thought it was perfect.
It's not a complete and total mess
like the rest of the world.
It's blissful.
Yeah, it sounds pretty damn near perfect.
You see that?
Water here is dead.
We got nothing, we got nothing,
nothing, nothing inside of us.
You know, I'd love to see a tree,
see a flower in my lifetime.
I mean, it's sad, isn't it?
Isn't it so fucking sad?
Why do you have to make me so fucking sad?
Here.
Try this.
Just go...
Go ahh...
So your traveling companion, Ash?
She's the perfect woman, right?
Incorruptible by time.
Not of flesh and bones
but of something pure.
Yeah, God, I love that.
Purity, purity, it's just...
It's what I've been after.
Sweet dreams.
My son...
My prince...
Come home.
Oh, shit!
Get up! Get up!
You're just a sweet little baby,
aren't you?
My sweet, little baby.
What?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't be sad. Don't be sad.
Because I'm gonna cherish you...
and I'm gonna bring out the best in you.
And then... And...
And you're gonna bring out
the best in me, too.
Right?
Oh, thank you.
Game's simple, Prince.
What you want...
is in that sasquatch's belly.
Now we're gonna make a deal.
It's gonna be fun,
kind of like a fight to the death.
All right?
You win, you get the cure.
You lose, you die.
Fun!
Here's the wild card.
Now for the wild card.
Can't believe it.
Didn't know you had it in you.
What you want is in that man's stomach.
You earned that, boy.
Ash.
Let's get out of here.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You asked for a cure...
Not a robot.
No.
- I'm not going anywhere without her.
- I gave you your medicine.
I saved your friend's life.
She stays... with me.
No, fuck you, fuck this.
We're leaving.
Look, you can leave now,
or we could end it right here.
Hm?
I'm not leaving without her.
Leave.
Time's running out.
Ash...
Go.
Breaking my heart.
Told you I choose what I do.
I'm gonna get you out.
Shit! What if they come?
- It's okay.
- Shit.
Lei, it's okay.
How can you be so calm
when everything's gone to shit?
Stop.
It is what it is.
It is what it is?
I wish I could be like you.
I wish I could just...
not feel my feelings and worries so much.
You should cherish your feelings
whether they're good or bad.
Can you feel this?
And this?
Yes.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't be doing this.
I shouldn't take advantage of you.
Lei...
I like this feeling.
It was at this moment...
I made a connection.
I feel something.
Something pure.
I've never had this feeling before.
It's so different than all the others.
Sorry.
Don't be.
I wanted to.
Could feel your heartbeat.
Your energy.
And I don't even know
what that is anymore.
I was taken from my family
when I was a young girl.
A group of raiders took me.
I was so little.
And I learned how really awful
people can be.
Then I got older.
They no longer had use for me so...
they just sold me away.
That's how I ended up here.
I'm really glad you fixed me, though.
Me too.
She was supposed to be the perfect woman.
She's pure, right?
Wow.
So fucking pure.
I gave you...
I gave you everything, though.
I raised you,
I gave you respect.
You don't understand.
You took away the one thing
that was supposed to be mine.
Fucking corrupted her!
You're a...
You're... You're a virus.
disgusting, sneaky, little virus.
Don't say that!
Shut your fucking mouth.
You know what? Everything's gonna be okay.
No, no, no, yeah. We're gonna fix this.
So, um...
What we're gonna do is...
You're gonna wipe her hard drive.
You're gonna wipe it clean.
Boom. Done.
Fresh fucking start, right? Yeah.
When she wakes up,
she's not gonna remember you...
or any of this shit.
When she wakes up...
she's gonna see me.
She's gonna...
She's gonna love me.
They're right there! Get them!
Hurry up! This way!
Hurry the fuck up! They're right there!
Get them!
What the fuck?
No, please!
My fucking palace. I'm the fucking jefe.
Get the fuck out!
Yeah!
Fuck you!
No fucking pain, motherfucker!
You like that? You like that?
Fucking bitch.
Hi.
Stop.
Take them.
They tried to take my bride.
She's mine!
They tried to make friends with her.
Take her away from me!
She's mine!
Put them down there.
- Come on.
- Ash... Ash!
Cut off their heads.
That's not you, Ash.
Don't listen to him, Ash.
It's not you.
Kill them.
- Kill them now.
- No.
Stop, you demonic bitch!
Kill them!
No!
- Stop!
- What?
- Stop the bike!
- Why?
- Stop!
- Ash, what are you doing?
- Stop! Get off!
What are you doing?
Ash!
Warlord is dead.
But another will replace him.
This world has no memory.
Everyone, the prince is back!
I have to go do something.
What?
Where are you going?
You gave me a soul.
Mom.
Mom!
I have the medicine.
My son...
We continue onwards...
searching for others like me.
We have to find them
and show them what we learned.
That beyond all intellect and knowledge
exists something greater,
something more powerful than any person,
any weapon.
Hope.
Man, what's taking
so goddamn long with my food?
Can a pimp get something to eat
around this motherfucker?
Shit, if I have to wait any longer,
I swear I'mma put my foot
in one of you bitches' ass.
Fuck!
Ahh! Fucking bitch!
You're all free now!
What the fuck are you doing?
Fuck! Rosie!
Rosie!
Fuck! Help! Somebody fucking help!
Fuck!