VAV STUDIO .:. VIETTORRENT.VN
www.facebook.com/VAV.AudioViet
VAV STUDIO
© Copyright 2013, All rights reserved
Subtitles by DramaFever
You give us Baek San and we hand over
Jung Yoo Gun to you.
This is Ui Sang Chul's
address you asked for.
Why do I need to agree
to this hostage exchange?
Because you are
Team Leader Jung's father.
Please stay alive.
I have something I have to ask you.
Did you find Baek San?
We are looking for him.
Is Soo Min still alive?
Thank you for coming back.
Why did you come back?
Who's there?
I'm sorry.
I came really late, didn't I?
Episode 13
Eat slowly.
Are you being chased or something?
You might get an upset stomach.
I have something to tell you.
This will be a sad story for you.
What is it?
Don't joke around.
Hurry up and tell me.
Don't be shocked
and listen carefully now.
Rey, the yellow head, you like.
He died.
Really?
How?
Look at this now.
I knew you'd be shocked.
You're aware that there was an exchange
mission for Baek San and Jung Yoo Gun?
Not only Rey... but every IRIS operative
was annihilated by the NSS
during that mission.
Rey was taken after he
received multiple gunshot wounds.
But I'm sure he's dead.
I thought I had killed him...
You killed him?
What are you talking about now?
Do you know why I ran
away from Japan?
I was caught while trying to kill Rey.
I barely escaped and ran away.
Rey that bastard, did he get caught
cheating on you?
Get serious.
Our relationship isn't like that.
I just pretended to like him
so I could use him.
Is that right?
Then I guess I don't need to
dye my hair.
You listen to me now.
I wanted to kill him the moment
he allied with the North.
If you are finished,
have one more bowl.
Wait.
It's nearby.
Wait a minute.
This is Section Chief, Hwang Tae Yoon...
who'll be in charge of
the situation room starting today.
It feels good to be back.
- Mi Jin.
- Yes.
Can you clear Team Leader Jung's desk?
What? But...
Section Chief Hwang will be
using it from now on.
Yes.
You called for me?
Do you remember the things
I told you in confidence?
- Yes.
- I still trust you.
But that's not the official
position of the NSS.
You still haven't been
cleared from all the charges.
Finding Baek San and Yoo Jung Won...
I want you to help me with it.
You mean unofficially?
I just told you a moment ago.
I can't officially help you.
You decide. Either you can continue
to be on house arrest. If not...
you can come out and help me
find Baek San and Yoo Joong Won.
You're giving me options
in which I have no choice.
It's the key to a locker
in Sadang Station.
You'll find the things you need in there.
You can use the cellphone in the
locker to communicate with me.
It's encrypted so it's impossible to trace.
Move in the shadows... and
find Baek San and Yoo Joong Won.
I'm back.
How did your exam go?
- I bombed it.
- Again?
They always have the things I don't know.
Ah, seriously...
You probably don't know that much.
That's probably why you bomb it every time.
Not true. I used to get good
grades until high school.
- How can I believe that?
- Why wouldn't you believe me?
I was a good student.
I was a class representative, too.
- Hi, how are you?
- Oh, you're here.
We aren't here today to eat.
By any chance...
have you ever seen this woman?
Yes, I know this woman.
I just saw her a moment ago.
- Where?
- At the cafe across the street.
Maybe it's been about 10 minutes?
Thank you.
Someone is tailing me.
Cut it off.
Ji Hun.
This is a Code F5 situation.
Requesting for back up
in the area JH730.
Hello.
It's me, Mother.
Really?
I'm back.
I knew you'd be back, Yoo Gun.
But you know... Mother...
I have something urgent
I have to take care of.
After that I'll come and see you.
I have a lot to tell you too.
Hurry up and come, Yoo Gun.
Yes.
Yoo Gun is coming.
He must be released.
Excuse me.
Is anyone here?
Like this... it was my dream
to live smelling the earth.
You can do that from now on.
Do you think I could?
Tell me.
- Ui Sang Chul is dead.
- What?
We need a forensic team here.
I'll send out the team right away.
So keep the scene intact.
Okay.
Are you sure?
Why is Baek San there?
Did you find out the address?
Send it now.
Do you think Baek San is really there?
I think he is.
I just have a feeling that he is.
I wonder who's here?
Yoo Gun.
I'm so relieved.
I'm really relieved.
Mo... Mother.
I'm sorry.
I have someone I want you
to meet.
Sang Joon.
Do you remember?
If we have a boy, we
wanted to call him 'Gun'.
Even though I had him
follow my last name...
I kept the promise I made with you.
I combined your last name
'Yoo' and the name 'Gun'...
Yoo Gun.
This is your father.
Yoo Sang Joon.
Good to see you.
Please now.
Mother!
Ji Young.
Hang in there.
Captain, why don't we
get out of here first?
Yoo Gun.
I missed you so much.
I was so happy...
that I got to see you again.
Yoo Gun.
Please forgive your father...
It's my... it's my wish...
We lost Baek San right in front us.
Jung Yoo Gun should be in jail now.
How the hell did he get here?
Calm down.
We'll have another chance.
Just an innocent woman got shot.
Don't worry too much about it.
Still, it shouldn't have been...
I, too, have a mother.
I just hope she doesn't die.
Do you think the NSS
will take Baek San back?
We can't be sure.
I can't believe Baek San is
Jung Yoo Gun's father.
Fill me in on the situation
at the scene first.
Yes.
It's been over 24 hours
since Ui Sang Chul has been killed.
We discovered a gun that appeared
to have been used as the murder weapon.
Including the gun,
the forensic team is...
looking for fingerprints
in other parts of the house.
Okay. We'll wait for the
results from there and...
I need to send you
somewhere right away.
Take the Operation B team
and pick up Baek San.
Do you know where he is?
Is this Baek San's location?
This is a location tracer.
The day before he disappeared,
Section Chief Oh implanted it in Baek San.
You'll know when you see it.
He's going away from
where he was staying.
I'll transmit his location.
Go get him.
You must bring him alive.
Understood.
Where would you like to go now?
Just go anywhere for now.
Okay.
Can't be...
It can't be...
Stop the car.
Do you have a knife?
Yes.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Did you catch him?
I got close to him but...
the signal was lost.
What?
You were already here.
Well...
There is something you
need to know.
I don't know what
I could say in condolence.
I know that no words can do
any justice but...
because it was such
a long ago and I was so young...
I don't exactly remember
how I felt that day.
Did you know it?
The fact that my father is Baek San
and my mother...
When my mother passed away,
he was there.
No, I didn't know.
The fact that Baek San is
your father...
I just heard from Team Leader Ji.
When did you find out?
Before my mother passed away...
that's what she told me.
Isn't funny?
I thought he killed my father.
It's as if it's a dream.
It was Yoo Joong Won.
The one who killed my mother.
He must have pursued Baek San.
I'm definitely going
to catch that bastard.
Rey woke up at the hospital.
We may be able to find out from him
where Yoo Joong Won is.
I'm going to interrogate him myself.
If I find anything,
I'll let you know right away.
I'll be in touch.
I know you're awake.
Ah, I slept well.
Men should keep their nails
short and cut straight across.
No matter how handsome the man is
it's a turn off when he
has long dirty nails.
With my looks, you can give me
a break. Right?
With these looks, perhaps...
still not okay.
Feels good.
It's been a while.
Sorry, I couldn't stop
by often, Brother.
That's okay. I know you're busy.
And yesterday...
Father came by.
I guess you knew it, too.
Yoo Gun's mother has left...
to go near him.
Yeah.
I'm so scared.
I feel like the people I love are...
leaving my side one by one.
Deputy Director.
The one who killed Ui Sang Chul
has been discovered.
Who was it?
- It was Team Leader Jung.
- What?
What should I do?
Jung Yoo Gun has a surveillance
team watching him.
We can arrest him after the funeral.
Wouldn't it be dangerous?
Rather...  what's going on with Rey?
He'll be transported to our
confinement system this afternoon.
I'm going to interrogate him.
He can't make contact
with anyone before that.
Understood.
You'll need to come with us.
Any report on Baek San?
No, nothing yet.
Yes.
Team Leader Jung did?
I got it.
Team Leader Jung...
has disappeared again.
What?
What is it now?
Team Leader Jung has run
away from the charnel house.
I'll put him on the wanted list.
No, not yet.
Section Chief Hwang
is with the A Team, right?
Yes.
Section Chief Hwang will solely
trace Jung Yoo Gun's location.
Understood.
Tell me.
Where is Mr. Black?
Mr. Black is going to get me out.
Then... I'm going to kill you.
Is that so?
That's not going to work.
Talk.
- Captain.
- What is it?
- Yun Hwa.
- What?
Can you give us a minute?
What?
I have something I need to
discuss with Park Tae Hee.
It'll just be a minute.
I just received call from the Representative
and I hear the talk with Mr. Black went well.
That's great.
And... we received our first
mission from Mr. Black.
What is it?
Rey has regained his consciousness.
He's currently jailed at the NSS.
I get what he wants.
Gather the team and prepare
for a mission.
Understood.
What are you doing now?
What did you talk about with her
without me?
Why can't I hear what
you were talking about?
It's not like that.
If not, then what?
Yun Hwa, I would like you to stop now.
I don't like to see you
getting involved in...
this dangerous work.
You asked me to help you and now...
you want me to stop?
- No matter how much I think about it...
- Still...
I still haven't even begun my revenge.
Listen to me now.
I'll take your revenge for you.
We'll be all good then.
Tell me.
What was that phone call about?
Who was it from?
- It was Mr. Black.
- What did he say?
Rey regained his consciousness.
That's good. I'll have a
chance to kill him myself.
Since many of Team Leader Jung's
fingerprints were discovered....
it's definite that he was
at Ui Sang Chul's house.
Just based on that evidence alone,
doesn't make him the murderer.
So what I'm saying is...
they were definitely his fingerprints.
Okay, over here...
Do you see this corner?
When we get fingerprints...
this is how we lift it.
So on the gun we found
at the crime scene...
along with the fingerprint, we also
found a square shape with corners.
Are you saying someone
planted the evidence?
I'm saying that
there's a possibility.
But Team Leader Jung probably doesn't
even know he's a murder suspect.
Where the hell did he go?
Shi Hyuk, you should secure Section Chief
Hwang and Jung Yoo Gun's identities.
Next time, Section Chief Oh should
only tell us facts not possibilities.
So he's been looking for me?
We don't know what the reason is but...
What do you think?
I heard you asked to see me.
Okay.
Now it's just the two of us.
Talk to me.
Get me out of here.
Is he out of his mind?
He called me all the way here
to talk about this nonsense?
Am I crazy, to give you up?
I can give you Mr. Black.
You have to notify him
that I've escaped.
That's the only way you
can contact him.
One condition.
Send me and Soo Jin to Switzerland.
What are you talking about?
How can I trust you?
Talk to Soo Jin.
Ask her about Escape Plan E2.
Director.
Please... get me out of here.
I'll tell you anything you want.
Just help me get out of here.
Tell me about...
Escape Plan E2.
The escape plan Rey and
Lee Soo Jin talked about matched.
It's probably an old manual
or some sort.
Rey was the one
Mr. Black trusted the most.
If he trusted him that much,
there must have been a reason.
What do you mean?
Making a request to run away to a
different country to get out alone...
doesn't fit his
behavioral pattern so far.
I'm sure it must have been
a difficult decision.
I understand you've been using some
painful methods to induce him to talk.
I'm not trying to make
an issue out of that.
More than anyone else,
Deputy Director is
probably the one who
wants to catch Mr. Black the most.
Okay, what would you like to do?
I think the decision needs to
be made by the acting Director.
We'll do it.
Team Leader Ji should figure out
the details and proceed.
- But Deputy Director...
- I'm not trusting Rey completely.
So we need to be prepared
on multiple levels.
I understand.
Is it encrypted?
Yes, it can't be traced at all.
This is Baek San.
It's been a long time.
How far do you intend to go?
Did you meet your son?
Soo Min whom I met for
the first time in 30 years, died.
Was Yoo Joong Won also sent by you?
I guess you can say that.
The next will be Jung Yoo Gun.
Why don't we meet?
We should stop playing
hide and seek now.
Not yet.
When the time comes...
I'll come and find you.
Did you send your mother away well?
Yes.
Rey suggested a way
to meet with Mr. Black.
Yoo Joong Won has probably
allied himself with Mr. Black.
So, other than the NSS's
backup plan...
I want you to be involved as well.
Tell me the time and location.
You have to be extra cautious.
If people find out that
I've been helping you...
that'll be the end of everything.
You won't have anything to
worry about.
Okay.
The mission has begun.
Get ready.
Yes.
When a text message is sent using the phone
from locker number 19 at Kimpo Airport...
IRIS will read that as Rey
succeeding in escaping.
They'll rendezvous at the
pre-determined location.
Have you found out
the rendezvous location?
No, the location will be
sent to the cellphone.
If this is a trick
and he tries to escape...
would it be okay to kill him?
Sure, you can kill him.
This is Lieutenant Lee Chul Min.
- Good to meet you.
Sergeant Major of the 7th Regiment,
Bong Myung Chul.
I'd been undercover, acting as a
North Korean escapee.
I'm Yoo Joong Won from
the Foreign Intelligence Division.
The mission we're preparing is one
step toward the welfare of the Republic.
You will all be decorated as
top warriors of the revolution.
Until the unification of our country...
do not be afraid to shed blood.
Salute to the Captain.
Take off now.
Please be on standby.
Connected to the underground
traffic signal system.
I'll ask the airport security
team for cooperation.
They've departed.
We found the lockers.
We've secured all of the
items in the locker.
Open it.
The password.
I said the password.
It's backwards.
What do we send?
Escape successful.
Plan E2.
What's this code for?
It's a location code.
It's a location code. G177613.
We'll be moving right away.
Where does the code point to?
Just a moment.
Hurry up and put the location on screen.
It's a church located in Paju
in Gyeonggido.
A church?
Words of Jesus aren't always
easy to put into action.
The words from the Gospel we'll
discuss today are 'Love your enemy'.
Indeed, this isn't easy to do.
We'll rent this place for a minute.
With all of you here.
Get ready. They'll arrive soon.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
This is...
Team Leader Lee.
By any chance, is the location code
pointing at a church?
Yes, it's a church in Paju.
Halt the mission.
Tell me what's going on.
Tell me now!
I told you once that I wanted to
make a confession to your brother.
Did you say your brother was a priest?
Do you think there will be a day I get
to make a confession to your brother?
That's going to be today.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Within 30 minutes from now
we'll exchange Rey and Lee Soo Jin
for the hostages here in the church.
I told you once that I wanted to
make a confession to your brother.
That's going to be today.
Why did you follow me here?
I told you. Now Rey and IRIS
are all my enemies.
I'll keep my promise with the
Deputy Director no matter what.
There is something behind the wall.
Now, listen to me carefully.
If you want to take
revenge on the Republic...
just as you'd allied yourself with IRIS...
I also need to appear
to have allied myself with IRIS.
The Deputy Director of NSS and
the terrorist sympathizer?
It's a dangerous combination.
My wish is for South Korea to secure its
status as a country with nuclear weapons.
VAV STUDIO .:. VIETTORRENT.VN
www.facebook.com/VAV.AudioViet
© Copyright 2013, All rights reserved