That thing...
comes from the East Sea.
Come for some sushi.
- Excuse me, come for some sushi. - What?
That thing possesses people.
It penetrates into one's
dark side and weakness...
and possesses them.
What is she doing?
A person who is possessed by that
thing is no longer a human being.
It enjoys the death of people,
deceives them,
and laughs at them.
Sohn comes from...
the East Sea.
I hope this year is better.
Let's do better this time.
He has grown up so much.
Hwa Pyung, come over here
and help the elders.
Hwa Pyung, stop being rude.
Turn down that TV!
That woman...
is staring at me so frighteningly.
What woman?
That woman hiding behind you.
That woman who has no hair.
Are you going to do it again?
I told you not to say such
things in front of others.
About 20 years ago,
an elder's first daughter
died of lung cancer.
She screamed in pain...
and caused quite a fuss.
That's what he saw.
A psychic has been born from
a hereditary shaman family.
We need to accept it.
That's the fate of a psychic.
Answer me!
Didn't you hear what Mother just said?
There's nothing Hwa Pyung can do about it.
Mom.
Is there...
something wrong with me?
No.
But if you see something from now on,
just pretend you don't see
it, and just tell me.
Okay?
Okay.
I don't like that mint-flavored candy.
Why? This is my favorite candy.
Why do we worship the wind and rain?
We pray that we will catch many fishes
and that ships will avoid accidents.
- There is another reason too.
- What is it?
Haven't you heard about the
ghost named Park Il Do?
Park Il Do?
I heard this when I was a kid.
A strange man suddenly came to our village.
He seemed mentally ill.
After that man came, some people
from the village disappeared.
Rumors spread that they
were killed by that man.
But it turned out that he
was possessed by a ghost.
That ghost said that his name was...
Park Il Do?
Yes, Park Il Do.
The villagers performed an exorcism,
but failed. They tried to chase him away,
and that man went wild.
He stabbed his own eye with a knife...
and ran into the East Sea.
He didn't die for days and
floated in the water...
staring at the villagers.
Scary, isn't it?
Since then, people have been
saying, "Park Il Do is coming."
"Sohn is coming."
- "Sohn?" - Yes.
- You know, Sohn means guest... - Hey.
What are you saying to a kid? I
wondered what you were saying.
The mountain and the wind
- Yes! - Yes!
Go to the south of the river
But things go south
We humans are the rivers
We humans are the mountains
- Yes! - Yes!
The rivers make its bend
The mountains are too high
Now we are all gathered here
to pray for our wellbeing.
Please provide this village
with water and light.
We wish for a good harvest this year.
Please fill our boats
up with loads of fish.
Please bring peace to our
family and children...
and let us lead a healthy and happy life.
We pray you will grant
each of our families...
all our wishes.
We pray to you.
Let us plant blue and red
flags on our boats...
and fill our boats with loads of fish.
We pray to you.
Look at him. He slipped.
Come on, let's go now.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
What happened?
Where did he go?
What happened to him?
Where is he?
What's happening?
Woong jin!
- Where did he go? - We should help him.
Someone help him.
- Someone help him! - What's happening?
Help him!
Sohn is coming.
He's coming!
Woong Jin, how are you feeling?
Can't you still see through that eye?
Go inside and rest, Father.
Are you insane?
Stop him!
Stop!
You!
Drop that knife!
This instant!
What on earth...
Please...
- What happened? - Hwa Pyung!
Hwa Pyung!
The doctor said...
that there's nothing wrong with him.
Hwa Pyung.
You still can't see through your right eye?
No.
What?
Do you see something?
You can tell me. Mom is here.
It's telling me not to say anything.
If I do,
it's saying it will kill everyone.
Hwa Pyung.
Hwa Pyung!
- Oh my gosh! No! - Oh no.
No!
- Stop him. - Honey!
This can't be!
No, this can't be.
Come on out. We have to begin.
Please come visit us
My ancestral spirit Please come visit us
We're gathered here to pray
Please come visit us
We pray to my ancestral spirit
Please listen to our prayer
Get lost, evil spirit!
Take this!
Poor boy possessed by an evil spirit.
He's possessed by an evil spirit
that committed suicide. Get lost.
If you don't get lost,
I'll tell the master,
separate your flesh and bones,
and cook you in a cauldron.
You evil spirit, get lost!
- Honey. - Oh, my!
Oh, no!
Ma'am!
Ma'am, are you okay? Ma'am!
Ma'am.
He should be killed.
What?
He...
Evil spirits possess humans and kill them.
He is one of them.
He controls small ghosts...
and lets them possess weak people.
He's possessed by a powerful ghost.
He should be killed.
- Ma'am. - Ma'am.
Hwa Pyung.
Father, how is my child?
He's not possessed.
He doesn't react to the
bible nor the cross.
There's no proof.
If he's not possessed
by a ghost, what is it?
My family died because of him.
You said you were an exorcist priest!
Cut it out.
You'd better watch your
mouth in front of priests.
By the way,
what are all these scars?
He did it to himself.
He did it to himself with his own force.
Is there anyone who would have
abused him behind your back?
What did you say?
Are you saying I did it?
I told you to stay quiet!
You'd better take him to a doctor.
I'm afraid there's nothing we can do.
Father, you can't just leave like this.
Tell him to leave.
Cult freaks.
Exorcist priest, my foot!
If there's anything you want to talk about,
come to the cathedral or my place.
It's close from here.
See you.
I'd like to tell you something.
Sohn...
Are you sick?
No, I'm just worried about the kid.
That happens a lot.
Most of the cases turn out
to be domestic violence.
Very little of them are actually
possessed by an evil spirit.
By the way,
you...
seem to be too weak for this job.
You could end up letting it have...
control over you.
No.
Today, I've become assured of...
my belief.
Belief?
All of a sudden?
I think I should go home.
I miss my family so much.
What brings you here?
There's good news.
What news?
You'll know soon.
Where is he?
Yoon?
He went to the private lesson.
He didn't ditch school, did she?
No.
For the first time,
I'm sure about my faith.
What?
Why is the dog barking so much?
Let me go have a look.
Dad.
I can...
see things now.
He should be killed.
Evil spirits possess humans and kill them.
He is one of them.
- Dad. - You evil spirit.
Please stop.
You are not my son.
Die!
No!
No! Let go of him.
- What are you doing? - Let go of me!
Leave him alone!
You told me when I was young...
that I didn't have enough belief.
But why did you make me become a priest?
I told you I hated it! I
didn't want to be a priest!
I told you!
Hello?
Is this Yoon's home?
Yoon didn't come to the
academy again today.
Hey. What are you doing over there?
What is he doing?
Hey.
Are you okay?
Over there.
Over there. Inside there...
Wait here.
Stay in the car. I'll be back.
Aren't you going to talk to me?
I told you not to skip private lessons.
May I help you?
There's a kid in front of your house.
Does he live here?
My little brother is at home.
I see.
It's so hot outside. Can
I have a glass of water?
I'm from the police.
Come in.
Thank you.
There's no one home.
I'll leave as soon as I drink this.
I need to use the bathroom.
I'm at a detached house near
Yoonmyeon intersection.
Bring all the backup you can.
Kid.
Come here.
It's all right.
Run!
Why did you hide him?
Hey, where's my mom?
Where is my mom?
I don't know!
You shouldn't go.
You'll die if you go inside.
Wait! Mom!
Mom!
- Stay away. - Mom.
Mom! Wake up!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Wake up!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
One meal set, please.
All right.
It's been three days since Lee Ha Bo...
went missing.
Hey, newbie. Did you fill the quota?
Not yet.
I'm not a newbie. I'm transferred.
He's right. You've been driving a taxi...
in different cities, right?
Yes, I was looking for someone.
That's unusual for a young man.
Are you chased by a loan
shark or something?
Come on.
Maybe he's looking for his
lover who ran away from him.
I'll let you know when I find
your wife who ran away from you.
Damn. What a funny dude.
A 40-year-old man surnamed Jeong...
stabbed and killed staff
of a convenience store...
with a knife after an argument.
After committing the crime, he...
Take us to any motel. Hurry up.
Darn it.
Why? What is it?
She's not your girlfriend, is she?
It's none of your business.
You'd better be careful, if you
don't want to be arrested.
- What? - Her brother...
is a police officer.
You didn't know that?
How do you know that?
I have psychic ability.
I'm supposed to have become a shaman,
but it's a long story.
You seem to even have a girlfriend...
who has a temper.
Let me see. She's got a phone
call from her brother.
What are you going to do?
Damn it.
Yes, I'm a taxi driver.
Wake up and get out of the car.
You're home.
Is this your place?
Who do you think you are?
- Pardon? - Gosh.
I wanted to date him and
now you messed it up.
Hey, I'm not paying for the drive.
You have to pay.
Hey, you have to give me money.
My goodness.
What a day.
Hey, sorry I have kept you waiting.
- It's okay. - Are you sure?
We have some time. Would you
like to go eat something?
- How about fried chicken? - Sounds good.
- Let's go eat fried chicken.
- I can't wait.
I've always wanted to watch this movie.
Sorry, I've mistaken you.
I used to have faith.
Please give me a dollar
so I can buy alcohol.
You're one tall man whose eyes are...
full of sexual energy.
You'll waste your entire
life as a libertine...
with alcohol, women, and gambling.
And when you're old, you'll get
soaked with poop on the street.
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing at
my workplace at this time?
Did you hear any news?
About possessed people?
Don't talk about scary things at night.
There's no news.
Are you here to ask me
that question or to eat?
Both.
Haven't you heard anything
from other shamans yet?
Including churches and Buddhist temples.
There aren't many people who are
possessed by powerful ghosts.
Maybe they think that
you're not good anymore.
That must be why you don't hear anything.
Hey, you rude brat.
I'm Yukgwang.
Six rays of light.
If you're so frustrated,
you become a shaman yourself.
You're possessed too.
That was a long time ago. I'm not anymore.
Do you ever call your grandpa?
Well,
sometimes.
What is he called, Priest Choi?
Anyway, stop following him around.
We can't deal with him.
Do you even look in the mirror?
Look what a mess you are.
How can a young man like you
live like there's no tomorrow?
Are you here?
I hated it as a kid,
but now I wish I could still see spirits.
Then I could see you, Mom.
I'll catch him.
I'll catch him...
by all means.
Hey!
What are you doing there?
Please call the police.
What?
Did you find something there?
My goodness.
I was supposed to be on
vacation from tomorrow.
I promised my daughter I'd
take her to a water park.
Water park? Forget about it.
We already had so much to do,
and now we have a murder case?
Look who's here.
What is she doing here?
Kang Gil Young!
My goodness.
Is that how you bow to us? Is
your neck stiff or something?
There's an investigation going on...
to take disciplinary action against you.
You should have stayed at the station.
The result is not out yet.
Who told her? You?
How can you eat at the scene?
You didn't have breakfast, did you?
- My goodness.
- You need to think before you act.
The guy you beat up wants to
file a civil suit against you.
What are you, a gangster?
He isn't a suspect. He's a criminal.
Also, he's been convicted of
sexual assault three times.
- He deserves to be beaten to death.
- Cut it out.
Send her back. Do as I say.
Do you have some more?
Has he been identified?
The CEO of Shiil Service.
His ID card, cell phone,
and wallet were all here.
It seems like he died from excessive
bleeding after being stabbed, right?
He must have been stabbed
at least 15 times.
He must have been transferred
here after death, right?
Yes.
He must have been killed in a car
before being transferred here.
The car is nearby.
It is?
That's strange.
Everything about this is strange.
The drain is completely
dry, but the body is wet.
Could the water be from the reservoir?
- Where's the car? - Right over there.
There it is.
What a weird punk.
Who? The killer?
Why would he leave his car here
and the body in the drain?
He could have hidden both the car
and the body if he wanted to.
It looks as if he had a reason
to leave the body in the drain.
How would we know what
the killer was thinking?
We're normal people.
Did you talk to the janitor?
Yes. But he said he wasn't the
first one to find the body.
A young man found it first.
A sly-looking taxi driver,
according to the janitor.
A taxi driver?
Hey, stop it!
What is the taxi driver now?
Why do you want to know about our CEO?
He is involved in a criminal case.
Do you clean drains too?
We do.
Have you ever cleaned the
drains of Nakmak Reservoir?
Well... It was a couple of months ago.
Something happened, right?
One of our employees got hurt.
Hurt?
Cleaning drains is a pretty dangerous job.
Our client was...
pushing us,
so our employee got seriously injured.
Did that make him fall out with the CEO?
He was just a temporary worker.
If our client keeps pushing us,
what can we do?
Many people seem to want to
know about that incident today.
Was someone else here?
A taxi driver came...
and asked for Kim Young Soo's phone number.
Did he look sly by any chance?
Thank you.
By the way, where are you from again?
Well...
Our organization was founded recently.
We're looking into cases...
where workers were treated unfairly.
He had a choking accident in the drain,
which resulted in brain damage.
He can't walk or speak properly anymore.
It was raining so hard,
and they forced him to clean the drain.
The CEO refuses to take responsibility.
They say a temporary worker is not
entitled to any compensation.
The big company that gave them
the work is just sitting back.
They put all the blame on my husband.
That's terrible.
If I may,
I'd like to talk to your
husband for a moment.
Sure.
Hello, sir.
I have some questions for you.
Do you understand what I say?
Well...
Have you ever...
seen this man by any chance?
Who is he?
Has he ever been here?
Honey.
What's wrong?
Please go back now.
If your husband starts to act strangely,
please contact me, okay?
Here's my number.
Sorry? What do you mean?
He might start to act
like a different person.
Then you need to call
me as soon as possible.
I don't care if you call me at night.
Do you understand?
Okay.
Bye.
Who are you?
Well, I just talked to your parents.
I'm from a social organization.
Aren't you going in?
I have to eat and go to a private class,
but I don't want to go in.
Why not?
Are you scared of your dad or something?
How did you know?
I know these things well.
Don't worry too much. He'll get better.
But his brain is damaged.
He's not likely to recover.
I know that much.
- You may be right. - But...
regardless of his injury, he's
been a little weird lately.
What do you mean?
He's like a different person.
Did you see anything?
I have to go to a lesson.
Oh, I'm sorry. You said you need to eat.
Here. Get something on your way.
I can't take it.
I'll get in trouble.
Gosh. What is it?
I can't give you a ride.
I'm taking a break.
I'm from the police. Please step out.
Why?
Am I not supposed to park here?
On TV, the police always
show their ID cards.
Are you really from the police?
You were at Nakmak Reservoir
this morning, weren't you?
Was I?
Well, a taxi goes everywhere.
I have a reservation. Can I go now?
Your hand. You could have hurt yourself.
You have a wrong person.
You got caught on security cameras
around Nakmak Reservoir...
and at Shiil Service.
It's you.
Gosh.
You have no criminal record.
Yun Hwa Pyung, what were
you doing there so early?
I was just passing by. I'm
a taxi driver, you know.
It's a remote place.
I had to pee. Fine, I peed on the street.
Please forgive me this once.
Were you just passing by the
victim's former office too?
Yes. What's with this guy?
His face is a mess.
You beat him up?
Can you still do that these days?
Hey. You want me to beat you up too?
Answer my questions.
You said I was just a witness.
Gosh, are you allowed to do this?
If you keep this up, I will
have you arrested as a suspect.
- Why? - Don't you think it's suspicious?
What you've done.
- You want me to tell you the truth? - Yes.
Well...
It'll probably sound strange.
I have this special ability.
What should I say?
I see things.
It started when I was little.
Last night,
I suddenly saw the killer
leave the body in the drain.
Are you kidding me?
I knew you wouldn't believe it.
Hey, the first identification
result is out. Let's go.
Hold on.
What about me? I have an emergency.
- What emergency?
- You won't believe me anyway.
Wait here.
Gosh. I really have an emergency.
He's the taxi driver, right?
Wrap it up and send him back.
He's really suspicious.
He visited both the victim's workplace...
and the injured employee's home.
Why would he? That's really strange.
Did they find anything on the body?
Salt.
The body was soaked in seawater.
Isn't that weird?
Was there seawater in
the drain or something?
There are 14 stab wounds.
And they're all in random places.
What a crazy jerk.
Either he's crazy or it was resentment.
I think I should go back to
the injured employee's home.
You said he couldn't
walk or speak properly.
The killer left the body
in the drain on purpose.
I think it has something
to do with that family.
Also, those white sneakers...
White sneakers?
I'm going to work.
What happened to these?
Water.
Why are you so thirsty these days?
I won't be back until morning.
Water.
- All of it. - What?
Slow down. Hold on.
You have wounds on your hands.
What happened?
Let's all die.
Honey.
What's with you?
What happened to your hands?
Let's all die.
Honey.
I'm going to work.
What?
Are you going to call that guy?
Honey.
You can speak...
You look comfortable as if you're at home.
You must have been here a lot.
You can go now.
We checked your dashcam and
found nothing suspicious.
Hey. Say bye at least.
Hey. What are you doing here?
Why are you back?
What is it?
Hey!
The body is wet again.
Hey. What are you doing?
Neither her husband nor
her daughter is here.
Her daughter?
I get it, so leave the scene. Right now.
- Get out. - Fine.
I get it, okay?
What's that?
I think the daughter is alive.
Someone's life is on the line.
We have to do something.
We need to make sure if
he is possessed first.
We shouldn't rush.
I think it's more dangerous for you.
You seem to be possessed already.
- Where is he? He's in there, right?
- Hold on.
He's going to perform an exorcism?
He's a taxi driver.
We're dealing with something too dangerous.
Are you possessed or something?
Where is your daughter right now?
Where is she? Tell me!