Hwa Pyung, come over here
and help the elders.
That woman is staring so frighteningly.
A psychic has been born in a
hereditary shaman family.
A strange man suddenly came to our village.
He said his name was...
Park Il Do?
Yes, he went mad and made a fuss.
He stabbed his own eye with a knife...
and ran into the East Sea.
He didn't die for days and
floated in the water...
staring at the village people.
Hwa Pyung!
My family died because of him!
It's a powerful demon.
We must kill him!
He hasn't been possessed.
If you have something to say,
come to the church or to my house.
It's over there.
I've become certain of my
belief for the first time.
Over there.
I'm from the police.
You'll be okay.
Hey, where is my mom?
No, Mom!
I heard you wandered
around, driving a taxi.
Yes. I was looking for someone.
He was moved to the drain
after being killed.
The drain is dry, but his body is wet.
Why would he leave his car here
and the body in the drain?
I have a strange ability.
I was sleeping last night,
and I suddenly saw the killer
leave the body in the drain.
Are you kidding me?
I suddenly see things.
Get your butt out of here. Now!
Okay.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Who is that?
Stop right there!
Stop!
Darn it.
I thought I'd never catch you.
Your daughter.
What did you do to her?
I don't know...
what...
She was lying down on the ground...
and I stabbed her with a knife.
Did you kill her?
Your wife, too?
Yes.
I killed that talkative old lady...
and that man too.
That young brat had soft skin.
The knife went inside her skin so easily.
She cried and begged for her life,
and I shut her mouth.
She suffocated...
and died.
Stop it.
It's over. Stop it.
Get up.
Since you confessed, I'll
take you to the station.
Get up!
What are you doing?
I said, get up!
My legs...
My...
- He can't walk. - What do you mean?
He can't walk right now.
I'll carry him to the car.
Hey. Wait!
Open this door!
You jerk! Open this door!
Hey, wait. You can't come in.
I told you not to bring
home spirits like this.
No, you can't. I told you to
get out right now, you jerk!
I found him. Sohn has come.
He's been possessed because of Park Il Do.
We have to perform exorcism.
No, wait. I said that you can't.
That Park Il Do or whatever.
It's a powerful demon.
We won't stand a chance against it.
My body already hurts.
- I can't do this. - What's wrong?
Never! Just go over my dead body.
- Move, I have to do it.
- Listen, Hwa Pyung.
I tried my best last time too.
I almost lost my life trying it!
What do we do then?
Only a sacred being can
perform something like this.
We don't have time. This man
almost killed himself earlier.
We have to perform exorcism!
He is driving me crazy.
He just doesn't listen.
Hey, I knew this would happen, so
I invited some powerful people.
Do we have to go to the shaman's house?
Yes, we must go.
If someone is possessed,
we sure have to go.
Let's see how good you powerful people are.
Don't be rude and call
these priests like that.
- I apologize. - I don't care who they are.
All they need to do is find Sohn.
I'm in a hurry, so let's do it.
What are those wounds on his face?
Did you do that?
No. A detective who goes crazy
when she sees criminals did it.
He seems unconscious.
Did you see his symptoms?
Yes, I saw everything.
He has been possessed.
You must see if he is really possessed.
He killed his own family.
He couldn't talk or walk properly,
but he ran away from me.
I told you he has been possessed.
Are you a shaman too?
I'm a taxi driver. Okay?
Then wait outside. You're interfering us.
I have much more experience
in things like this than you.
- Understood? - Although I'm inexperienced,
I know the procedure well.
We must check if he's
really possessed first...
and we must not hurry.
He might die if we don't hurry!
He has woken up.
Are you all right?
You smell...
very filthy, don't you?
Let go of me.
Stay still, you jerk.
Tie him up tight!
Will you be okay?
- We didn't receive permission.
- We have no choice.
- We have no time. - Let's begin.
I will perform this exorcism...
according to Article 1172
of the Catholic Rule...
- based on the procedures...
- Just get on with it!
Father, give me the power...
You two need to go out.
No, I have something to ask this guy.
You can't. You might be possessed too.
You should worry about yourself.
Isn't this your first exorcism?
You sound like you've
already been possessed.
What did you say? You jerk...
Hey, stop it. What's wrong with you?
It's important to perform
exorcism, so let's go out.
- Come on, let's go. - Darn it!
Let's go out.
Good luck, then.
I told you to hold your temper!
Let's begin.
Your Holy Spirit, Benedict.
Give us the strength.
Your Holy Spirit, Benedict
who has chased away demons.
Give us the strength.
Your Holy Spirit, Benedict.
Your Holy Spirit, Benedict
who has chased away demons.
No!
He who has abandoned idol worshiping...
He brought home his daughter.
He secretly peeked at his daughter.
And he felt aroused.
He who has abandoned idol worshiping...
I'll take care of you tonight.
But then, she was caught by her stepfather.
She was beaten...
and was abused.
When she was dying from cancer,
he went to see her at the hospital.
He was happy!
Wait a minute.
Were you there?
Am I right?
You were there.
This is where you were hiding.
It's you, isn't it?
- I knew it was you! - Don't look at him!
Go outside.
Get out.
Now!
Why did you come out? Is it over already?
He will do it on his own.
What?
Why is he doing something like that alone?
That startled me.
My goodness.
- Who is that?
- Darn it. She's already here.
What? Who is it?
Who is that?
- Hey. - Where is he?
Hold on. Listen to me first.
A ritual is being performed right now.
What?
Who are all these people? Is he inside?
Hey, wait. Wait a minute.
It may be hard to believe,
but that man has been possessed,
and needs exorcism...
- Goodness. - Wait, lady.
Wait!
What is that? Is she a policewoman?
Father.
It's all over.
What?
Hey.
I'm going to be back with a warrant.
I don't care whatever you'll bring.
He's definitely possessed.
You should rather be thankful to me.
You're crazy.
You said you had to eat.
Buy some food with this.
No.
My mom is going to scold me.
Wait. Hold on.
Be careful of his eyes.
Why?
- I think we failed. - What?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay. Let's take a walk.
I think I need to quit this soon.
What?
I told you.
If you exorcize for a long time,
your soul slowly gets eaten...
by them.
But you made it this time.
It was just a weak spirit.
There's something suspicious.
I think it's controlling them.
It's too powerful for us to deal with.
What?
That guy.
That taxi driver guy.
He provoked something very dangerous.
Mateo.
You shouldn't be involved.
Father.
What?
What is my step-father doing here?
Father!
I think he's actually just a sick person.
If not, he's such a good actor.
Hey, I saw you running here
and there, and jumping.
You even had a physical fight.
Water.
Seriously, are you kidding me?
Doesn't it smell somewhat fishy here?
It's getting worse.
Water.
Get him some water.
Okay.
- Hey, what are you doing? - Stop it.
- Stop it. - Relax.
- You could hurt yourself. Stop it.
- Stop it.
Stop it.
Stop.
Itchy.
It's been itchy since that day?
Since...
the day he came.
Since the day he came?
You understand him very well.
- Write it down. - Okay.
Who is he?
He is...
from the ocean.
We...
came from the ocean.
Park Il Do!
Stop him!
- Get out of the way! - What happened?
What happened?
- Call an ambulance! - Call an ambulance!
- Call an ambulance!
- Hey! Call an ambulance!
Yoon Hwa Pyung. Yoon Hwa Pyung!
How did you know that?
How did you know he would poke his eyes?
I told you.
I told you he's possessed.
I said I could see what
possessed people do.
Are you still saying that?
You're crazy.
It sounds crazy, right?
What can I do? That's what I see.
You want me to believe that?
Both the corpse from the
sewer and Mr. Kim's wife...
had sea water in them.
That's...
The police find it strange too.
That's what happen when you get
killed by a possessed person.
Everyone who was killed and
related to Park Il Do,
the powerful spirit,
was soaked in sea water.
And they kill themselves
by poking their eyes.
Look.
It suddenly started again four years ago.
All of them are cold cases.
It's killing more people these days.
Let me meet the culprit.
Are you going to do
something like exorcizing?
Yes, I need to kick it out.
Gosh, this is ridiculous.
Ma'am!
Hey, let's talk later.
His daughter is alive.
A fire accident from...
December 30, 2014 that killed a family.
Of course I remember that.
Since it was the end of the year,
there were many accidents,
but I still remember that accident vividly.
It was so odd.
Was it really a suicide?
That's how it was concluded.
There was no evidence
of break-in nor murder.
The corpses were greatly
damaged because of the fire.
Were there any other strange things?
Strange things?
Right.
The second son had a pierced
wound on his one eye.
On his one eye?
It seemed like he injured himself
with something like an awl.
There was a big wound on his one eye.
Everything was odd about that accident.
There was no reason for the
family to kill themselves.
I see. Thank you anyway.
I'm sorry.
Belly button? What does that mean?
I love you. Are you happy now? Okay.
I'm busy. Let's hang up. Bye.
You must've been nagged a lot.
My life is tough both at home and at work.
How is he?
Since I've become a detective,
I've dealt with murderers,
rapists, and gangsters.
But...
he's different.
When his one eye stops
rolling and stares at me,
it creeps me out.
Bong Sang.
Do you trust me?
What?
What is it? What now?
Your daughter is alive, isn't she?
You tied her and locked her up.
Where is she?
He's peeping us.
He reacts to us.
Even dogs and pigs can
feel when they're slashed.
What are you doing?
Aren't you excited as well?
Am I wrong?
That blood.
You like that, don't you?
Just tell me where your daughter is.
He's still looking for his daughter.
Later,
let's drain all the blood
out of the little girl...
and kill her slowly.
Why this family?
They're innocent.
Innocent?
It's what this man wanted.
He wanted them all dead.
It was unfair...
and frustrating!
If the client doesn't want to get involved,
who is going to take responsibility?
What about his hospital bills?
He'll be bedridden for
the rest of his life.
The three of us...
will starve to death.
Please help us, sir.
This man was...
in despair, right?
He was. He was in despair.
He wanted to kill his family...
and himself.
That's why you killed his wife?
One's...
dark side...
That's why...
he chose the man...
and we came.
How did this man meet Park Il Do?
Where is Park Il Do?
See?
We should tell him.
He'll die before he finds him.
He is a hunter and a predator.
This is his eye!
Hey.
Run away like last time.
Keep running.
Run away.
Park Il Do is in Priest
Choi's body, isn't he?
Priest Choi's little brother.
Little brother?
Yes, the priest's little brother.
He's around your age.
His family died because of you.
You made him an orphan.
What about him?
I should have killed the little brother,
but that female police officer interfered.
I told you not to skip private lessons.
Come here. It's all right.
Run!
I should have beaten him up...
to death.
The priest is...
on his way to...
his little brother!
You jerk.
He's not going to tell us
where his daughter is.
You said you saw something.
Do you have any idea?
It was an enclosed place.
I'm not sure if it's a
storage room or a basement.
If she’s confined there
too long, she might die.
We have to find her soon.
I'll bring exorcists.
Forget it.
I'll find some more information
about Kim Young Soo.
Hey. But what you said...
Forget it.
Hey. Have you contacted the priests?
Yes.
But there's a problem.
It was an accident.
No, it wasn't.
He was killed by Sohn. His exorcism failed.
I see.
It failed.
I should have realized earlier.
I was being hasty too.
By the way,
why are you here?
- That man... - I quit.
I can't do it anymore.
There are no other exorcist priests.
That man's daughter is still alive.
She's locked up somewhere.
We have to find her.
Ask the police.
Do you think they'll believe me?
He'll think I'm a lunatic.
The girl's life is on the line.
Both the man and the girl might die.
If you keep being so hasty,
you might really die.
Yes.
I admit that I was hasty.
It was an emergency.
But this is an emergency too.
A person's life is on the line.
We have to do something.
He is under complete control of the demon.
There's nothing we can do.
So you're just going to sit back?
You're just going to run away?
Are you really a priest?
Are you scared? Because
your mentor got killed?
Stop...
pretending you're saving
everyone by yourself.
You don't understand demons.
You've never even suffered because of them.
I've never suffered?
What do you know about me?
Don't pretend you're surprised.
You're running away like a coward.
Exorcist priest, my foot.
Gosh.
- My dear... - Gosh.
Why do you look so upset?
Like you stepped on poop.
How did it go?
That young priest...
isn't interested.
Can't you do it yourself?
Have I ever refused to help you?
This time, there's nothing I can do.
It's an extremely superior spirit.
It'd kill me.
You look so strong on the outside,
but you're just a coward.
Do you know any other exorcist priests?
Couldn't you work things
out with the young priest?
He's more famous than you think.
The late Priest Han was
sick for many years,
so the young priest had
to do most of the job.
He did?
Yes. He's incredible.
Right. I heard...
he is looking for someone
just like you are.
Whatever. I'm not interested. I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
You said you can't do it.
I'll have to talk to
other monks or priests.
It's an emergency.
All right. You don't have to yell at me.
Darn it.
One could really die.
What's the emergency?
It seems like his daughter is alive.
What makes you think so?
There's no blood stain on the knife.
He left his wife's corpse at the scene.
If he killed his daughter, her
corpse would have been there too.
He must have kept her alive
and locked her up somewhere.
He said himself that he killed
her during the interrogation.
He said he dumped her
body into the reservoir.
I think he wasn't sane when he said that.
I'll check out the places that
are related to the culprit.
- I need a search party... - No.
I already reported we will...
look for the body at the
reservoir with the police.
Didn't you hear I just said
I reported it already?
If we don't do anything about
it, she could actually die.
That's what you think.
Is there an evidence that she's locked up?
Is there?
- No. - See?
Go keep an eye on the culprit.
Don't let him hurt himself again.
You dishonored Violent Crimes Unit Two.
The superiors are really upset.
Why is she so stubborn?
No, it shouldn't have been this way.
He should've done it.
You...
You should have done it!
My goodness.
It can't be helped.
This is insane.
- You're here. - My goodness.
I have no idea what's going on.
What have you been doing
until it went this far?
Enough.
He doesn't even have family.
Mateo, it must be a lot of work for you.
By the way, what will
you do with his body...
after the funeral?
Aren't we burying it at the
parish natural burial?
No, we can't. It's a suicide.
The police said it was a suicide.
My goodness.
How could a priest commit a suicide?
This is totally insane.
He was too into those things.
I heard he was sick and
a little lunatic too.
Exorcist priest sounds cool,
but there are no demons these days.
He could have just counseled
mentally ill people.
- He didn't have to... - No.
He helped a lot of people.
What?
He actually helped people.
He didn't do it for nothing.
What are you saying?
He's been having a lonely fight.
Don't judge him because
you don't know anything.
How dare you!
Mateo, you're being rude.
He was a real priest unlike someone...
who collects donation and
gets food from the people.
How dare you...
You're just like him.
You're just as pathetic as him.
Just go.
Goodness.
We should talk later.
Where's your daughter?
She's alive, isn't she?
Where is she?
What?
It's dangerous.
His daughter will die soon.
You freak!
Calm down!
Get out.
Now, we're going to find
where his daughter is.
Come out!
Get him.
Are you okay?
Yukgwang, wake up.
Yukgwang.
Take him outside.
I'm going to take care of it from now on.
All right. But being
alone here is dangerous.
I said I'm going to take care of it.
- Let's get out of here. - Let's go out.
What is going on right now?
Well...
You said that you'd believe me.
So tell me what this is. Are you...
Is this something bad?
I'll take full responsibility.
I really have no idea what to say.
And who are those two?
It was inside the water.
It was really...
inside the water.
Those black eyes...
Hwa Pyung.
- I think I... - Okay.
I know, Yukgwang.
You did well. I have to go.
Where are you going?
Listen to me. It's really a powerful demon.
I told you that I didn't want to do it!
I told you I'm in a hurry.
Where are you going?
Yukgwang.
Don't let anybody in during the ritual.
Bong Sang, don't let anybody in.
- Hey. - Where are you going?
What are you looking for?
When Park Il Do possessed Kim Young Soo,
I'm certain he used something.
And that is?
We have to look for it now.
Look for it with your eyes.
Don't touch anything.
Hey!
In the name of the Father and Son,
and of the Holy Spirit, amen.
The Angel Saint Michel.
Protect us from the fight
between power and violence.
Protect us from the rulers
of this dark world...
and from the fights...
- between sinners. - I killed her.
I hit her with a car.
What did I say? I told
you I would kill her.
Please tie up the dragons and
snakes possessed by the demon...
with chains and send them...
What should I do with you?
Should I kill you like that man?
Should I kill you like his wife?
Please save the people from temptation.
Die!
I said, die!
Like that old priest!
Die!
Please send Satan and demons...
and chase them away from this world.
- This way. - What is going on right now?
Let's go have a talk.
Wait a minute. What is going
on in there right now?
It's nothing at all.
Just a religious event.
What else would a priest do? Don't mind it.
Have a seat.
Mr. Kim Young Soo.
Can you hear me?
My daughter...
Soo Jin.
Soo Jin...
Your daughter.
Where is your daughter right now?
My...
Soo Jin...
I told you not to touch anything.
Hey.
What are you doing?
You're ruining the crime scene.
What shall I do?
Shall I kill him?
Shall I?
Everyone who stays near him will die.
He is just like us.
Hey.
Are you okay?
I have to hurry.
You punk.
What are you doing?
Hold on.
Let me go.
Just a second.
I just did something weird, didn't I?
You jerk.
Are you possessed or something?
I was just reacting to the possessed man.
It happens from time to time.
That's why I can see murders.
I showed a strong reaction
because this is a murder scene.
Gosh.
I just saw Kim Young Soo and his daughter.
It's true. Please believe me.
Hold on.
- There. - What?
I see something.
I command you...
to leave this man's body right now.
Get out! He's already dead.
This guy is already...
Help me.
Who are you talking to?
Are you controlled by a
more powerful spirit?
Help me!
A superior sprit is controling you, right?
Tell me.
What do you see?
Please look inside the
range hood right now.
Gosh.
Tell me.
Where is it?
Tell me!
I command you...
to tell me the name of the superior spirit!
Please!
Tell me the name of the superior spirit!
I command you!
Everything is all right.
I hear some noise.
It's just a religious ritual.
You've never been to a church?
Why would they have a
religious ritual here?
What else could a priest do?
He hands out candies,
- cookies and all. - Move out of the way.
Hold on. You can't go in there.
Father! Move out of the way.
Open the door! Open the door!
Tell me his name!
Park...
What?
Park Il...
Do!
What's going on?
Park Il Do?
I command you...
to leave this man's body right now.
Help me.
I command you...
to leave...
this man's body right now.
In the Name of Father, the Son,
and the Holy Spirit, I command.
Get lost, evil spirit.
Go back to where you came from.
Our Lord is the one...
who has the most power.
In the name of the Father,
and of the Son,
and of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
Father.
What is this?
Please call Detective Kang Gil Young.
Kim Young Soo will tell her...
where his daughter is.
That way.
Down there!
Are you okay?
- Hurry up. - Hold on. It's okay.
It's okay.
It's all fine now.
Where is Park Il Do?
She was kidnapped and murdered.
I saw a dead woman in a trunk.
I clearly saw it.
There has been no such report.
It's just that the body
hasn't been found...
because the killer is carrying
it around in the trunk.
Are you sure you saw it?
Is there any evidence?
If the third woman turns
out to be the right one,
- the police will work on it.
- Forget it. I'll find her.
I saw the superior spirit. Park Il Do.
Who is this jerk? Park Il Do...
- Are you ready? - Everything is set up.
Then let's get started.
Money-stealing action drama.
"Player".
There are always unexpected situations.
Go get him!
Please find it.
We don't know what he
might be doing out there.
Let's start for real.
Be careful. I don't feel good about this.
Stop while I'm still patient.