The vegetables are not bad today.
This is an exciting time. In a moment,
Hong Kong separated from its fatherland.
A wanderer for half a century
has finally gone back to her
mother to her love and embrace.
The whole world is watching this.
Everyone is anticipating
the return of Hong Kong to
- the embrace of her motherland.
- Mom, I'm back.
Jiang Sheng, don't touch it. Put it back.
Mom, I want to eat the egg.
You can't.
Mom, let me have a small bite.
You can't. This is for your father.
Dad? Dad won't definitely
return for the new year.
I don't believe he will return.
Your father said that
he will be home today.
I don't believe that he will be back.
You are a liar.
Your father is a senior reporter. He's
busy with the affairs of the country.
He wouldn't have that much time
to keep us company. Eat this.
Jiang Sheng! Jiang Sheng!
I'm coming.
Quick, we already made an appointment.
Hurry up, Jiang Sheng.
Mom, I'm going to play
with Bei Xiao Wu first.
You are not going to eat?
- Is it fun?
- You are riding the horse.
Be careful. Dad is making a right turn.
- Right turn.
- Okay.
Uncle Bei, can you be my horse?
No. My father is my horse.
No one else can ride on him.
Who's your horse? You ride on me every day.
Let Jiang Sheng ride.
Get off.
- Okay, Dad.
- Come, Jiang Sheng.
Are you ready?
You are riding the horse.
We are knocking into them.
Is it fun?
- Yes.
- It's fun?
Doctor, did you see my family?
Did you see my family?
Doctor.
Nurse! Nurse!
Here, quick.
Nurse.
Nurse, did you see someone
by the name of Jiang Liang?
Over there. Go over there and check now.
Did you see someone by
the name of Jiang Liang?
We are busy. Check over there.
Look over there.
Doctor.
Did you see my family?
Gave my family a big painful blow.
I didn't expect that my
childhood would change.
Someone said that my father and a female reporter from
the provincial capital came her to conduct an interview.
At the same time, they had this kid.
Who's he? How is he related to my father?
My mother didn't say anything.
They simply walked in silence.
One, two, one.
One, two, one. One, two, one.
Mom.
Jiang Sheng, call him Older
Brother in the future.
Greet him.
I don't have an older brother.
He's your biological older brother in the
future. Address him as your Older Brother.
Older Brother.
Liang Sheng suddenly came into my world.
Older Brother, what's in your bag?
I couldn't and also didn't know how to ask
why this boy, Liang Sheng,
suddenly came to our home.
I could only determined
that he's my older brother.
As for me, I'm his younger sister.
Older Brother, are you crying?
Are you afraid of the dark?
If you are afraid, I'm not.
I will keep you company.
Come and eat. Sit over there.
Eat.
Enough.
Liang Sheng, take your younger
sister into the house now.
Return my man to me. That's right.
It's your family.
I'm not leaving. I'm very sad. I want to
settle score with his family. I want my man.
I will talk to them.
Where is Liang Sheng?
She's at home.
Take good care of her.
I'm going to get some water.
He's only interested in making quick bucks.
This is retribution.
How it would be? Do we still
need to talk about this?
You will definitely be the
manager in the future.
Congratulations, Uncle Bei.
You will be rich soon.
Jiang Liang Zi is really unlucky.
This is great. He's now crippled.
What are you doing? Why did you step on me?
Let me tell you. I heard
that woman is his lover.
What do you think is the relationship
between that kid and Jiang Liang Zi?
One, two. One, two.
Older Brother, let's play together.
Older Brother, what are you doing?
Are you going out?
Older Brother, where are you going?
I want to go home.
Mom said that this is your home.
Older Brother, what's in your bag?
Can you show me?
Older Brother, what is this?
This is a music score.
What's a music score?
It's for playing piano.
What's a piano?
A piano has lots of white
and black keys.
They produces sound when you press on them.
Older Brother, your shoes are really nice.
What are you doing?
I'm sleeping together with you.
- No need.
- When I'm afraid of the dark,
I would cover my head with the blanket
and I won't be afraid anymore.
I'm not afraid of the dark.
You were crying and you still said
that you aren't afraid of the dark.
Who's crying?
Weren't you crying just now?
Eat now.
Jiang Sheng, finish your food.
I'm going to the hospital.
Eat now.
Thank you, Older Brother.
That was the first time that I felt
that my older brother was really nice.
She's coming.
Jiang Sheng.
Look at who this is.
Jiang Sheng, why is he sticking to you?
He's my older brother. He's my
biological older brother. Greet him now.
Biological older brother?
Where did he appear from?
I have never seen that you have
a biological older brother.
I remember now.
My mom said that he could be your
father's illegitimate child.
Bei Xiao Wu, you are talking nonsense.
Did I say the wrong thing?
- You don't have the right to say this.
- Why did you hit me?
Bei Xiao Wu, bring it on.
Does it still hurt?
It doesn't. You won and Bei Xiao Wu lost.
How could he do that? Let's
look for his mother.
Let's go.
- Where's your mother?
- She's not here.
Who hit him? Did you hit him?
Go and hit him now.
Come out here. The both of you, come here.
Hit him now.
- What's wrong, Mother Bei?
- Look at my son.
Look at my son. That wild kid hit him.
What's going on? He hit him.
Jiang Sheng, did you hit him?
He will hit others in the future and even kill
others. He will also set fire. Isn't that so?
Why did you hit my son? Why are you crying?
He was beaten by him.
I told you to stay at home and you didn't.
- You insisted on wandering out there.
- What are you doing?
Do you want others to laugh at you?
You are really something.
Are you done yet? She's just a kid and
you used the feather duster to hit her.
Stop crying. Everything's fine.
Are you going home or not? Go home.
Do you want everyone in the village
to notice you? Are you happy now?
Bei Xiao Wu scolded Older Brother.
He said that he's a wild kid.
Sorry, it was my fault.
We went to elementary school later.
Liang Sheng! Jiang Sheng!
- What?
- Here.
This is for you.
You don't want this?
That's right. Give it to him.
Sit down. Let me take a look.
Why did you go to the kitchen?
I merely wanted to cook a bowl
of noodles for Older Brother.
Does it hurt?
Why are you so careless? Does it hurt?
From that day on,
Actually, I knew that
You didn't want me to cook.
You only knew how to cook noodles.
Thus, Liang Shen,
all those years, the noodles
that you cooked for me,
it was your way of doting on me.
Why aren't you eating?
You can have it.
Jiang Sheng, where are you taking me?
Don't open your eyes. You will know later.
Wow.
Older Brother, is this place pretty?
Yes.
We have flower shops there.
You still need to buy flowers? Look, there are so
many flowers here and you still need to buy them?
Also, do you know what I like most?
But when I grow up, I want to
go to the flower shop too.
Jiang Sheng, you have become much prettier.
Really?
Mom.
Mom, these are for you.
For me?
Thank you.
Jiang Sheng has grown up and matured.
Yes.
Older Brother.
The stars are falling from the sky.
These are not stars. They are fire flies.
Yes, they are fire flies. I
read about them in a book.
Older Brother, why do
fire flies emit lights?
Because...
I know. It's because its
mother is afraid that
it will lose his way. That's why, it
places a small light on its back.
Yes.
Older Brother, look.
We should release it.
Why? Can't it go home with us?
Perhaps, its mother is looking for it now.
Fire fly, go home.
Older Brother, I had a dream last night.
The fire fly found its mother.
Really?
Yes.
Jiang Sheng, you are really foolish.
The both of you...
Both of you were born from your mothers.
Understand?
Let's eat.
Where are you going?
Okay.
Go now.
Let's go. Where's your mother?
What is it?
What do you think?
What do you think it is?
Your family stole my stuff.
Who stole this?
Tell me who stole this? Hurry up.
- Bei Xiao Wu gave this to me.
- That's right.
What do you mean? You stole this and you
are still talking nonsense and lying?
What's wrong with you adults? He
stole my stuff and he still lied.
- What's wrong?
- Manage your children.
He stole our stuff and he still lied.
Did you steal this? Tell your mother.
Bei Xiao Wu gave this to Older Brother.
It's true.
How could it be like this? Let's go.
- It was a misunderstanding.
- What do you mean? Let's go.
Let's go home now.
Sorry.
What's going on?
Speak!
Bei Xiao Wu gave this to Older Brother.
Manage your daughter.
Here, for you.
Older Brother, do you want to eat this?
Older Brother, do you want to eat?
Just take a bite.
Just eat it. I'm not hungry.
- Really?
- Yes.
I dreamed that I was playing
the piano yesterday.
Older Brother, I want
to play the piano too.
I will teach you when you are older.
Don't separate them.
Furthermore, if you separate them,
they will feel the pain.
Really?
I have never seen it
You are not allowed to say
that about my father.