[Episode 12]
How about this one
Why don't you use their Soup
It tastes bad
It's full of monosodium gluatemate
And I like soup
How about I make you one?
You made this?
What if it doesn't taste good?
Let me show you a rope
As long as the ingredients are fresh enough
they taste grate
Even if you're not good at cooking
And I think cooking for others
is a great skill
You understand?
What's up
Please pay attention to your image, okay?
Is the soup ready?
Let me taste it, what did you put in the soup
Not good?
This soup is really good
What did you put in the soup
The magic?
I put some seafood in it
Haven't you ever had sefood soup?
Why I always thinking the kiss?
It's really delicious
I can be a cook
Are the other cooks dead?
First of all,the ingredients are good
The most importang is
that there's a lady-killer next to you
And exuding an enchanting breath
That's why the soup tastes good
Are the other lady-killers dead?
Me?
Yongze
Your friend Bai Yongze let me tell you
Not worth mentioning in your life
I'm working here
To comletely forget you
This is a nice place
Song Cha
Song Cha, Song Chacha
Lan Tian mistook you for Song Chacha?
Lan Tian, I got it
Unfortunately, you fired Chacha
An unfortunate woman
Jiang Shi?
Say what?
Are you going to land training?
What the hell are you talking about?
Why am I going to land training?
Why told me that?
Does he miss me?
What a pitiful man Yongze is!
They are going to land training
Why are we going there
We're going there
so you can see Lan Tian
Nah
While your fake boyfriend
is still here
Go ahead
Maybe it's the last day
What's your mean
What's the last day
Bai Yongze,Bai Yongze
What exactly do you mean?
Are you leaving tomorrow?
Tell me,are you?
Where are they
You're not gonna tell me?
Well, I'll go tomorrow
I found a sponsor
So, today is the last day
to be your fake boyfriend
Just go
Hey?
What's wrong?
My foot hurt,I canlt walk
Wake up, Lan Tian
That's waht you want
She has gone
That's what you want
Look out
Here we are
So beautiful
What's that
Fireflies
There are no fireflies in the city
Except here
When night falls, we can see it
I see it for the first time
Song Chacha
I have something for you
On Valentine's Day
I brought it for you
That
If you feel stressed
You can refuse
Very well
How do you know my size
I won't tell you
I'm going to show Lan Tian off
Well
I told you I'd take you home
I wasn't drunk today
And
The lamp's fixed
Really?
Who
Who fixed it?
I can't believe it
It's said that
the lamp
was fixed by a moron who wasn't afraid of death
And then the moron fell off
Thank you, my boyfriend
Love you, my girlfriend
Chacha
What happened
Lan Tian took me to dinner
I haven't visited in a long time
Have a cup of tea before you go
Thank you, aunt but it's getting late
Well
I two talk,I'm going in
Don't worry
I won't let Chacha go anywhere
Don't you worry
What' my mom's mean
Why she won't let me go anywhere
I told aunt let you spent more time with her
It's good for her health
There days
I'll help you, including money
I'll help you
Why do you suddenly care about me?
Don't get me wrong
Aunt didn't know we broke up
Just doing my job
Bye
Show me how you feel
Pity me?
What were you thinking about
Pack up
There're something I don't know if I should say
Break words
Nah
It's better not to say
Then don't
There, there, I'll say
Your new sponsor
is a movie company
which is connected with Li Bao
What's your mean
It's connected with Li Bao?
Li Bao,
She accept a strange movie
It's said that she was dressed outrageously  in the film
And the movie might be a porn
She accept it
is trying to get the company's boss
to fund you
What? Who said?
The company's boss?
No,no,no
It's Zhou..Zhou Xiaohu
That's enough
Sister, have a cup of tea
How about the thing I asked you to do
It's all done
I told Yongze's agent
My sister's life is ruined
Because of Bai Yongze
What did he say?
It's ruined
No,no,that's he said
not me
Don't be angry,sister
In my view,
Pu Jun is a loudmouth
who cannot be trusted with secret
He must have told him
See?I told you
Li Bao
Honey
Did you make some movie
on the condition
of sponsoring me?
Did you?
Honey,how
I don't need sponsorship
Refuse it now
It soesn't matter,honey
I can do anything for you
To support me
so you can take the request
whatever it is
And dressing outrageously and posing pretentiously?
What are you thinking of?
Whatever, after the video thing
I'm out of work
So, stop blaming yourself
You're the most important for me
Refuse it
Right now
Honey
Answer me
I'll do what you told me
But could you come see me tomorrow?
I feel low
I'm out of work and my ex-boyfriend threathned me
I'll call you
I told you
Bai Yongze really treasured me
You are good
Are you really gonna take it
For Bai Yongze?
Are you out of your mind?
I've always been pure, okay?
Even if they pay me hundreds of millions, I won't go
Hundreds of millions, for you?
You're not hot
I thought we found a dependency
So I spent all our money
What should we do now?
Are we going back home?
Fang Jingjing
God,Are you the Olympic champion FangJingjing?
Don't we talk for a second?
I'm busy,sorry
Bai Yongze,do you like swim?
If you don't
Jist chasing for what you like
Or
No amount of effort is worth anything
What's the worth?
Just stories imposed in me
By those who envy me
Whatever you did before
That's all for
living up to what dreams have to do
If you really love it,you won't fail it
So you must find the answer
She is his fan
What?
You mean,the daughter of Jinxing Group's chairman's
is Bai Yongze's fan?
Looks like I'm going to the Hainan myself
You take Lan Tian and Bai Yongze
And we have dinner together
It's not fair to Song Chacha
If she goes, I'll go
That what you say
Okay
Just do what you want
God,I Drove him away
What should I do
All I know is that you begged him,
and he's coming back
Why should I beg him?
That's your business
But
You two are good friend
Good friend
Don't think everything is
what it looks like
but
You two
are always together
What's wrong with you now?
Are you gus at loggerheads?
Are you?
How about me?
Are you kidding me?
Let me beg him?
That's what you should do
Look
I don't care whose fault it is
I won't beg him
But he is your teammate
I don't need a teammate like him
Sorry
As a coach
You have no emotion
for your teammates?
No
Not even
a sense of responsibility?
No,
So
Please get away from here mow
If you don't, I'll go
I never expect you to be like this
Please,help me
If Bai Yongze doesn't come back,
I'll die
I can give you money,I can give you whatever you want
Then, then I promise to date you,okay?
What's you mean?I beg him
And I have to date you
Are you a gift to me?What's your logic?
Anyway
You must help me to find him back
Please
No
Okay?
No, I told you
Chach Huang
Would you knock it off?
To avoid misunderstanding
I don't want to ruin my reputation
Please, just the last time
Please, okay?
He said we were no longer in touch
What's wrong with him
Coach
I am about to aboard the plane
Just come to the point
What's the matter if you miss your flight
What?
Well,let me say this
There's a madman,not Lan Tian
Is Lan Tian's sister,Lan Xin
She asked me
to get you back
Not Lan Tian, is Lan Xin
I'm not a person
who do anything for others
But, her words
Changed my mind
She asked me, as a coach
Do you have feelings
For your athletes?
It seems to question my attitude to my career
to my career
I recall the time when a was a player
I hoped I could have a coach
who concerned me
If I had
My life will be Better
Right?
So you means you want inject feelings into me
Not to you, but to me
I hope
I can put some emotion and enthusiasm
on my job
especially on someone like you
who is dawdling
having no idea of his limitations
but
gifted
I wanna try
So
Is that a declaration?
I'm not your type
You don't have to be a prick,okay?
Ahyway
I told you
Just believe your choice.
I hope you can
challege yourself
I really hope so
Nana,here you are at last
How is everything
You must be exhausted
It's okay
There is beautiful
It's a feast for the eyes
Really,you should often come here
Our service is always ready for you
Thank you
We'll have alot of cooperation in the future
I'll often came here
Great
Let's come in
Okay
Bowing
Uncle Lan
Where is Bai Yongze's trained swimming pool
Can I see him training?
Of course
I'll arrange it for you
Thank you uncle Lan
Lan Xin
Go see what Bai Yongze's doing
Now?
Of course,when do you want
Okay.
It's great that you can come back
You still care about me
If you're coming back
Why held the farewell party?
You've been gone a few times
THis isdn't a gotel
I'm sorry to bother you
Lan Tian,did you get him back?
No,I didn‘t
If he will go,I feel relieved
Why si?
You must for DongChacha
No,I'm for coach
Coach Huang? That's impossible
You must for Song Chacha
How great is the power of love
Shut up
Bai Yongze
Hello,Bai Yongze, I'm your big fan
I'm so excited to see you
Really really excited
This is
the daughter of Jinxing Group's chairman's, Jin Nana
Hello
Nana
I wanted to invite you to dinner
And it's been delayed this day
Yeah
Lan Tian
Are you an athlete now?
I thought you'd take over the uncle
I'm far away from
the professional athlete
And more far away from taking over my father
I'm fine now at the resort
Bai Yongze,what's your point as a friend
I think Lan Tian has great potential
Yeah,I think so
So you two,must do your best
I'll go first
Wait, Bai Yongze
How's your reaining environment?
Anything you need?
Nana, you don't have to worry
Our training conditions here
are first-rate
Just go
Ah, I've got it
Uh-huh?
Let me show you arope
As long as the ingredients are fresh enough
they taste grate
Even if you're not good at cooking
And I think cooking for others
is a cool skill
You understand?
My personal chef
Bai Yongze is so famous
Doesn't the swimming star
have a private chef?
He does,of courese,he does
We're recruiting for him
A celebrity chef will be here
in a few days
Nah,I already have a choice
What?To be your private chef?
So you're not going to go away?
Yes, for some personal reasons
So do you agree?
You told me
cooking for others
is a cool skill
Yeah
But to be a private chef
I never learned to cook
I can only eat and identify ingredients
But It's too difficult to cook
Where are you taking me?
You
Why,why are you here
She is the person I want to employ
She?
Are you kidding me ?
She doesn't even have a certificate
How can she cook for you
I only want to employ her
Uncle Lan
Maybe she's got something unique
Just do what he want
Thanks for your understand
Okay,okay
To make you do this
is to respect Miss Nana's opinion
Well
Well let's go
Why make me so embarrassed
I don't want you to run and hide
Just face it bravely
They didn't put you in trouble
It's yourself
You look down on yourself
You have to think zbout your future
Maybe one day you'll like cooking
and become a famous cooker
or a dietician
Right?
I've told you so much
I'm going to crying
Hey,I'm crying
Chacha
Uncle Lan
Do you know
the Bai Yongze's chef?
We've met several times
Do you know why I admire Bai Yongze?
Why
Because he's not as mean as I am
He has the courage I don't have
He is the only person
who makes me feel inferior
What
You employed Song Chacha?
Why didn't you  discussing it with me
before you making such a childish decision
I've made more childish decision
What decision
To make you my agent
You you
You know how it's to be your agent?
You fell in love with Song Chacha
I'm gonna help you hide it
And help you act
And worried about your trouble
I'm suffering a nervous breafdown
and can't sleep every night
Look, to cover the dark circles of the eyes
I wear sunglasses every day
I think
looks better with sunglasses
Nasty guy
Hello,sister
I'm not your sister
Oh sorry
All I saw was your hair
How did your shopping go?
Now that I agreed to be your private chef
I'm going to try
Be brave
Song Chacha
Are they sucked?
Is it for people?
Rea,really?
Oh,it's terrible
But I made it from recipe
Did I treat salt as sugar?
Did you treat Coke as soy sauce
I'm afraid so
You almost had me there
You told me you know the ingredients
What are these
I really know
I know
all the precious ingredients you tole me
Such bird's-nest
I used to do a lot of research on food
But I never actually cook it
So I think
Cooking is a cool thing
God
I was cheated
So you can just eat,right?
But I can't just give up
I'll work hard
I shouldn't encourage you
After the test
We dicided to
send two people to the competition
Bai Yongze and Lan Tian
Coach,I am not ready yet
You needn't reatd
You need experiments
According to the text
I don't think that's your best performance
Just enjoy the game,you know?
Can I not going?
Why
We had those plans
Who is within 1min and 55s,who is taking part
As for me
This is my chance to make a comeback
It's too important for me
At least
I have to compete in a race which is deserve
So, you think
It doesn't deserve you
in the race which Lan Tian  can take part in
I didn't mean it
So what's your mean
What the race
which is deserve
You did do well last time
But to be honest
You've been doing badly these days
You either lose your temper
or you fight
and affected your body
Okay
I'm gonna put you
in an international competition
and take part in 100m freestyle that is your best
How fast can you be?
So
the most important thing
is to test your training results
and
raise your self-confidence
Just keep in mind,stop showing off
Taking it step by step
Understand?
Okay
Let's training
It semms like
Lan Tian,you really like freestyle
Finally, do you want to overtake me?
Come on
Let's cheer for yours competition
Cheers
At this sxciting moment
I'm going to the bathroom
And
Don't speak tale of me
after I leave
Just leave
Go
Keep in mind
Chacha
I employed Chacha as a private chef
Please don't mention her
She is your girlfriend now
But she has nothing to do with me
No matter why you hired her
It don't matter to me
The better it is
From where I stand
I have to mention it
Before you care about it
Just pay mor attention to the competition
So are you
Challenging me?
If not
I won't swim
So
Let me ask you for one thing
To  you.Am I your friend
or your opponent?
Let me answer first
For me
You'll be my friend all the time
Even if
You're challenging me
Understand?