Why do you get in my way?
You are getting in my way!
What's going on here?
You want to tell me something?
OK, you first.
You don't want to say?
Fine
I will wait for your apology.
When you are available.
Are you out of your mind?
Who the hell are you? Apologize?
Is there any
appetitive food?
Yes, we do.
What?
As long as you move
your eyes away from Miss Song
I go and check for your request
Your family are so funny
Funny? That's rude.
I will finish her later.
I invited you because
you are Lan Tian's sister.
And I am the CEO of this resort.
What does it concern me?
Your fate is on my hands.
Hey, you owe me a supper
Cha Cha.
Lan Xin,
Aunt, do you remember me?
Yes, you are Lan Tian's sister.
So do you work here?
Everything goes well?
Just so so.
It's so good to have Cha
Cha here to help me.
You mean Cha Cha？
Your friend is still waiting.
I just forgot about him.
Aunt, why don't you drink some tea?
Take care.
I will visit you later.
That's very nice of you.
Let's go.
Cha Cha,
Why did she say you helped her a lot?
Eh~
I am just helping her manage this resort.
I gotta be paid for my work.
That's good.
You can often see Lan Tian here.
And your problem
can be resolved soon.
Then we have to stay here.
It's too hot.
Aren't you curious about what
Bai Yongze has been busy with?
This costs too much.
You may never have your loved one back.
Thanks for your news.
Walk yourself out, please.
Good night.
As long as I catch this big fish,
all news will come to me
will come to me itself
Got it.
Watch out!
Happy?
Happy! This is so beautiful, the beach.
True.
Thanks for understanding me!
I have to thank you
for believing me
and tellling me your story.
Angel, where r u?
You think I will tell you
I am on the beach
in bikini and under the sun bathing?
Bikini!
Running on the beach?
I just want everybody relaxed.
And change the environment for good moods
What do you say?
Come on
Beach beach
Go go
Let's go.
Angel, angel.
That sounds familiar.
Angel.
He is really here?
Perfect.
What a good shape of the figure!
I might leave first
Wait.
Let's hang out after training!
That is what I think.
Stay for my dream, please!
Stay
Just stay.
He is just
complicated.
Cha Cha
Song Cha cha
Where is she?
Where?
Why are you so mean?
So what?
You shouldn't just sneak away.
Sorry,
It was so embarassing to be there.
Why?
Because of your ex?
You said you
felt nothing about him.
Who is coming?
Making this so grand?
Yeah!
Who is coming?
It would be great
if I could stay here.
Hey, look
Isn't this Song Chacha?
You are working here?
It's more considerate than I imagine.
Caring about ex's life
is really
noble.
Song Chacha.
Hey, guys, this is Bai Yongze.
And these are my friends.
You do have so many this kind of friends.
Then who you think
is worth being Lan Tian's friend?
At least,
The one with a head.
Stop it, cheers.
The manager asked me to check here.
Yeah, I asked you here.
We were sort of
friends.
Song Chacha was a figure at that time.
And it's hard to ask her out.
We finally have this opportunity
to get together.
And you must
miss this kind of reunion, right?
Cha Cha,
come on, have a drink.
Thank you so much,
but I am different from
you these aristocrats.
I have no time for this.
You really think
you are still that precious princess?
Your time is of no value.
I pay you twice.
Is that enough?
Take it to cure your illness.
Take it to cure my illness?
Just drink.
Why did manager want me to send the phone?
Where the hell is he?
Give it to me.
Hey, what are you doing?
Stay away from me.
What Lan Tian can't give you, I can
Be my girlfriend, Cha Cha.
I dared not love you because
you were above my position.
But I can totally feed you now.
You are a pysco.
She can't be your girlfriend.
Because she is my girlfriend.
Let's go.
Things of one kind come together.!
You should know that
the Song Chacha you abandoned
was already picked by him.
Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
Lan Tian, that's enough
Get off me, I will kill you today.
You will kill him.
Phaethon
is the son of Apollo
One day
he wants to
show off to his friends.
So he asks his father
to let him ride on his chariot.
And Apollo agrees
and tell him not to ride too low
also not too high.
It must be in the middle.
But,
Phaethon doesn't listen to his father.
The chariot is out of traces
and burns all the crops.
The name of the chariot
is...
Shut the fuck up.
Desire.
Lan Tian, that's enough
I will kill you today.
You will kill him.
Desire is terrible.
So if you grow up
and have something you really want,
never out of track.
Do what you can, OK?
OK.
Do you understand?
Understood.
His head is bleeding
just truma.
It's not deadly.
But,
he has concussion.
He needs rest.
And his arm broken.
Are you out of your mind?
What that broken-down woman is?
She is nothing but a loser.
Watch your mouth!
He is not himself right now.
Let's just go. Don't get
ourselves in trouble.
Lan Tian!
Shut the fuck up
if you don't want trouble.
Even so,
It's not true about
what I said.
Are you innocent or stupid?
You really think I believe that?
Do you know about her?
No matter what,
i f she wants something,
even just a pencil,
she won't give it up.
Understand?
Have you heard of this song?
No.
It's a song of Plein soleil
It tells a story that
a guy who stole his
friend's money and woman
ended up declining.
It warns us not to steal
or you will get punished.
Right from start,
there is something that
you shouldn't lokk at,
or your life will be messed up.
Sorry, the call you dialed is not
answered for the time being,
please redial later.
Why didn;t he pick up?
Something happened?
Even it is,
I can't be that reckless to ask
what happened to Lan Tian.
Is he asleep?
I am sorry if
woke you up.
He can't be asleep
for what hppened today?
Why didn't you answer my phone?
Deliberately?
Is that too mean?
I'd like to ask you something.
What?
It's that..
You?
When are you here?
If I woke you up...
I
Come on in.
What do you want to say?
How is that friend?
Is he awake?
Why do you care about him
after what that asshole did to you?
Are you that serious?
Is Lan Tian OK?
He is fine.
Don't be so worried.
Wonderful!
Wonderful? Who do you mean?
That friend? Or Lan Tian?
Why are you so mad about me?
Why not?
You must have done somthing and le that
guy take advantage of you.
I wonder how much
you can take.
Some people just like to
differentiate others.
They will look down on those
who is worse.
And I am a woman.
So I should be to blame
for everything.
Yeas, you are right.
And why do you care if I am easily
taken advantage of?
You are damn right
Because this has nothing to do with me,
then,
don't get involved in my life.
And don't you show up in front of my face.
I am begging you to
leave and disappear from now on.
Right now.
Lan Tian, let her go, that's not love.
It's not true about
what I said.
Are you innocent or stupid?
You really think I believe that?
Do you know about her?
No matter what,
i f she wants something,
even just a pencil,
she won't give it up.
You are damn right
Because this has nothing to do with me,
then,
Don't you show up in front of my face.
I am begging you to
leave and disappear from now on.
Right now.
You are way too much.
I got fired?
There must be a mistake.
So what is the reason that
you wane me to leave so sonn?
宋茶茶小姐 你好像忘了
You job is to clean the room.
Not guest himself.
What do you mean?
Seriously? I tell you why.
A guest witnessed
you, Miss Song,
walked into
Bai Yongze's room.
I did that because of
something.
I am innocent.
But you were wearing uniforms,
and you were a server of us.
Do what you should do.
Am I right?
Song Chacha.
You want a reason?
Because every stuff of our resort
of our resort
feels ashamed.
I didn't do anything that I am ashamed of.
I won't leave for this
ridiculous reason.
I won't accept it.
I will report in
no matter what the results are.
It's your freedom to report in
But if you do that with that
ridiculous reason.
I will sue you for defamation.
I believe you know that clealy.
Truth is truth.
We are not your
puppets.
Where does your justice come from?
You have balls ha?
Just leave.
Lan Tian is not enough for you
and you went to seduce Yong Ze?
Just say it
taht you are jealous.
Are you shy?
Let go of me. Let go.
Why did you do that?
What if you get excluded
because of me?
If I were in this situation,
I might just leave it. But
you are my only friend,
what else can I do?
And the most important,
you looked so cool.
Especially when you said
'We are not your peppets'
If he fires me
because of this,
he will do that to other people.
I really wanted to kich the door and
walked out of that door.
But I have no luck.
God knows how I have
gone throught all this.
Why do we have to compete?
You can do your conversion fluently
can't you?
That's why we have two teams.
Right?
Just take it as a fun before simming meet.
OK, Lan Tian?
As long as I am not in your team.
Of course
I am with my Yong Ze.
I dare you.
I will not be in your team.
Neither am I
We are a team? We are a team?
I really don't want to leave this behind.
Lan Tian, on your knees, apologize.
What if I can't.
If you know
who your father is working with,
would you still say that?
You did this to me,
and I almost have concussion.
What would he think
if he knows?
It doesn't matter!
So it is with Song Chacha?
Itdoesn't matter if I play with her?
Why is it cncerned with her?
We are already here.
Why do you bully her?
Shame on you.
Shit.
Do you know who I am?
Bluffing?
I am telling you to
apologize for Lan Tian.
Now!
I will do that.
It's all because of me.
Is that what you want?
Don't do that!
Behave yourself, you brat
Stop, stop.
Lan Tian.
I can kneel before you.
You can
just beat it back.
Come on.
Stop when you want to!
You think I won't?
You asshole!
Stop Lan Tian!
I told you to stop.
Carefull, OK?
Sorry, sorry
You don't want to go tohospital?
Take a day off, it doesn't matter
It's no big deal.
You should just rest.
He just walked away?
Cold-blood guy.
Anyway, I am here
taking care of you with my heart.
What about your training?
Skip it!
What a great opportunity
to stay with my idol.
Go training
Now!
OK, OK
I will be back when I am finished.
What else do you need?
Anything except you.
OK
Get out.
Hey, what are you doing?
Get off me.
Why did you cry?
Who do you want to go crazy?
I feel comfortable to see you.
Just go.
I am far from comfortable.
I will figure it out
if it is money.
Who will work for money
in front of her boyfriend?
Then why are you doing this?
I want you to see me like this
and I want you to feel guilty
for the rest of your life.
Even you don't love me,
at least I want you to fell guilty.
That's fair
But I don't want this
anymore.
Because none of this works.
So I just want to leave.
First Zhao Yan didn't want me to go.
Then the rumors.
They force me to stay.
And...
Don't say a word.
The test is coming soon?
Fight?
What were you doing when the fighr started?
Where is your team spirit?
Stop it or call the police!
Sir, that's between privileged children
We just...
You don't care about their resentment!
Why did you take their drinks?
Lan Tian, listen up!
Even this is your resort.
I want you to remember that
it's not allowed any personal issues
in my team?
Do you understand?
I am sorry, sir
And you
It's all done
no matter how hard you practice
You get injured before the meet?
It's all gone.
Yes, sir.
Next time? None of you will
take part in contests.
Yes, sir.
Go on your training.
Song Chacah, I am afraid.
I am afraid 'Bai Yongze '
comes out of your mouth.
Lan Tian, what are you doing?
You are shaking?
Concentrate, please!
What's wrogn with?
You were doing great.
Why is this?
Put it on!
Hello?
Can you make porridge
with sliced thin pork?
Porridge with sliced thin pork?
What do you want?
Yong Ze isnot feeling well.
I want to make him one.
I am excellent at that.
See you in an hour.
Deal.
What a long day!
Can you make porridge
with sliced thin pork?
No, but I read about it in abok, why?
Hey, where are we going?
Can we use this kitchen?
I just told
the aunt.
Alright.
But why are we making
that?
For Yong Ze!
It's said that he doesn't feel dood.
It's my chance to
show him off
But how is that making?
Eh~ I will help you do that.
But there are no preserved eggs,
let's make porridge with abalone
Abalone is full of vitamins and minerals
and helps improve immunity.
The shell is so hard.
We need to remove the shell.
Cooking is so terrible!
Almost done.
What's wrong with you?
I seem to eat too much.
Oh! I need to go to the infirmary.
Give that to Jiang Shi when he comes.
Where is my angel?
She's sick and in infirmary.
Infirmary?
My angel!
Why did run?
Did you come here for porridge?
Do you know who leaked the video?
No, not intersted.
I did.
You know why?
I can sacrifice everything for you
even my reputation.
Don' you feel a thing?