Dad
I need to go to the loo.
How is it going?
Today
I just want to tell you about Bai Yongze
According to the files you showed me,
he has sports anxiety symptom.
Which is somatic anxiety
Somatic anxiety? Is that serious?
Find why?
And he will be fine with
some scientific training
But we can't leave me like this.
This has to be you, to assisst him
Forget it, it doesn't matter.
He left anyway.
Just let it go.
What?
Check your time!
It's about time.
Why is he not out yet?
I am sorry, dad.
I can't just leave Hainan like this.
I need more time!
Is it Yong Ze? What idid he say?
Let's go.
Just us?
What about Yong Ze?
Yong Ze
You scared me!
Why are you still here?
Watching you. Everywhere.
Watching you.
Who told you to do tha?
Who? Your parents!
You are not having constipation?
No wonder it takes you so song!
I don't see other problems.
Maybe is's just mental problem.
Mental?
Maybe you got
some hit recently
or in your childhood.
To be honest, you went through something,
which cause your heart problem.
No, I didn't.
What did doctor say?
Constipation? Is that serious?
No? So what's the problem?
Mental problem.
If I were you,
your mom pushed you so hard,
I couldn't get it out either.
Does it really have something with
sports anxiety?
What?
But,
How can I get back to the club?
What the hell are you doing?
I tell you what,
he didn't go because of constipation.
Shut up!
Anyway, that's it.
You are going for training?
It's been a long time
since we last competed.
So, interested?
Compete what?
100m Free Style.
Good.
You are not in the game.
What are you thinking?
Can you tell me about it?
What is this?
My gratitude
Of what?
Frankly,
I really don't know our deal
is so important to you.
You surprised me.
Wait, you better be clear
about what you said.
You can get Bai Yongze back
within one day!
Impressed!
I didn't do that.
Don't explain!
I know it clearly!
Forget it, thanks!
Hope you enjoy the present!
Do your best, Song Chacha!
Left without a goodbye.
That's too much.
So... sorry, I thought you left.
I don't you are sleeping with a woman.
Woman?
Hey!
Why are sleeping in my bed?
Your mother told me to
watch you.
What the hell? You really...
Song Chacha. Song Chacha.
It's a mistake.
That was a mistake. There was no woman.
He is my agent.
What's going on with them?
I thought you were gone.
He didn't catch the plane
because of constipation.
Enough, shut up.
It's not because of...
You stop it!
You were sent to the hospital
because you fainted.
You are dead, fucker.
Hey, what are you doing?
You bully me every time!
Get off me!
Let's talk!
I believe we have empathy under water.
But I recently found we got
seperated by something
Something that I can't see through.
Why?
Nothing! You think too much.
I am goona ask you one last time.
Do you have something hiding from me?
No!
How is that possible?
Did you say some bullshit
uneder the water?
I want to talk to you.
Please think before you say something.
You know what you are talking about?
All I know is that you not yourself.
There must be something wrong!
That's a lie.
You can't fool me!
I told you I don't want anyone to
know my problem.
Fine. Your secret is safe with me.
But I have a request.
One more.
This your seventh one.
Why can't I get drunk?
Be my boyfriend.
Just pretend to be.
I want you to tell him
that we are in a romantic relationship.
You are really insane!
What's wrong?
It's still daytime, and you are drunk.
What's wrong with you?
Lan Tian.
Did you ask what
what got us seperated
seperated by?
I am telling you.
I like Song Chacha.
And we are in a relationship right now?
What? You are pretending to be in
a relationship with Bai Yongze?
Just like you said. I am
trying to get him back.
I wonder if it's possible?
But if I got Lan Tian back,
I would fire the manager first.
And put you on that position.
I think you are a clumsy bear.
Didn't think you are a fox.
But,
you can't let anyone know this.
Especially Jiang Shi.
We are not close!
Why would I tell that?
As long as he is back,
we can go back like before.
It should be like that.
Did you tell him?
What did he say?
He wanted us to be good.
That's it?
He is not angry?
Not at all.
So what did he look like
when he said 'I want you to be good'
Nothing.
He must be angry inside.
He is coming！He is coming！
Oh~
There is something in my eye.
Can you help me?
Hey hey hey,
Did he look angry?
No.
You miss me so much.
Do you have to eat with me?
This is...
Are they together.
You don't know?
They are so sweet now!
Just like us.
I don't wanna hit you with my spoon.
Yong Ze.
Just a minute.
Yes, dad.
Blind date?
Got it.
You dad ask you to go for a blind date?
When?
Now!
Bullshit
This is just my delusion.
He didn't take me seriously.
I cry a hundred times
just for him comforting me once.
I walk you home.
No.
How can you go home like this?
I am telling you
that I have not been
drunk since I was born.
I am not.
I am warning you
not to follow me.
Or I'll sue you for abducting.
Song Chacha, is that really hurt?
Why do you have to turn a holiday
into a group outing?
Right!
But why do you look so tired?
Is is because Lan Tian
went for a blid date.
I am not sure.
I feel so gutless.
I fucked my life
up.
So I plan to get rid of it
and go home with my mom.
What do you think?
Where is Zhao Yan?
She just ran up there.
Up? Thanks.
Zhao Yan, Zhao Yan
Zhao Yan.
Where are you?
Just follow up.
Where is Cha Cha?
She just went uo there!
Up? Such a troubling girl.
Zhao Yan.
What should I do?
What happened my angel?
Don't cry. Don't cry.
What happened?
Cha Cha is missing.
I thought she is back.
And her phone is powered off.
What should I do? She must
get lost in the woods.
How was she lost?
What are you doing?
Yong Ze, Cha Cha is lost in the woods.
What?
Yong Ze! Get up first!
Jiang Shi?
Lan Tian, I need your car now.
What are you doing with my car?
Song Chacha is lost in the woods.
Lan Tian.
I am sorry. I am sorry. I am sorry.
I am sorry.
I am sorry, mom.
I shouldn't have left my brother alone.
I am sorry, mom. I am sorry
Cha Cha, don't be scared!
I know you must be scared.
Just wait there.
Cha Cha where the hell are you?
Just wait for me. I am almost there.
I will find you.
Cha Cha. Song Chacha, Where are you?
Cha Cha
Song Chacha
Cha Cha, answer me!
Cha Cha
I am sorry, mom.
I shouldn't have left my brother alone.
I am sorry, mom. I should
have protected my brother.
I am sorry, mom.
Cha Cha
Where are you?
I am sorry, mom.
Song Chacha
Cha Cha
Just answer me.
Are you OK?
Are you really OK?
I am sorry.
I am sorry, mom. I am sorry, mom.
Mom
Sweetheart. I am sorry.
I didn't know you were in there.
I am sorry.
Let's go. It's OK!
Careful!
Watch it.
Don't go. Don't leave me alone!
You have been troubling
since you were a child.
What should I do with you now?
You goota take care of yourself. Got it?
Is Cha Cha OK?
Cha Cha. It's all my fault.
You wouldn't be lost if it weren't for me.
I am so sorry.
Enough, angel. Stop crying.
You didn't do it on purpose
And she is back now.
Bulb, are you Ok?
Lan Tian, are you ready on board?
What's up?
Cha Cha got lost and fainted.
She is in hospital now.
Are you listening to me?
I am telling you I am leaving.
Wait. Stop by my place.
What?
Just do it for me. Stay and watch her.
OK? I gotta go.
Only in this way
does she see hope
when she wakes up.
Even it's so slight.
Bai Yongze, don't you understand?
It's not good even we
just ignore this
awkward relationship.
Hey, angel, all you need is
to rest at home.
Come on, let me walk you home!
Why are you so sweet?
Not used to it.
Not used to it?
I seem to be like this every day
Someone just don't see it.
She just can't see it.
You are saying me?
I am just comlaining!
If you are not happy,
just hit me.
And I want it.
Come on.
So I am gonna do it.
Jiang Shi.
Oh, shit!
I almost had a heart attck.
Left.
Heart attack? You are so caculated!
Angel! Angel!
Almost forgot.
Cha Cha.
You are so
far away now.
No more waiting. Leaving.
Asshole, why don't you wait
until morning?
Cha Cha.
I really want Lan Tian to
be the first one to see
when you wake up.
Cha Cha. What's wrong with you?
Anybody here?
No one is here?
Cha Cha.
Can I help you?
Please check her.
She seems to have a fever.
We will check her now.
But, sir you...
I am OK.
I will get doctor right now!
Alright.
Cha Cha. Cha Cha. Cha Cha.
I am here. It's gonna be Ok.
Cha Cha. Lan Tian...
Don't hurry. Let's ask where she is now!
Where?
This way.
She is ok. She is ok.
Cha Cha. Cha Cha. Cha Cha.
You OK?
Mom.
It's mom. It's mom. Sweetheart
You feel better?
How do you know ...?
Lan Tian told me last night.
He said that you fainted.
He sent you to hospital.
But it was too late.
He told us to come in the morning
and visit you.
So... I am OK, mom.
Mom, don't worry about me.
I know it, he was here all night.
And I am not worried.
Mam, don't worry.
I think Cha Cha is fine now, isn't?
I feel I can run right now.
You awake? Do you feel better?
You know what?
Something maybe went wrong last night
if it weren't for your boyfriend.
What?
You had a serious fever.
Thanks to your boyfriend.
Cha Cha. Cha Cha. Cha Cha.
Lan Tian. Lan Tian.
We didn't what to do,
thanks to Lan Tian.
What the are are you doing?
This is so important. And you were absent.
I am sorry.
That doesn't help.
You know this Gold Star Enterprise
is larger than ours?
I wish to unite through marriage
We seem not to have that luck.
I don't care what methods you use,
make that luck.
You heard me?
What's wrong with you?
Not talking?
Is it
is it because of Song Chacha?
No.
You know what it costs you
if you break our deal, don't you?
I hope there is no next time.
If things go south,
I have warned you.
You had fight?
Look at your face!
Lan Tian? Is it you?
You were with him, right?
What are you talking about?
Look at hsi face,
he said he got drunk and had a fight.
That is worring.
It will influence his training.
Is there a drug store?
Is is serious?
I don't know.
I am so angry to see his face.
I really need some herbal tea.
I told you to leave me.
Why do you get back so fast?
Don't you go to breakfast?
What's wrong with your face?
You here!
What about hospital?
I didn't make it.
I don't care if you got drunk
or got into a fight with sommone.
You should go to check her.
I know what I am doing.
What do you know? Ha~
You said you like her, right?
You are her boyfriend.
You just can't let her go, can you?
You didn't went to that blind date
when you heard abou her.
I am right?
I will step away if that's true.
You are giving your love to me?
But, I don't want it at all.
I am not moved.
There is no such thing
in my life.
Love, contest?
There is schu thing.
Win or lose. Bai Yongze.
Do you give up because
you are afraid to lose?
No
So stop talking about that bullshit.
About that bullshit.
And,
Song Chacha
she is afraid of darkness.
She can't sleep with lights out.
I cancelled my blind date
for that.