He left his phone here
I'd nearly foget. I haven't
found my phone yet
Lan Tian, is that the surprise?
Lan Tian? Surprise?
So, do you want to use another
phone to blackmail again?
Lan Tian, are you with him?
You always said Lan Tian, Lan Tian
Do you know him?
I am asking if that
scoundrel's with you now
That scoundrel?
What's your name
Song Chacha
Lan Tian, do you know Song Chacha
Promise me, whatever happens
You definitely marry me
You're not running over
at the wedding, are you?
Why didn't you tell me sooner
You can bring it next time
Where is Lan Tian
Why are you always looking for Lan Tian
Lan Tian is the one who's gonna marry me
But he didn't appear
The guy you're talking about is a jerk
But the Lan Tian I know said
He didn’t know Song Chacha
Really?
What am I lying to you for?
He doesn’t know you
Okay, I got the phone
Goodbey, then, and thanks.
I'm leaving
I'm really leaving
What kind of person can that Lan Tian
make you so sad
You just go
I know my friend Lan Tian
He wouldn't do anything like this
And, I never heard
that he had a fiancee
Enough
You go
Who’s the runaway man?
Why the sudden heart pains?
Maybe I am under too much stress
Lan Tian
Why are you hanging around in the street
Didn't you have to wait
for me to come back?
Suddenly wanted to go out for a walk
Did you get your phone back?
Yeah, but... That girl looks pathetic
As if she's going to crumble
I even wanted to help
So that's not your fiancée, right?
Your expression was difficult to read
And where are we heading for?
Just go, and dress yourself up
What do we come here for
Yu Ge comes and he desires to see you
You have so much friends
And you know the Olympic champion too.
I'm popular
Cheers
How are you, Bai Yongze
A lot of things have happened recently
have you adjusted to a good condition?
Not bad
Look Yu Ge
Lan Tian is going to
re-enter the swimming arena
Really?
Uhm, yeah
Being rich is great
Don't have to worry too much
Not necessarily
What I really want, I can't get it.
Yu Ge, which one of us you
think is more appropriate
to be your successor
It's unclear
But, no matter who he is
not only he has a target
but also makes a plan
So, as of tomorrow
Pack your luggage, let's leave Beijing
Where are we going?
Hainan
Hainan!
Finally!
Just for training
what a pity for this place
Then find something else to do
I won't stop you
Do you want to set me trapped
and beat me
in this way?
Although things have been bad lately,
it is not enough to bring me down
True talents still manage to stand out
You're so confident
Welcome to home
Nice service attitude
Is this resort yours?
I Inherited from my grandfather
I put it in custody to my lawyer
when i was in America
Now I'm back
It's mine
If I have a girlfriend later
You know
Arrange deluxe suits for me
Girlfriend?
Li Bao?
No
By the way
have you arranged for the coach?
Already
Who's he
Alexander
Ivanovsky
Who's he!
Look at your face
Is he better known than them?
I can't wait to see him
Of course!
Why didn't you tell me?
Who the hell is he!
It's really gorgeous
So beautiful!
Sir
Are we really gonna train here?
You're annoying
You've asked it a thousand times
Bravo, bravo!
After such a long distance
and ended up in my hometown
If i had known it,
I would not have paid
three months of tuition
And be bewildered by Goggles Man equipment
Do you just regard Goggles Man equipment
as an equipment?
It's a belief, you know?
It inspires you to work hard for your goal
like Goggles Man
You know?
Stop talking. Or I'll punish you
Okay, okay
I got a great bargain
Bai Yongze!
It's really Bai Yongze!
I told you
There must be important person
Let me introduce
This is Coach Huang Donglei
Who?
Yeah
I am the Huang Donglei who was suspected of
taking medicine and withdraw from swimming
Where are you going
I know I'm down
But I won't practice with people like this
Hey, who are you talking about?
You think you're good?
But I agree
American players are really
good at making nicknames
Sorry, although we have a good relationship
I absolutely don't accept this man
Yeah
I am the Huang Donglei who was suspected of
taking medicine and withdraw from swimming
Although we have a good relationship
I absolutely don't accept this man
Sorry Lan Tian,
I'm so sorry
Is he the only one with
special personality?
I have my personality
If I ever wanted to
please the rich
I would had three swimming pools
About Bai Yongze
I'll try to persuade him
Please don't. If he stays
There will be more troubles
And you must keep that in mind
That you are going to participate
in the standard match
Don't drag others down
But I wanna try again
Please give me some more time
I will call Bai Yongze back
and train with you
Do you think it works?
I don't believe it
This is life
About Bai Yongze, I wanna try again
Please give me more time
I'll call Bai Yongze back
and train with you
Don't go
Don't go. Lan Tian
Pleasa don't go!
How could a man who deliberately failed
to make an appointment contact me
Chacha! Open the door!
Okay! Wait a minute
Chacha! Open the door
You have delayed your rent for a long time
When can you pay it
I'm not a philanthropist
Hum, I'm sorry
After the pay check,
I'll pay it immediately
Okay, enough. I won't let you explain
Within the week
Or I'll get you out of here in my way
Make a bet?
Or
You can compete with Yu Ge
You win, you're in charge
Since you despise Coach Huang
Then you beat me first
Oh, no.
Good job!
YE
Well, what do you say I beat you
Yu Ge, I didn't pay much attention
Just watch you swim
You mean
If you play as usual, you'll win
Are you seriously
to invite me to the culb?
We just bickers a bit
Anyway
Admit the defeat for bet
You have to keep your promise
I know Coach Huang
Yongze, you are a man who won't give in
So is Coach Huang
I believe you two must
have something in common
Think about it
Yongze, you are a man who won't give in
So is Coach Huang
I believe you two must
have something in common
Think about it
This is Bai Yongze
Have you found your phone?
It's been a few days
I found it, so stop thinking about it
We must meet
And I'll check it
Don't you believe me?
How can I rest assured
There are my photos in your phone
And our photos
And text messages and stuff
Okay, I'll delete them now
No, I delete them myself
Let's meet in a secluded place
I've had just about enough
of those annoying matters
Why hasn't he arrived yet
Reporter Xu pestered me every day
I'm getting nervous
You know I'm very sensitive
Even though you're unhappy
Please understand
All deleted?
Then I'm leaving
A man's belt in the back seat
It'll be better to put it away
I don't mind it
But what about the other men?
That would ruin the atmosphere
I'm ready to go
I'm waning you
No one ever stood me up
You know what you must do
Now go!
Why are men called Lan
Tian so unreasonable?
Break the date with girlfriend
And threaten others not to break the date
Hello?
Oops, my stomach hurts
I'm afraid I can't go
Go for yourself today
Okay
It's too humiliating to come back like this
How can I go back right away?
I should carry a mighty bearing
and has the air of a king.
Cool!
Of course
Why are you still here
I told you
No one knows you better than I do
Humiliation is temporary
Swimming is the most important thing
Come on. Swimming is the
most important thing
Wait
Who said that
Lan Tian
Don't thank me so much
I came here just for the
development of swimming
and other teammates
Shut op
Do some warming up exercise first
50m freestyle test
What?
We haven't warmed up yet
Such an unprofessional coach
50m freestyle test. On your marks!
Who taught you to swim like this
Today's interim test, Guan
Jie is the first place
Well, I got to the end first
You're really the fastest in the water
But quality is more important
than speed in training
What a messy theory
I've seen the video of your game in the USA
Your paddles and turns can be better
But you're too pround
You didn't do it
Your final result is 0.5
seconds behind the preiminary
Such a champion makes no sense
The real victory is defeating yourself
Who are you to say it doesn't make sense?
No one's swimming before they warm up
This is unprofessional
Swimming takes exlposive
force and endurance
My way of training is
I'm ordering you into the pool
And you will be into the pool
I'm in charge here
Today
The training proogram
is on the blackboard
Practice the basic movements
No
That's for beginners
set
Look
From now on
A man disobeys orders
Everyone will be punished together
So
Everybody
Go to the Ocean supermarket
Bring two bottles back
of four liters of mineral water each
In 60 minutes
How could that be
40 minutes
Sir
Stop talking, okay?
It's usually 90 minutes
Go
I'm coming
The rent on these small
houses is really expansive
How can I pay for them
The landlord is about to get rid of me
What should I do
Hello
Is that Chacha?
I'm Lan Xin, Lan Tian's sister
Sister Lan Xln
So much has happened over the years
Unfortunately, I'm abroad
My dad died
The company closed down, too
My mom lost her memory
because of stress
She still thinks,
My dad is abroad on business
You must have a hard time
Just feel desperate
And I lost contact with Lan Tian
Lan Tlan even cut off the contact with you
Maybe
When his mom died
He's in a bad mood, too
So I'm trying too understand him
Because I know how painful
it is to lose the loved one
I thought he'd be back
after he was not sad
and contact with me
But he didn't
and I was informed of the
wedding by Uncle Lan
How do I understand these actions?
W....Wedding?
Yeah
But on the wedding day, I was reneged.
Don't you know?
You okay?
Your legs are still shaking
That's my habit.
Waiter! Two beers
One more!
My God
Brother Yongze
For a new start!
For the first day!
Cheers!
Lan Tian's in Hainan
Go find him
Hainan
The unlucky man said Lan
Tian is also in Hainan
Is it really the same person?
Maybe he's having a problem
Why don't you ask him face to face?
Why Hainan!
Are you too dependent on my shoulders
when you walk?
What about you
Yours arms around my waist are too tight
when you walk
The revolutionary friendship!
So enviable
Okay!
From now on
We have to prepare
for the team's first competency test
You're gonna try
to break through your weakness
This is our team's first test
The best result is
On behalf of our team
to participate in the national
standards competition
But
We shuould first perfrom our small targets
What
I won't
My level is higher than the standard, okay?
I know
You did well abroad
and took part in a lot of competitions
But you're back now
And come to me
You have to take part in the standard race
Look
There are no Dongfang Feiyue here
You have to do it step by step
and make a fresh start
You know?
Are you kidding me?
My freestyle is the
Fine, we race freestyle
200m
I'm not demanding
Just withthin a minute
and fifty-five seconds
You can compete on behalf of the team
But...
Last year's line is 1 "53"
I know
It's clear that
freestyle plays an important role
in swimming
whether a team is good or not
Depends on freestyle
Our list of for candidates is
Bai Yongze
Lan Tian
Jiang Shi
Guan Jie
Of course
Other players
If you take less than 1minute and55secon
The tournament is open to you
There's no need to compare
The winer must be Yongze
Of course
Let's begin
Today, we train with this
You
I don't need it
You go and swim by yourself
I mean
Training
Thank you
You
Been playing
Here's a float
Practice by yourself
You want me to time you?
Get out
Very good! Very good
I'm looking for Lan Tian
Who's Lan Tian?
It's said to be a low-key boss
The one who owns the swimming club
Please leave your contact information
We'll convey it for you
I'll back later
Is anybody there?
You again?
Song Chacha
What did you see
I'm asking you what you see
By the way
Lan Tian is your friend?
I'm telling you
Even if I know him
I won't tell you
No
It does not matter to you
She is so ..so
Ouch. That hurt
If you came for Lan Tian
Go for him
Why came to the locker room
It's clearly I'm in there
Bai Yongze
You know I'm here
So meet me, huh?
No way
No wonder last night
I had a bad dream
Where are you going
If you want to ask me about
my affair with LiBao
There's nothing I can say
I was commissioned be Mr. Lan
Flying fish Bai Yongze is down
Lanshi group offers timely help
Mr.Lan asked me to write a story like this
with a photo
And promote the resort
Is that okay?
Bai Yongze, you should smile
Smile you know?
Laughing while swimming, that's stupid
Okay
Let's take photos outside
I've ifgured out the title
Bai Yongze's pool show
That's wonderful, right?
And interviews?
You can email me
I'll reply when I am free
But I'm not sure if I have free time
Someone told me
There is a video, which can prove
the relationship between you and Lan Tlan
A video?
I don't know what the video is
The video's on your phone
But you can send it to me
And I'll do some editing
To create a vivid story
For you
Who told you
That's bullshit
I can't disclose that
I am doing this for your sake.
If you have anything
that need to be reported
in advance
Remeber to tell me
I'll polish it for you
Okay
Go
So you are not interested in woman
Right?
What are you doing?
Is it this?
Just kidding
If it was edited
It's easy to be misunderstood
Who is it?
Who took my phone?
I'm going crazy!
The lamp bulb?
Anyway
I can't just go back like this
At least to see Lan Tlan
I told you last time
You can't let her go
Do you know
what is she's gonna do to me?
Wait!
Who are you
What the hell are you doing?
What do you want
Did you copy my phone?
Did you?
What?
Didn't you copy the content
and call the reporter?
What are you saying?
That's why you threatened me?
Are you sick? I didn't
Wait