Are you new here?
I am Zhao Yan
As your senior,
I have to tell you something that
I won't look out for you
Don't you cry by then
Understand?
Start cleaning the room
with the plate
Your heart is beating?
It seems like yours
This is not your first time
to show up when I am not
decent
Did you put
a security camera
on me?
Because you are always naked in fron of me.
Are you an exhibitionist or something?
I dare you say it again
Stop
You came to my room for no damn reason.
I want an explaination
You are not wroking here?
Yes, I am
I am a hotel server
You are so close to collect
garbage on the beach
please be self-dignified!
Not everyone can sollect garbage
And
why do you care whether
I have dignity or not
I really don't understand
why do you stay by him
in this way
Have you been at rock bottom?
And you have nothing
To rise to my feet,
so
I need Lan Tian
He is your stepping-stone.
Is that what you meant?
Why do you care?
If you can't help me,
then leave me alone.
And I am warning you,
Don't judge a person's value so easily
It's my fault
I did that because I care about you.
Why are you here?
What is this about?
Your friend Bai Yongze
wangts me to tell you that
you are just nothing
in my life
And it turns out that I am right.
Because I decided to work here.
What did you say?
And Lan Tian' room is yours.
What?
Aren't you my sidekick?
Thanks.
This is just a mistake.
Don't be disgusting.
She said that because...
I am not talking about her.
Coach Huang and I
can't let you be yourself.
So I had been speciallly treated.
There is no one who wants take you in
To be hoest,
It is Coach Huang that
chooses to take you in.
Not you
Wait
Whoever takes me in,
I only cooperate when he
gets my aproval
It weren't for you,
Coach Huang,
he didn't even get a chance to see me.
And the test?
You all know what i got.
Do I have to be tested?
Well done
Well done, Song Chacha
Lan Tian
Be honest,
what do you really think
that stands in your way.
So we need to improve this project.
That's it
Let's call it a day
Everyone, get out.
Is it that hard to
control yourself?
After all, I am in charge
Frankly,
when do you think I am doing right？
What's the hurry?
What do you want from me?
What is wrong with
Song Chacha?
She is not a person who
can make her own decision
I want to know
why she is here.
You are right
I asked her to come
I just want her to
know that not
everyone in the world
will abandon her
and stay away from her.
I just want to encourage her
I said I don't have a problem
with you being CEO
And it is a deal between father and me
But,
don't get Song Chacha involed in this
I know
dad only cares about you.
The reason why I am here is that
dad is using me
But I am not a puppet
I am a CEO
Don't give me orders
on managing this resort.
I don't care why you are doing
all this.
Even you try so hard,
Song Chacha is never going back.
Why?
I am not interested in both of you.
I can act like nothing happened
and forget about her.
But she can't
So
I am gonna give her enough time
to forget you
One satnds on the edge of cliff
and is going to fall off it.
She deserves my sympathy
He's really changed.
No, you can't do that
No, you can't do that, Song Chacha
Who is it?
Lan Tian, I heard you are back.
I'd like to call you.
Do you remember me?
You
Can you show up
if I ask
Did you really see Bai Yongze?
Yes, I did
What? You mean
you saw him in person?
So what?
Dose he look more handsome than pictures?
He must be handsome.
I didn't see clearly, he
just got out of shower.
Did he...?
He what?
You flushed
Flushed?
Why did you run away?
Your ears are hot.
So what's really happened?
Come on, come on.
What I said about seeing Bai Yongze
is a lie
I lied, OK?
I knew it.
How could a new guy
see him?
It' would be so great if
I can feel
his swimming suit.
It's said someone went to his room
and saw him
with a halo
Just like,
he doesn't belong here.
Just like an angel falling from above
I am!
I must be crazy.
Let's get started.
This is today's training
except Bai Yongze's.
Cumbersome
Here is your training program
Do it yourself
Seriously?
I don't have that time.
This is not my first time
and you told me last time that
I can start next phase training.
Are you kiddding?
Ridiculous, I am the coach
I am telling you that
I only focus on those who listen to me.
You are not one of them.
But it depends on yourself.
I doubt your ability.
How?
Let's make a bet.
You?
Pontoon?
200m free style
The fastest one wins.
Bum-boy, what if you lose?
You do what I say.
Deal.
Come on
Come on.
Why
did Coach Huang do that?
200m free style
He is asking for trouble.
Shut up.
Yong Ze's explosiveness
is extraodinary.
If he keeps it,
Coach Huang is never gonna win.
No one is able to continue this way.
He swam so hard in the first half
I bet he
will be tired in the last half.
Come on
Come, coach
Come on, come on.
Come on
Yong Ze come on
Coach Huang wins!!
Yes.
What's wrong with him?
Yong Ze, are you Ok?
What happened?
I don't know.
Something is wrong?
Yong Ze, what's wrong with you?
Where are you going?
What is wrong?
I don't know.
You ok, coach?
You sure you don't do to the hospital?
Foeget it, I am ok.
No need to.
You have to go to the hospital.
You have to
Sir, if your condition is aggravated
if your condition is aggravated
you have to let me know
Got it, buddy
I gotta get my
three-month payment
I know it, go go
go, both of you
These cold-blood guys
So ungrateful
I just threw the car into reverse
I didn't see this coming.
How how is he?
The patient can't stand right now.
I think he should be observed in hospital.
I just threw the car into reverse
Are you picking me up?
I was going to the airport.
But
I couldn't remember your face.
So do you remember now?
What the hell?
So annoying!
I didn't expect such
a warm welcome.
Not bad.
Oh gosh, is that Song Chacha?
Did you just break up?
Yes, we did.
Then why is she here?
Is she stalking you.
I am so sorry
to let you see something you shouldn't.
Since you saw it
Forget about those hypocritical
greetings and concern.
I just want to buy you a coffee
as condolence.
But I have a date with Lan Tian.
So,
Song Chacha
Finally.
I have been waiting for you, like, forever
What the hell?
Isn't this Lan Tian?
Let's go!
Want some water?
I am not in that mood.
Can't you just pretend to see nothing?
You were standing there like a fool.
How could I pretend to see nothing?
You are the one
who prentended to see nothing
Why were you standing there, pathetic?
You what pathetic is?
Pathetic is when you are too embarrassed
to let people find out but get found out
by someone who shouldn't.
What the hell are you talking about?
My comfort is worth nothing?
I am so sorry.
It's OK to be embarrassed
in front of Lan Tian.
It's not OK to be
embarrassed in front of me.
Don't you understand?
I just don't want people to find out
what I look like when I look like shit.
This is my business.
What do you really want,
Song Chacha?
What is it you truely desire?
Revenge?
Or wanting him back?
Why are we at the aiport?
I have booked you a ticket to Beijing
You can walk yourself in.
Are you playing me?
I thought
you prepared well to be here.
Isn't it?
I bought you a first-class ticket
as freight of refund
I have been nice to you.
What do you want?
Scumbag
You heard that?
Song Chacha
I am scumbag
So
It only hurts to stay near me.
That's all you got
What? You quit?
What happened?
Why did you just quit?
What about me if you are gone?
What's my dimission concerned about you?
It is concerned.
We are colleagues
Don't you know?
Besides comrades-in-arms
colleague friendship is
the firmest.
Song Chacha
Ten minutes
Wait outside.
What happened?
I quit
Because?
It's personal.
Personal?
Got it.
Then
Zhao Yan will resign with you.
Manager, I don't want to resign.
I really never thoght about that.
I just take it as you are ready to leave
She wants to leave, not me.
It's personal.
OK?
I don't think it's reasonable
So you walked in and said
you want a resignation.
Is that reasonable?
There has not been a casual
worker who dares to want
a resignation since I worked here.
Who the hell are you?
Is it great to go through the backdoor?
I am sorry,
manager.
I worked hard to get this job.
I can't leave before my dream comes true.
I can't, I just can't, manager.
Just think
it's not your lucky day.
Manager
Out.
She won't leave with me
as long as I don't resign, right?
Cha Cha
Even so,
I can't pretend nothing happened.
Go and make an inventory of
equipment and materials;
,take that as your punishment.
Get it done, today.
How dare you ignore me.
I will show you what I got.
I am so sorry.
Because of me
That's fine
You said
our colleague friendship
is the firmest one.
Your dream almost shattered
because of me.
Don't worry,
I never forget you
if my dream comes true.
Who knows?
If I am the wife of the owner,
I will fire him first.
And I'll let you be the manager.
Is getting amrried to Lan Tian
your dream?
Of course
You know what?
I have a dream
What is it?
Getting married to a good man.
Why do you bet your life on a man?
It's not a dream.
It's gambling.
Anyway,
just wait there, Lan Tian.
I will bring him down
with my stunning beauty.
But what is your dream?
Dream?
What is dream?
It's something that can fill in your heart.
Everybody, think.
Do you have a dream?
Do you?
It's that urge
To be the winner.
It's so close to our test day.
Ask yourself,
where is your heart?
Did you put everything
into swimming?
Did you?
Lan Tian
Are you listening to me?
My dream
is to be the best swimming player
in this world.
That's my brother.
What about you?
What's your dream, Lan Tian?
Then I to be the best swimming player
in this world, too.
You have the same dream!
No
I am the only one of the best
swimming player in this world
That's not gonna happen.
I want to be the best swimming
player in this world, too.
If I win, I am the best.
Deal.
OK
Since you all have your dream.
Think about
who is the one you want to defeat.
Bai Yongze
Who is it?
I am asking you, Bai Yongze.
What kind of athlete do you want to be?
You are born to swim.
You will shine wherever you go.
Coach didn't defeat you.
You are defeated by yourself.
But
you won't admit it now.
Faster
Think about your dream.
Run.
What kind of athlete do you want to be?
Just someone?
Ha~
The kind of kissing girls.
Kidding?
Or provoking?
What do you think it is?
If it's provoking?
I don't have that time.
Just take it as provoking?
I just have a problem with you today.
Just wanna have a fight.
That's what I am thinking.
You are a real eye-opener today.
Which one is the real Lan Tian?
Both of you
what are you doing?
Forget it
Hey, stop
You have strengh to fight?
I am warning you
If I see you fighting again,
you will be banned from swimming.
That's it.
Training on the land is over.
Let's go back to the natatorium
Yes
He's not...
He was out of hospital this morning
Can he walk?
Doc says he is fine and releases him.
I know that.
Tears almost stained my face
Is it really necessary to come froward?
I am the CEO of this resort
with manners and high status.
I have to.
And I have to do it in person.
Damn it!
Who are you,
please?
Why...
are you taking off your pants?
What the hell are you going to do?
I am sewing my pants in my room?
Why do you care?
The problem is not whose room this is,
is you not wearing your pants.
Pervert
Psychopath
You are still busy with this?
Let's get out of here!
But
I haven't finished this.
We wiil do that later.
Manager is askng for us
Let's go!
You...
Come on, come on
Are you sure the manager
wants us to be here?
He told us to leave
when we cleaned that up.
What..?
Destiny is on own hands.
Hey, look!
Love love love fall in love love love
fall in love love love
What should I do?
He is looking at me.
Song Chacha
Is that not hurting enough?
Why are you still here?
Fall in love love love
just fall in love
the scene that I saw you
she remembers all
let every colour
Shit, you scared.
I already
see through you.
What?
Do you want
my number?
Who the hell are you?
Step away!
You look so cute
when you piss off
What about
having a drink
with me later?
Do you get along well with Bai Yongze?
Absolutely!
We are good friends!
Seriously?
I feel embarassed if
we have dinner
together
Just... you know
That's awkward!
What about
you asking both of them out
Fine!
Then, tonight
at the bar at the crossing.
Sure!
See you!
Bye!
This idiot
is just perfect for Song Chacha.
What?
Lan Tian told you to meet at the bar.
Lan... Tian?
Lan Tian...
Yong Ze ask tou
to meet at the bar.
Well, I sent the message
and I am gonna leave.
We are finished if you lie again.
The manager did say that we can leave
we can leave
after cleaning the pool
and organising the inventory.
How dare you say that!
Can you jsut sacrifice yourself
for me?
If I were the owner,
I could give you a position
larger than manager.
No!
I buy you some drinks
as my apology.
Song Chacha!
What the fuck!
You asked me out?
You asked me out!
Shit!
Jiang Shi!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I changed into my cool clothes.
So
I am late.
What tricks are you playing?
I just want to ask teamates
out for some drinks.
This is quite a good place!
Perfect
Waiter
Three packs of beer
Make them full!
Don't you know
we can't take in alcohol
because of training?
Well
Three glasses of beer without alcohol.
We should finish our work.
And then have a drink.
We will be more efficient
after a drink.
Then just have a liitle and we will leave.
Only if something miracle happened,
after a drink.
What are you saying?
I remembered.
There is a place that can changes my fate.
What are you talking about?
Just go, go
Cheers!
Hey angels!
Come here!