Episode 1 subbed by KuKan
Look at this guy listening to his music
Somebody pissed his pants right now
Isn't that right pissing your pants?
Its about to start the American
swimming men’s 100m Freestyle
final competition here in LA
Anderson who got most cheer is believed
to be the winner this year for
being the stable type of athlete.
For being the stable type of athlete.
He never made a mistake in many
international competitions
Knous keeps behind Anderson.
He rose to fame in Australia
and is sort of a dark horse.
Follow by Knous is Chinese
swimmer Bai Zeyong
nicknamed the East Flying fish
They are all very competitive players
and we are really looking forward
to seeing their performance today
Cruise has been doing
amazingly in the preliminary.
Will he be able to keep his game on today.
That’s what we are all waiting here to see
Bai yongze has kept really
impressive record in the American
Jet star swimming club
in the past few years.
Despite what an intense competence
it is going to be today,
he seems pretty calm and relaxed.
Cruise as expected to
be first bright leader
right from the start with tremendous speed
With Knous on the six
wing trying to catch up
Bai is right behind him,
but it doesn't seem easy for him.
Come on Bai, we will cheer for him.
The twin swimmers are about
make that 50m turns.
Are about to make that 50m turns.
Cruise takes the first turn.
And right on Knous and Bai Yongze.
Ah, they are not able to
close the distance here
Last 25m ahead
Bai is starting to speed up
trying to close the gap
He is just trying to pass Knous
Here is the final rush
Bai is really getting
close to Anderson Cruise
With 47s 96 Bai Yongze is the champion
What do you think about the competition?
I think I could have done better
You must be very excited
to win your first world champion.
May I ask who you want to share this with
With someone very important
Who is the one?
It's you.
You are watching? This is for you.
You crazy
Wow... be a lady, OK?
You don't want to be with me?
What if someone had known
about the relationship?
I thought you were gonna
announce our relationship.
So scared
When did I say you were my girlfriend?
I, Bai Yongze, the most favored,
got to be picky about choosing a girlfriend
Are you shy?
You know what,
this head is really expensive
and i got an insurance for it
Li Bao,
drive the car away as soon as i get off.
What’s wrong?
See you in the vally
There is your sweetheart,.
But I already knew that
When did you fall in love with each other?
What do you want?
What am i doing?
Help you get the headline. Have a look
If I see you again,
it isn't the camera smashed on the ground
you have nothing to be proud of
Fuck
Now welcome our main guest
this evening, Bai Yongze.
Where？
He has just won a match
and he will be a swimming
star in the world.
How are you doing?
Oh, Mr Lan, what’s up
Absolutely in the school’s library
What is the noise?
I am in the restaurant of the library.
Ah, I got an emergency,
I gotta go, bye mom
Seriously, again?
Do your job
Yes, sir
Welcome
oh, isn't this Song Chacha?
It seems you are really broke.
With no money for your postgraduate recommendation,
you poor thing come here to be a waitress.
Who is the pathetic one?
Of course the ones who can't
graduate in senior year
or the one who gets the first
class honour in thesis defense?
So what with the first?
You don't have enough
money for your tuition.
We, are going to America
I have lived the seedy life.
If there were nothing that
happened to my family,
I might still have been the one
who can't even take care
of myself just like you.
If you haven't decided your order yet,
I will come back later.
Wait, I heard that you
were discarded by Lan Tian
Oh, sorry to let you down.
If I am dumped, you will
be the first one to know.
If you like him,
go for it.
It’s just
he is not interested in you this type
What a stupid girl! We will see!
Wipe this out!
Wipe this! Are you a deaf?
Excuse me, sorry
What’s going on?
See for yourself
I am so sorry
Song Chacha
Wait, i heard that you
were discarded by Lan Tian
Sorry, the number you dialed
is not in the service
I hate you, Lan Tian
bye bye
OK, look at you
Do you really understand
what I feel about you?
Does it seems that I don't understand?
Then, prove it
Kiss me here
Bai Yongze
We are in the middle of talk here
Who do you think you are, man?
What kind of bullshit you
tried to pull your string?
Hey, don't be a loser.
Do you know the real one
is contesting in the pool?
Yong Ze
Stop, I am warning you
Get off me
Why don't you just go back home
and look at yourself in a mirror,
then ask yourself 'why did you lose'.
Maybe because I am better
Better?
Better? better than who?
You are just a bastard
without your parents.
What did you say?
Yes, I said it.
Everybody, this guy's dad only adopted him
to make a swimmer.
You ain’t shit. Let me
tell you something, buddy.
Your parents don't love you, just like a
little dog, nowhere to go, nowhere to be.
So dogie, sit,
stand, bark, wolf wolf
Wolf wolf
Yongze
Yong Ze
chill!
American News
Cruise Anderson, member
of Burn swimming club
And Bai Yongze
member of Jet Star swimming
club was witnessed to be
involved into a
physical confrontation earlier
Anderson claimed that
he was attacked by Bai
He started it
What?
Rumor?
Who wrote this?
A guy named Xu?
Mom, I have a party tonight,
I will come back later.
Hey, bring me an ashtray
You heard that?
Eh
Eh, I have a sober party tonight
and I am the volunteer.
Anyway, remember to take your medicine
I will call you later
Ashtray
Oh, I am sorry, no smoking here.
No smoking? What nonsense! You crazy?
Are you out of your mind?
I...
Song chacha
I said I will contact you.
It's inappropriate for you
to come to my working place.
Let’s go outside
I don’t care. pay the debt
When?
When
Why do you ask me for money
I can't find your uncle.
Who am I to ask for?
When! when will you pay
I am working to pay you,
so, out, now
This is a good idea
Penalties?
There is another reason they fire you
chairman of the board Lan
withdraws investments
What?
Oh, my BP
You go to them and ask for a favor
About what?
Investment
This is your fault at the very beginning
I got maligned at first. Why do I do that?
Why? Swimming.
Sir we are here to apologize
we are here to apologize
No need
even so i won't change my mind
Yong Ze is a grateful child.
Please give him one more chance
What a great father,
always believe in his son
Ha ha, you are right
I invested
because i trusted my son to much
Please, sir
Enough
Enough. Go home just.
Sir
If you want me to kneel down
I will do it.
Dad
enough, stop
I don't want to continue my career this way
I am telling you
I don't want a child who don't want to swim
Let go of me,
I would have never done
this job if I had known it
if I had known it
go
Let go of me
You have come this far, you
think you have a choice.
Fine
I go
Just behave
Come here
You
check the dance floor
, keep you eyes on it
You go to the back door, watch on it
Song Chacha, stop right there
You that way, you go this way with me
Song Chacha, come out right now
Who are you?
You are dead if catch you
I am asking who you are
Sir, help me please
Song Chacha
Thank you
Wear this
You will never walk out
that door with this dress
Bai Yongze is thrown out of Jet star
for good
At the same time,
It's reported that he is dating
with an actress named Li Bao
Who is that? It's midnight
You! You got so drunk
You come here at this time to
take me down with you?
You seem not happy to see me
I heard that the club
is going to dismiss you
What are you going to do?
There is nothing I can
do except for swimming?
I think I might be an actor
You are nothing if you don't swim
if you don't swim
Wait, you want to count on me?
I am just a new actress
There is no chance for us to survive
to survive
Right
Delete pictures of me
Well, forget it, I will do it
Where is your phone?
I think it's lost
What?
Lost?
What if people find the photos?
I am gonna ask you only one question
do you love me only when i am on
stages to receive the honour?
Fine
You must find your phone
Lan Tian, this
may be the darkest day of my life.
I feel abandoned
by the whole word
Yong Ze, don't lose your heart
Things may not be as terrible as you think.
No matter what happens,
I am on your side
So
So, take back what you said about
Withdrawing investment on Bai Yongze
I have made my mind
It’s not your business
Then we can make a deal
A deal?
Fine
What’s your leverage?
Leverage? Enough
And I have a condition
what is your leverage?
I want to restart swimming
Nonsense
You are my heir of my company
Are you out of your mind?
So I am making a deal with you
Alright, show me what you got
And I will decide if I want to do it
You must know what date
it will be in a few days
You stop me from swimming.
I will get married to
Song Chacha as promised
what?
You will pay all Song’s dept
According to previous agreement,
What do you think?
You are ..what?
A tough guy ha
How dare you!
So, do you accept it or not?
Fine, accepted
on conditions that:
I will invest on this team
Ok, I take it as a yes.
I will meet my lawyer when i am back
and I will turn the resort
my grandpa left for me
into a training base.
If I don't take care of Song Chacha,
she will be like poison.
Every time I think of
You being sad because
your loss of your father
I am as sad as you are
I know whatever I say cannot comfort you
cannot comfort you
I hope you will think of me, be strong.
You just left without any explanations
Who am I to you?
Hello
I am the owner of this phone
Who are you
The girl you just met in the
bar and wore your jacket
and wore your jacket
That bulb
Bulb?
You can have the jacket
Can you give me my phone?
Absolutely, yes
Can I give it to you tomorrow?
It's too late.
Hello?
Hello? No signal?
How can you be an agent?
You get up so later than I do
You don't remember?
You were drunk when you came back
I cleaned you up. And I was very tired.
I got home myself?
Yeah
Absolutely, yes
Can I give it to you tomorrow?
It's too late.
Phone! Your phone!
Come on! Come on!
Lan Tian
Hello
It can't be Chacha
Hello, bulb
Why did you take my phone?
Why was the line busy?
You know a guy named Lan Tian?
You went through my phone?
How can I be that kind of person?
I say
Take my phone and give it to me
My address is...
Hello
Battery is dead
I thought you were nice
Such an asshole
Hello
This is Lan Tian's father
Uncle Lan
Hello, what’s up. She hung up?
Sorry! The subscriber you
dialed is powered off
powered off
getting married
Yeah, getting married
I know you have a promise between
You and Lan Tian
And he mentioned that
He wants to fulfil it
That promise? I am sure he won't forget it.
Ok
So
I recently know that you
lost contact with him
you lost contact with him
It’s probably because of his mother
That he ignored you
Now that he put it on board and
I found you
So let's get this done
What do you say?
Wait! Uncle Lan
I think it's too fast
We haven't contacted each
other for a few years
You don't want to see him?
It's true that this is ridiculous
And I do think so
But, I know my son, he is so stubborn
If he wants to get something
done, it must be done
I can do nothing about it
Cha cha, i think we shouldn't
tell your mom about the wedding
After all, she is not
aware of some accidents
that happened to your
family for her amnesia
If your father doesn't show up
in your wedding, she might break down
she might break down
Therefore, I think
You two young couple just get it done
We will have a ceremony
when you mom gets better
Eh... does Lan Tian come back?
I'd like to see him first
His words are that
he goes straight to you for wedding.
It seems he has planed this for a century.
So weird.
Promise me
No matter what happens we will get married
We will get married
What if we break up before that?
Even you don't love me, I still do
Even if there is some kind
of mistakes blocking us,
I will come for you on the day
when we promise
to get married.
Just promise me, OK?
A promise is a promise.
I guess the answer will
show up when I see him
You can't do this
Can I give back your money later
I will return your money. I have money
I spend all my money on swimming equipment
That one
Look, I bought this
These goggles man's goggles and hats
Look, I bought these. there is no money
You know the story of goggles man?
I tell you
the man who wears goggles man wins champion
our players are great
You will regret it when we get championship
Just give us a chance
That’s pretty cool.
What? No
Why are you being a jerk?
I will give you money
No is a no
Oh my gosh
My idol Bai Yongze
got dismissed
Are you done?
We are the ones who get dismissed
Quiet
Please reconsider it, OK
Coach Huang
No
How you doing?
I am Lan Tian, remember?
You... look at you
Lan Tian
as for payment
Just relax, i will treat you right
You really want to be an athlete?
I thought it was
A joke or something
Then, have you decided?
How can I say no
when I can't even pay my rent?
Alright, i take it as a yes
There is one condition: I have a friend
And I want you to take care of him
Friend?
Stop kidding. What’s the hurry?
I said I come back because of business
I almost believe it,
you must miss me
Your company decided
to continue investing on your training
What
And I will start swimming again
What did you do to your father?
Did you sign some creepy
contract with him?
Much creepier
Much creepier?
Hey, Lan Tian
Bastard, he tricked me
What? He left his phone here
Almost forgot mine
Lan Tian? This is your surprise?
What surprise?
So?
You want to cheat on someone again?
Lan Tian? Is him with you?
You said Lan Tian last time?
You know him?
I am asking whether that
asshole is with you
What? Asshole?
What's your name?
Song Chacha
Lan Tian do you know Song Chacha?