I can do anything for you
Even at the expense of my reputation
Don't you feet it?
Too late
I want you to care about me
And want you to look after me
I regret breaking up
With you
I really regret it
Sister, the time had come
Are you crying?
Okay, Tears can replenish water
Later, too
Just pit it at the door
But he should drink hot
Well
and, run
Song Chacha
How old are you
You can't walk?
What if
you disfigure?
I don't know if it will leave a scar
Let me see
If
It leave a scar
Your face
Just become more ugly
The porridge is here
I'm gone now
Ugly face
Bad temper
What?
Ugly face, good ear
How can you be so sharp tongue
Did you cook it?
Yeah
You can go after I eat it all
Why
What if you poisoned?
I
Relax your muscles
Why you
I want you to see the wat I look
To let you blame yourself for a lifetime
This's just fair
But only in the begining
Not now
Because that's useless for you
So I wanna leave here
At first, Zhao Yan begged me to stay
Then
All sorts of of possip forrced me to stay
And
Song Chacha, you can't do that to me
What's the matter?
Give me the beer
What's this?
Abalone shell, broken by a hammer
There may be some residue
What?
By a hamer?
Use your head please
Use the spoon!
How do I know
You didn't remove it's teeth?
Does it have teeth?
I won't eat it
If you cook
like this again
You're in real trouble
If it wasn't for Jang Shi
It never would have happened
And
Why should I cook fou you?
You're not Lan Tian
I'll go
Song Chacha
You'll never give up?
Even
A pencil
If you like
You'll never change, right?
What are you saying now
Lan Tian told me
He told that's who you are
Maybe I am
Are you okay?
What that noise was?
Did the fool girl fall again?
Sister, where are you going?
I haven't any work lately
I can only sit and get older
I'll leave for Hainan
Do I look gaunt?
Why do you go to Hainan for?
You need to enchance your
cardiopulmonary function
Now continue to choking exercise
Swim as fast as you can
Change your air once at most
Ready
Coach Huang, I have a headache
What?
I have a headache
You said
Headacha, right?
Ready, go
Ah, they're a little naughty
We seemed to make the appointment next week
Here is the report
Ahem
OThe others have no problem
But the inspection report shows
Bai Yongze has got some exercise anxiety
It's just preliminary date
I'm not ure
what kind of anxiety it is
I wanna talk to him
Does it serious?
I'm not sure
But, go down so a long time,
His training will be affected
Even his competition
Brother Yongze
Are you okay?
I'm fine
How are you, what's the matter
I suddenly got cramp
Walk slowly, you got cramp
Is it really just cramping?
Of course
Teacher Fang wanna talk with you
I'll arrange
Why?
Your inspection report came back
It's bad
I just want to make sure
Thank you, But I have no problem
You needn't make sure. Bye
Brat
It doesn't matter
Then please give me his training date
I'll study it again
And you need to pay more
attention to his training
Today's case
Migth happen again
OKay, I know, thank you
Then I've got go now
You scared me to death
Please call me president Lan
Neuropathy
Fine, it doesn't matter
What are you doing with me, you're annoying
I have something to tell you
Stop prevaricating and come to the point
I want to invite Bai Yongze
To be a spokeperson for the resort
No way
His training
your saliva's on my face
I've to go
Why cannot I open it?
Why cannot I open your door
What's up
You did it?
What do you wang
Stay
Stay away from me
This door opens outward
I know
I could I met
such a stupid person
Your inspection report came back
The situation is not optimstic
I wanna make sure again
I'll meet you in the lobby
Long time no see
You don't think that's reigh now,
is it?
So
I'm going to stay here for a while
That's your business, bye
Disappointed in me?
The video thing
I'm glad
That before the video thing
I was dissappointed in you
Actually I've known that man a long time
I always believed he really loved me
After I met you
O cut oll all cintact with him
After eht video thing
I'm having a bad time
Song Chacha
What's up
Hey?
She is my girlfriend
So
You'd better adjust your
feeling as soon as posssible
What?
Sorry
That's all I can do
For the time being
I'll have to borrow you
I
Don't worry
I'm on night duty today
I'll come back soon after cleaning
Yongze
What's wrong with you, Are you okay?
Is anyone there?
What are you doing?
Aren't you uncomfortable?
Tell me what happen?
Since she met you
Her eyes were full of sweetness
I don't want people
to find out I'm sick
Sorry
She recalls every time she meets you
Every color is more warm to meet you
How is your weather there?
About you
All her thoughts
Except Lan Tian, I never thought about it
It's sunny rain
The strong wind brought in the
dark clouds in the distance
Just a wind
Is the sun useless?
It's like it just happened yesterday
It's all clear
But what really pisses me off is myself
Because at that moment
I felt it
Except Lan Tian
I never thought I'll be
with somenone else...
And my heart raced uncontrollably
In love with you
She lost herself
You're right
It does not matter to me
So
Please
Get out of my life
Don't hang around in front of me
Get ou of my sight,
Now
What I'm sad about is
I know he love her
But, I can't hate him
So I heat myself
If I didn't do this
I really don't have the
courage to let him go
I won't let him go
Congratulations
Congretulations
The groom is so old
Is it a wedding anniversary?
Maybe. You go first, I go to the toilet
Excuse me
Can you
Can you help me?
Thank you, Thank you so much
My dad owes a lot of money
He forced me to marry this old man
But a have a boyfriend who love me
Don't let your boyfriend down
Just go, cherish this relationship
Do not miss it
Bride
Who are you
Do you know how much money
the woman owes to me?
I'm sorry
Look
Either
You pay her debts
Or, you marry me
How much
Who are you
Give me a number, I'll pay
I don't care who pao it
The thing is
my wedding can't be messed up
She had to accompany me through the wedding
Whoever she is
Hands off
I said, I'll pay it
Anyway, don't touch her
I don't knows how much that woman owes you
But she
She can't be measured by money
I only left for a while
What happened again?
I never felt
this way before
I just think
It'd be a pity that the girl
and her boyfriend are apart
and she have to marry an old man
That's pathetic
Good job
This is you, Song Chacha
Get me some dress
Girls' clothes
Change to a favorite dress
I have my clothes in the locker room
I want you to take the wedding dress off
So, change
I finished
Just put the wedding dress on the couch
I'll give it back
So, this dress
No need to bring it back
It's rubbish anyway
Just handle it yourself
I wish I could turn and see you
This time, I'm sure I'll
catch it even harder
Chacha, We agreed on the day of our wedding
That's how you dress up
in your wedding dress
And I lost my promise
Does your ex-boyfriend still like you
Not the way you think
I can feel it
Actually, you still like your ex-boyfriend
Right
No
Less routine, more sincerity
I don't know
Anyway
Don't worry
I know your dream
So, I'm not gonna break it
Fine, but I know
My chances of realizing my dream
are still low
But, If you do it
I shall let it pass
No
I think, you should fight for it
Then don't regret it
Love is zbout timeing and action
You have a chance to gix it now
I don't hou much that woman owes you
But she
She can't be measured by money
Save my heart rate
And get some honey
In my eyes
Nofocus, except you
I still remeber, the way you looked at me
Today's training
Twice hands, forth legs
Anre you sure?
So what do you want, sixth legs?
I have my own habits
Sixth legs, I have done
from my youth upward
Good
Just show me
That was a deliberate attemp on my life
How coule Huang Donglei
to be Yongze's coach?
What a shame
Maybe they had other intentions
That's impossible
Huang Donglei is not reliable
It'll destroy Yongze
Who's esponsible for the consequences?
How could it be?
My Yongze is world champion
Woeld champion
Who can teach the champion
Even those world-famous coaches
Can't preach
No
That's because something happened to him
Nobody dared to take over
Are you hot?
Wear a suit on such a hot day
My skin is too delicate
to withstand exposure
Look at you
Didn't tell him
we were coming
Yeah, Keep your strength in this way
Once more, forth legs
Come on!
Keep forth legs
Huang Donglei
How did you train Yongze
Sixth legs even not enough
You let him did forth legs
That's the reason why he's
not good in the second half
What?
I don't need you to teach me
I'm improving her ability for second half
You know?
You're the onlt one who takes drugs
to improve your abilities, right?
Yongze, Here we go
Dad
He said that the basic
skills should be solid
Who is he talking to?
He is the one who not be solid
Good for nothing
I must be better at teaching than him
You're kiddingme
Anyway
Hong Donglei
Good for nothing
I taught him when he was a athlete
Have you ever heard of his medication?
Jst heard
Bustle up
Almost done
But, our group has an assignment
Already ready
Assignment?
Looks like an in-team test
Such a bad team, Test what?
So, are we leaving now?
Why don't you leave?
There's nothing to nostalgia
Yongze, you don't need this support
I can bring you up by selling my coolies
You can't even carry me
Who'll employ you
You
Yongze, now is the most
important time for you
I know
Let me say goodbey
Honey, now that we're in Hainan
Why not have a rest for several days
I heard the beach here is great
We can blow on the beach
and bask in the sun
And drink a glass of romantic wine
That's what I've always wanted
I want to be with you
Can you be a little reserved outside?
I think so
One mouth is annoying
That's awesome
You want to die?
It wasn't going well when I came here
I didn't think it was the same when I left
Has given you a lot of trouble
Good you know
But I also enjoy a lot of things here
That I don't have
anywhere else
You're wronged
Without you
I really appreciate it
I just wanna see
How long could your father take care you
I admire, your father is a good coach
But you can't grow
under your dad's care
If you want to get back to the top
You have to be
independent
Too bad
Qingshuiwan is a good place
You can't find a better place
than this in a short time
Such a pity
Brother Yongze
What do I do when you're gone
What about our standard competition
Without him, someone else will come
Why don't you go with him
Just go
If I go
What zbout Tianshi?
I'm sorry
I don't want to go also
But, what can I do
Tah's fathers'way
To dnhance the sense of existence
In this regard, we are both alike
Its a pity I didn't fight you once
But I'll always be ready for you
Thanks, man. We'll be in touch
Or
Is there any other reason
why you want to go?
You
I really want to swim with you
Song Chacha
Did you contact Bai Yongze?
No, What's up?
Jiang Shi just test me
Said that Yongze is going to leave
Now
Yongze, why don't you get in the car?
Dawdling what?
Here I go
What's the hell is going on?
I haven't had time to ask
Is there another problem on his body?
Goodbey, lamp bulb
I told you
Bai Yongze should be the spokeman
Hou could you let him go
So easily?
Then what else can I do?
Even if you hold him by the neck
Even if you hold him by neck
You have to let him to stay
For what?
For me
For you? Why for you
Do I have to tell you?
You'd better tell me
I don't know at all
You know
Anyway
You have th get him back inthree days
Such a crazy woman
Every time she shows up, she troubles me
Who is she?
Dad, I need to use bathroom