Cheers
Tian shi
Here!
You never told me
We have new friends
I'm Jiang Shi
Come on
Sit down please
Come on, come on
Come here
Here
Let me introduce
This is Tianshi
Tianshi 's friend
So
Hello everyone
My name is Zhao Yan
How about you
I'm Song Chacha
What do I call
This one?
How come you don't know Lan Tian
I already knew you
I'm a big fan of you
Thank you
Turned out to be such famous friends
Nice to meet you
Come on
Let's cheers
Cheers!
Tianshi, Tianshi
Your friends are unusual
Slowly down there
Take it easy on the booze
Are you concerned about me
No seduction
So
Do you have girlfriend?
No, I didn't
And
Before?
No
I just got dumped by my boyfriend
Oh
You must be sad
No, I'm not sad
Great
So It's time
to start a new relationship
Look
he
And he
Which one do you like
Bai Yongze
Do you like me?
So boring
Me too
Tianshi, Tianshi, Tianshi
Lan Tian, I'm going with you
You and I are a couple
No way
You said
It's about Liantian and Bai Yongze's video
Whatever
You just need some news
Or
Isn't this better?
Are you sure I got it?
If you ask again
I'll change my mind
Looks like you really did
Ask a personal question
Do you think
it's necessary?
Have you ever loved someone
Until there's no distinction
between right and wrong
Or even
Hated?
That's what I'm like right now
Like a madman
Cheers
Chacha, you're a great drinker
Lan Tian left too early today
What a pity
But
Why are you
letting him be your boyfriend tonight?
He has a girlfriend. Do you know?
Stop this nonsense
I'm single
The affiar between you and Li Bao
bacame generally known in the whole country
That would have been clarified
Explanation is covering up
Cover-up is truth
We really have a taict understanding
Cheers!
So
Can we be together now?
No way
Come here, come here
I'm coming Tianshi
I know what you think of me
A fool
Always around him
and wish he could change his mind
Anyway
Lucky enough to be able to do it back
But
That doesn't matter
When I saw
Lan Tian kissing her
I suddenly felt
Maybe it's not me
standing on the edge of a cliff
Maybe it's Lan Tian
So
He deliberately kept away from me
Think this way
A little comfort in my heart
You only understand others
if you have experienced it
The way he looked at me
Really hurts me
That's not what he used to do to me
Really hruts me
You won't regret it?
If I can get what I want
It doesn't matter
I'm not scared
And
I decided to follow my heart
until the last moment
Maybe
Time will answer me
Look like
I don't need to worry about you
You're stronger than I thought
Don't treat me like a girl
I'm veteran in battlefields
I can lead a life of rich people
I can also live economically
The famous car
is the same as the bus to me
So all this pain is nothing
Nothing
Just leave it and try the different one
You're drunk
Don't worry
I'm not drunk yet
And said you was a good drinker
Aren't you drunk now?
I was
I was afraid you'd fall
What do you think I am?
How dare you! capricious!
I'm an aesthetic
Beat it
You're going the other way
Your house is over there
I know
I'm going back to resort
for sorting supplies
It's too late now
I'm a temp, I have to do
I say it again for the last time
Beat it
Lan Tian
You know he did it on purpose
Bai Yonge
Why do you care so much
Why
Do you like me?
I knew
Song Chacha, I
Song Chacha
Wake
Chacha
Lan Tian
Don't go
Bai Yongze
Be sober
Lan Tian is my best friend
You shouldn't like her
You shouldn't
I'm a temp
I have to go back to resort
for sorting supplies
It's too late
Still working so late
Better help her
I'm so kind
It's a disease
It needs treatment
How did she clean up so much
Fine
take it as exercise
Did she get home safe and sound?
Disappear
Right now
Where am I
Who am I
How did I fall asleep
It's bad to be found
Just in time, My room is ran out of this
Just right
Did you get home safetly yesterday?
Yes, I did
You look good
I didn't sleep all night
Because of you
Because of, me?
Why?
Don't you remeber?
Yesterday
You kicked my shank
I'v been hurting all night
Up to now
My right leg is still hurting
You know?
Really?
I don't remember
Of course
What am I lying to you for
Didn't you hurt your right leg?
Be sure to tidy up
berore manager finds out
Who tidied it up?
Zhao Yan?
Song Chacha doesn't do that
She was drinking with me yesterday
We drank late
No time to go to the warehouse
Whatever
She's in charge of supplies
She should know where the missing box is
What happened?
Song Chacha
Where'd you take the hotel supplies?
The hotle supplies?
Brother Yongze
breaking news!
What happened
Brother Yongze
I ask you
What time did you dring
with Tianshi's friend
last night?
Why..
Why ask me
She just called me
said
Chacha stole from the hotel
She might be fired
Articulate your words carefully
How could Song Chacha
be treated as a thief?
They say she stole hotle supplies
The manager was angry
And he said
I'll not let it be
What do you think
what should we do?
What kind of equipment
did Song Chacha embezzle
It was me
What?
What did you say
Nothing
There is
No
Anyway
Not her
Is it the toothbrush?
Toothbrush?
What toothbrush
Tell me, tell me, tell me
Tell me!
After you drinking with ZhaoYan
You were here to misappropriate supplies
Right?
Not me
It's really not me
How do you prove it?
I
Hey
Chacha
Would never misapropriate
hotel supplies
She was with me
until this morning
Where am I
Don't worry
Nothing happened
Don't be ashamed
You were unconscious last night
I can only bring you here
We
How did we meet?
Don't you remeber?
You called me last night
I must be mental
Have a drink
My mom must be worried about me
Must have been up all night
Aunt called me last night
Called you?
Yeah
I said you were with me
You drink too much
So sleep at the resort at night
Sorry
I think it's enough to prove
She didn't midsppropriate it
Okay?
Okay
I hope
I'll never
hear the relevant gossip later
Yes, Sir
God
Too much information
Let me sort it out
Everybody out
Zhao Yan
You seduced
the boss
You're lucky this time
Next time
It won't be that easy
Zhao Yan
Don't talk to me
You want to tell me
how you seduced the boss?
You know that
I wanna be with Lan Tian
Bad Woman
I'll tell you everything
Shut up
I don't want to hear it
I never thought
That you looked so pure
But resourceful
Zhao yan
You're so scaring
Ostensibly
You said you liked him
Stealthily
You seduced Lan Tian
I didn't
I shouldn't be your friend
I didn't mean to lie
I don't know
why I'm in his room
Looks like I was drunk
And called him
I don't remember
You don't need to report to me
There is no affiliation between us
Lan Tian
Please don't go
Hey
Song Chacha
Where are you now
I'm doing something against myself for you
You know?
You're driving me crazy
What can I do for you
That's all
So
Song Chacha
I'm just giving back what I owe you
what if I can't do it?
I don't want you to get me wrong
I'm sorry
I just wanted to tell you the truth
I just wanted to explain it
to you
Song Chacha
Is a bitch
If I were her, I would have resigned
Stop talking aout her
So
The bitch is coming
Can I sit?
How dare you?
Just because you
Temporary workers are always scolded
Stop pretending to be pure
Do something like this
Why don't you just go to bar
It suits you there
Bad luck
Do you want a friend
or an opponent
I wanna know your idea
What if
I want them both?
So greedy
So you asked as a friend
or an opponent?
What kind of opponent?
Swimming?
Now
I ask you as an opponent
Chacha,
Do you l ike her?
No
Then, I ask you as an opponent
I ask you as an opponent
Song Chacha
Do you like her?
No, I don't
Then don't sympathize her
If you really think about her
That's my advice as a friend
Neither a friend,
Nor an opponent
So boring
Hypocritical guy
Feverish and drinking
You're too willful
Song Chacha
Me Bai Yongze
I can't believe I'd do anything
For Song Chacha?
Just out of sympathy?
Bai Yongze
I told you to clean
Didn't let you break my bag
Madam
I really just
Moved your bag
Please believe me
Just move?
So
Where did this mark on that bag come from?
Maybe it was before
But I just opened the seal
Go
Call your manager
Pay me immediately
Madam
Please
Please don't do that
Madam
Your bag looks like a fake
What?
That's impossible
Though
It looks well
But
If it's genuine
There will be a logo here
And
The location of the lock
Seems different
What do your mean
It's from my husband
Anyway
It must be a fake
What if it's not?
What should you do?
Treble damage
Song Chacha
How did you know?
I used that bag
So I know
But I'm broke now
So I sold them all
What?
You used that bag?
Lan Tian
He was my fiance
Of course
I was dumped
So
Your dreams are not broken
I don't want to get in your way
Just
About yesterday
Okay
Stop talking
I don't expect you to forgive me
If you're still angry
There's nothing I can do
I just hope you know
That I think of you
as a friend too
Recently
There's a mysterious person
exposing the video
The video has aroused heated
discussion on the Internet
In the video
Libao and a man of the same age
Brother Yongze
Something terrible happened
Li Bao's video
Her pure and lovely
Public image
You've already seen it
would you like a drink of juice?
Calm down
Why me?
Are you
angry now?
So
Are you really with her?
I told you!
Sister Li
Something's going on outside
Is the ambulance here?
Already
Why do we call ambulance?
It's full of reporters out there
How did you
become my agent with your low IQ?
But...
What's your mood now?
Is the man in the video
really your boyfriend?
You really have nothing to do
with Bai Yongze?
I'll say it again
We are just friends
I hope you don't bother him
because of me
As your friend
Does he know
about the video?
What did he tell you?
Miss, Li
Can you answer that again?
That's all for today's interview
So serious
Tell what?
Beautiful? Sexy?
Sister Li
lie down
The windows are transparent
Quickly
Sister Li
Is your makeup
too pompus?
After all
you're sick now
It's called image management
As a star
Be beautiful even if I faint
The way she was sent into the ambulance
So cute
Brother Yongze,
Who was she showing it to?
Show?
But
She just said one sentence
before she got to the ambulance
I hope
you don't bother him
because of me
She spoke out my name
It's a problem
Well
Stop talking zbout her
I envy your confidence
So good
Brother Yongze,
You look good when you're overbearing
I'm so attracted
You are my superstar
50 meter butterfly stroke
At one go
Butterfly is important
to the start of the game
Be sure to train well
Come on
Ready
I'm done
I only work for half a day today
I'm all day
You work too hard
Song Chacha
Are you off tomorrow
Yes, I'm
Me too
What's this?
Tickets to the beach?
If you're free
Let's play together
I'll get the food ready
Okay
Are you okay?
Probably too hard
If I was there all the time
You must work so hard all the time
Adjust yourself
wait and see
It hurts more today
Maybe I need go to the hospital
Woe worth the day
Why didn't Bai Yongze appear
Maybe for Li Bao's video?
Fainted by shock
It's too late
Yeah
He really for Li Bao?
Just waiting
whatever, It doesn't matter to me
The misunderstanding has
finally been solved
Sweetheart
We have to cheer up today, too
You can talk with a flower
God
You
What are you doing
Sorry
If the reporter finds out
it's going to be a lot of troubles
You,
Was it really hit?
What?
The reporters said
You're hit
By Li Bao's video
We just liked each other
In fact
We're not together
Why told me
There's no relationship between us
Are you angry?
Really angry?
Cause I said the words?
Actually, you're right
Today, I know
The sky is so beautiful
The world is so vast
But I lived in the water
Suddenly I felt
I've been bound by something
Maybe
Myself
So, Song Chacha
Don't worry too much about
what others think of you
Just follow your heart
If you like Lan Tian
Just do it
Do what you want to do