What
You left the club.
Are you okay?
Noisy you
Now I'm in the same position as you.
I left the club anyway.
We must have a good drink today
But why are you responsible for this?
And make me back
One can be without a job.
But not without dignity.
A girl is so vilified.
How can you keep quiet?
I can't stand them talking
about you like that.
Are you satisfied with the answer?
Waiter, one more bottle.
Two more bottles.
Actually, it doesn't matter if I’m fired.
But, your training
it’s about your future.
And haven't you been
choosing someone for the competition
Don't you care?
Why bother your own future for me?
Cause you're my girlfriend.
Anyway
I’ve been officially
talked to others about us
Now everyone knows
You're mine
So, Bai Yongze just left.
Then I can't let the Song ChaCha come back.
I'm a boss.
How could it be threatened by Bai Youngze
Bai once said
It's not Chacha’s fault.
Shouldn't you have brought her back?
Does she look better to you now
She’s like to die to live
and let me get her out of here?
No, not now
I brought Yongze here
So I'm responsible.
Dad said he was coming.
So, if Dad knew Chacha was here
It's even harder to do.
You know that better than I do.
There's no other choice.
Dismissed by the reason
What do those people think of me?
Anyway, for me
There's no more nostalgia.
You should go back soon, too.
To Lantian
Without any nostalgia
Since i was a kid
I tried my best to do so
At the orphanage.
My dad said he was gonna adopt a kid
who swims very well
I remember I'd never been in water.
But I said I could swim.
And swims very well
But I can't reveal it
So, before he took me,
I sneak out every day.
Went to a nearby pool and practiced alone.
Try my best
Can you believe that I learn it myself
I’m such a person
Who walked through all the pain to this day
Yourself?
You can learn to swim without a coach.
If you don't try to go upstream,
You just wait for drowning.
Then you can learn it
These years
I've been surviving
so
I'm not going back because
of your requirement
As for the competition,
I will always find
Someplace that suits me
Cheers
You drank too much
So I took you home.
You drank too much.
Come on.
I've never been drunk since I was so old.
You mean me, right?
Look at me.
Am I drunk
You walk in this way
Still insisted that you aren’t drunk
Yeah
Come on, asshole. I'll take you home.
Fine
Door
Who’ s it?
My God
What did you
Oh, that stinks.
How much wine did you get
Yongze
I’ve delivered you, then I left.
That's the bathroom.
Sorry, I know, l konw
That's the bedroom
Where the hell is the door?
Toast
Let’s go since you recovered
from your drunkenness
Yeah, yeah.
I’m out of wine, broker sister. Out of win
I amn’t your sister, okay?
What sisters? brothers?
There's no beer, anyway.
There's no beer. beer ...beer
Two lunatics.
No
What's he doing bringing
a woman in so late?
Then, should I leave? leave him alone.
Cheers
Once your real girlfriend knows that
You're leaving the club because of me.
She’s gonna to be pissed off, right?
Who? Libao? Don’t mention her
It’s over between me and her
I only have a fake girlfriend right now.
That is you
Well, didn't you leave me to Li Bao?
So you're sad
Bye
Wait, I'll give you a ride.
Song chacha
Is anybody here
She left yesterday
Who’s gonna be early in the morning
Had a drink last
Yongze
Just drank a little bit. What 's up?
I heard that you’re leaving the club
Sorry, I didn’t tell you earlier
But I screwed up the event
You shouldn't blame Chacha
She’s important to me
Since she’s so important to you
Why’s on valentine’s day that you
embarassed her so much
What about the news between you and Libao
How can you believe this gossip
Anyway, I have no defence for that
Cause I didn’t do it in a right way
I see
If
What if you stay
Will you stick to your decision
Don’t you really want to
Take a fight with me
Tomorrow
Sorry
Only remember this
I really should stop drinking
Cumbersome
He doesn’t know today’s test
He won’t come today
Why
Sorry, I’m late
Okay, it’s our team testing day
The test is the 200-meter freestyle
After this period of hard training
Though there’s a lot of stuff
But I also saw your efforts
Someone try to complain about the coach
Someone try to play the missing
Someone try harder to steal wine
And someone try to look after his wallet
Anyway
I hope all of you can get good grades
For the rest of the time
It’s our team
To sent someone to the
national standards contest
Also, it’s the first test of our team
Just do what you can
Bai Yongze 1 "47" 85
Yongze brother
You’re the world-class
LanTian 1 "53" 20
Guan Jie 1 "56" 30
Jiang Shi
Coach, forget about mine
Oaky, then forget it
When you finished relaxing training
Come to my office for a meeting
Coach
How
I can’t attend the meeting
and I’m not going to play for the team
Why
What’s wrong with you
I promised to take this test before
So wait until it’s done
The last valentine’s day
I caused damage to the resort
It’s right to leave
I hope all of you will understand
You mean, it’s all my fault
Fine, if you want go, just go away
Don’t come and left, okay
Don’t worry
I won’t let you down
No, I can’t let you go
You’re a swimmer
Just because of a commercial event
Then you’ll leave the team
It should be the coach if
someone has to be away
What’s the meaning? Why is me
For it’s you who make him
to join the event
Listen to me, I didn’t do that
It's up to you to decide
whether to participate or not.
Even so
Lantian, aren’t you Yongze’s best friend
Try to persuade him
He won’t listen to me
he had won
but he’ll go
You want us to keep you
Do you know how many people
want this opportunity?
Anyway, everybody, take care.
I'll see you later on the court.
Yongze brother
It’s the coach
Shut up
I told you, I didn’t recommend it
So you wanna leave, don’t you
Coach Huang, I want to know instantly that.
Who can play the game
No matter what, it’s not your turn
A man who didn't swim in 1 "55"
isn’t qualified to speak
No... He...
Relax and train
You quit without telling me
Are you still taking me as your agent
And, uh, do I look like a valet?
So ridiculous of you
It's not funny. It's humiliating.
So humiliating.
What’s wrong with your hair
You know nothing
What else can you do besides swimming?
Listen, this is called airport gear.
Only when on the plane
I have this kind of haircut
Would you mind paying more attention to me
And we're not going to the airport.
What about airport gear?
So, you’re not going home
Even if you had to go back.
You have to figure out how to go back.
Don't tell my dad about this, please.
Your dad
Your dad, he wants you to leave.
What about the coach Huang
Then where are you going?
Let's find a nearby hotel.
What about the hotel money?
Of course the broker did.
What’s up
I mean
Why don't you take charge
of the swimming team?
Are you proposing to me now?
Asking... for... marriage
Don’t you just want to marry me now?
And then let me be
the actual hostess of the swimming club.
No
You... You ...understand what I'm saying?
Even if your EQ is low, your IQ is low.
Your understanding is poor
And not to have my words
understood like this.
Why are you so angry
What the hell are you talking about?
What I'm trying to say is
Miss, you have no power
To decide whether Bai
Yongze will stay or not.
Bai Yongze is my man.
Think about it, if
If I fire your staff,
What would you think?
I can’t thank you more if you do so
It happens that our Lingshuiya
is near the Ching Shui Wan
There's a lot of collaboration
with other big businesses.
I can't do it myself.
You... You're capable.
I'm not talking to you.
Listen to me
You made me coach, right?
You can't go beyond your
authority or you'll coach.
Can you teach me how to swim?
Can you be a little reasonable?
I... I just
I just did what he asked, okay?
I see
You wanna to talk to me, don’t you
All right, take it easy.
I'm still busy.
Wait, are you insane?
Should you go see a doctor?
What do you mean I want to talk to you?
What do you mean, I want to propose?
Oh, my gosh, I'm having a headache.
I am so angry
I really can't talk to her.
She's such a psycho.
What's all this sudden?
You're leaving.
We can't help giving you a farewell party.
Anyway, thank you.
And thank you, Guanjie.
There's nothing to thank.
Yeah, I'd like a drink, too.
Come on, join us
Come on
You don't have to move out so soon.
Staying in the resort
And no one's gonna kick you out.
Lantian, you don't understand.
Yongze moved out
is to date Song Chacha more conveniently
What the hell?
But, before I go
I do have a place to go
with Song Chacha
Anyway, it's all here in Hainan.
We need to find something.
Like Beach villa. Come and live.
So, do it with Song Chacha
Are you through?
Song chacha
Why are you suddenly here?
Of course I did.
Isn't it just Yongze
Hurry up
You were both forced to leave.
Anyway, having a fight with Lantian
For a final battle.
Let his eyes sparkle.
Come, come, come.
Come, come, come
You two little couples sit together
Sit down
I'd like to introduce you formally
This is my girlfriend.
Hey, Bai yongze
How many girlfriends do you have?
The other day, don’t you stay with
Libao for the valentine’s day
That story is not true.
I know
I suggest that we go to KTV later
Good
Round two, you guys go.
I have something to do
Wait, wait. You're in charge today.
Where do you want to go
KTV KTV KTV
Where are you going? Go
Song chacha
Why do you have to turn
around in front of me?
Why don't you stay away from me?
You go
The farther the better.
I'm not drunk. Why do you
have to send me back?
Everyone knows you're my girlfriend.
Haven’t drunk. Okay. bye.
This doesn't fit me.
Bai Yongze's image as a gentleman.
When did the Lantian leave?
I do not know
The guy left without a word
I don't think we should
pretend to be a couple.
That's hard for you, too
And I think I misunderstood Lantian
He may not have attachment to me anymore.
As for the feelings
Men don't share it with others.
Once others see it
They'll feel humiliated.
So, once people are aware of their minds
And they'll guard against it.
Lan tian might be the same.
Anyway
Bai Yongze, you ‘re singing too bad to hear
What the hell are you talking about?
I sing as well as I swim
which attracts million of girls
Oh, my God
You haven't been tuning all night, okay?
Really?
I think it’s great
If I don’ t continue swimming
I’ll be a singer
You still put aside your
plan to be a singer.
Keep swimming.
Go in
By the way, are you okay?
It's okay. Guess it's
because of a girlfriend.
Although it's a fake.
Song chacha
Last night, you
Don't say anything about that.
Chacha
Go in
Right
It's better to pretend.
What if she remember remembered
Why bother about this?
What the hell do you want?
She must have said she was just drunk.
Just be drunk.
Bai Yongze
Song chacha, She has been afraid
of the dark since she was a child
She can't sleep at night without it.
Why? why?
Why commit suicide?
I said no.
Don’t talk back. I know all about it
Cause you are leaving the club
So, you're so sad that
you're gonna kill yourself.
Baiyongze, what's going on with him?
He tried to kill himself and climbed onto
the street lamp and was electrocuted.
What
Yong ze, are you okay?
How could that be?
Suicide, Suicide, Suicide,
Suicide
And it's all because of you, Coach.
But for you
let him join the event like that.
Get him out of the club.
How could he possibly kill himself
You useless thing
How big a thing, you kill yourself.
I said no. That's not true.
I know you're not the
kind of person to die.
What the hell is going on here?
They said that you climbed up the
streetlight and was electrocuted.
Why climb up the streetlight?
Yeah, why climb up the street lamp?
See you again.
Looks like your boyfriend's
in the hospital this time.
What boyfriend?
Your boyfriend.
The last time you were hospitalized with
a fever in the middle of the night,
He's hurt, too.
But he doesn't care.
Come back and forth for you
You have to take good
care of him this time.
Who come back and forth for me
You mean the guy in the room?
Yeah, it's the one called Bai Yongze
Yongze
They said that you climbed up the
street lamp and was electrocuted.
Why did you climb up the streetlight?
Yeah, why did you climb up the street lamp?
Your boyfriend.
The last time you were hospitalized with
a fever in the middle of the night,
He's hurt, too.
Song chacha, chacha
Lantian
Bai Yongze
What the hell are you doing?
Have you asked about the
sponsoring company?
I had a chat about the
difference between big and big.
But we're not sure yet.
What is it? wait, what did you say?
What? what?
Bai Yongze
You have sponsorship.
And it's a lot of money.
I'll be right back.
I always pretend to go out with Lantian
It's not a way.
But Mom's in better shape.
I can't tell her the truth.
Then where am I going?
Looking for a little sidekick.
No, no
what's up?
You don't miss me?
You're sick
It's just a joke.
It's a famous girlfriend, anyway.
Why are you so angry?
Then why are you looking for me?
Let's meet.
Great.
Take this
Okay. Okay.
That ring
I don't know where I lost it.
What’s wrong with Lantian today
Two seconds late. What happened?
He is now
Like a lonely wild goose
that lost his companions.
Lonely geese, what's your mood? I get it.
But, uh, we miss Yongze
He doesn't care.
The only thing in his heart is Song chacha
By the way, Yongze is leaving tomorrow.
He might propose to chacha today
I'm leaving tomorrow, chacha
So there's something very presumptuous.
I want to ask you once, just once
Are you coming with me?
Lantin, sorry
Lantian, what are you doing?
We’re teammates.
A gentleman will speak with
tongue but not with the tongue
Lantian, Lantian
What? what's going on like crazy?
Are you all right
What’s wrong? You surprised me
You just see through the mirror.
Can't be beautiful, right?
I
You look in the mirror and
you're gonna get in there.
The face doesn't work like this.
You're perfect, right?
Sneaking around, peeking at people
Are you sick?
Why don't we go get some dinner? come on.
What? all of a sudden.
Just in case.
In case that Lantin suddenly pops out,
We don't look like couple
Isn't that helping?
Lantian will be around here today.
Isn't it?
I mean, in case he's around here,
Don't make such a joke.
Are you a real pervert?
Come on, I'll take you some delicious food.
Miss chacha
Do you think I’m that kind of person
who can't afford someone else
to go to a fancy restaurant
Go somewhere else.
I just like to hang out here.
Here are mangoes, oranges, and
It's so fresh.
Do you just smell the scent
and know if it's fresh?
Of course, if it's fresh,
Can be sensed by smell.
Smell it
how
Do you feel a sweet smell on you
Nope
Looks like you're not
just thinking about it.
Not even a nose.
Such delicious scent is not to be heard.
What a sin.
Why don't put their soup?
Because their soup taste bad
It's monosodium glutamate.
And I like the soup in hotpot
I'll make one for you
How about it?