Song Chacha
She's been afraid of the
dark since she was a child
She can't sleep without light
That's the reason why
I didn't go dating
What's the manager's job?
To keep employees safe?
Because she's not a regular employee, so...
Whether she's or not
Now there's an accident
If the news went out
What about our resort?
You know?
If that happens again,
You quit your job
Song chacha
You're a disaster
You'll see
I won't let you pass the exam
Song Chacha, why don't
you take a few days off?
Take care of yourself
She's fired if she doesn't come to work
That's for you
And, who caused the incident?
Disregard for the safety of colleagues
Left her there, Went ahead
Are you not responsible for this? Zhao Yan?
It's my problem, not her
You really think so?
Fine, It's your problem
So, you don't need to clean the guest room
But, you need to be a restaurant waiter
How tiring that is!
Cleaning customer service is easier
I want to be a restaurant waiter
Look at your face yourself
Who will have the appetite for
the food of our restanrant?
I'm a woman
How coule he say someone
else with an ugly face
How can you laugh under this circumstance?
Anyway
He thinks my face is okay
God
You are out of mind
Did you fight with others?
I'm fine. Don't worry
I hope something happens to you
So I can get you out of here
And I'm free
Should the coach say that?
Should an athlete fight with others?
Instead of protecting his body?
Well, well
Don't worry, brother Yongze
You have me
If something happens to you one day
And you can't swim
I'll take care of you
Get out
Start training
Yes!
Hello, Tea please
So tired, right? Song Chacha
I can't even watch it
Zhao Yan, did you finish your work?
Anyway, I'll help you first
After all, you got lost because of me
Don't worry about me
Then, I'll treat you to dinner
Just dinner?
And beer?
Nah, after you marry to Lan Tian
Let me be a manager
So, did he get hooked?
Of course
He didn’t even go to the blind date
Your method works
He's getting jealous
Let's wait and see
If Lan Tian changes his mind
Song Chacha
You must repay me
Okay, touday's plan
Two groups of 200m freestyle,
ten times per group
To be a good swimmer
Leg movements must be in place
Lan Tian, you keep sixth legs today
Forth, okay?
No, you're getting more
and more out of red line
What have I done?
I know you don't like me
And you like Lan Tian, I know
But you can't be so unfair
What have I done?
If you have problems, you can tell me
Coach Huang
You know anything about me?
Before you set me a training level
Anyway, I've won countless prizes
Reduce frequency?
Do I still need to practice basic posture?
You do, you need it
I don't care how many prizes you've won
What were you doing when
I started swimming?
Let me tell you
Ability is more important than speed
No matter how fast you swim
Coach Huang
You should realize your current situation
None of you can meet my demands
Your worst problem
Is tactical physical distribution
Your second half is so weak
You have to practice basic posture
Yes, I really don't like you
But, I'm a fair man
I don't care who you are
I don't care who is rich
Here, you're all on my team
You must remeber
This is a team
A swimming team
Understand?
Start training
Today, Lan Tian is the best
Brother Yongze, you're the worst
You even slower than me
Did I improve?
Shut up
Lan Tlan helped Song
Chacha yesterday you know?
If you go on behaving in this way
Not only do you swim slower than him
but
your girlfriend will also be taken away
I said shut up
Don't be angry
Have you seen Song Chacha?
I don't know!
What's up
Got kicked out as a claener?
Can you say something good?
All I can say is
that I 'm too good to be good at everything
What's wrong with your face? Did you fight?
Huh?
If I get hurt
must it be a fight?
So I ask you
Well, get to the point
Why am I here
Did you know I was sick yesterday?
Well
Maybe you were fighting
Even if you knew I was sick
You wouldn't come to see me
What do you want to say
Maybe
You're gonna continue
to be my fake boyfriend
What?
Lan Tian semms jealous
He canceled the blind date yesterday
So I wanna follow up a
victory with hot pursuit
How to follow up the victory
Be more proactive
Honey
Chacha
Honer, are you hungry
I cooked for you
Oh, sweet heart did you cok all this?
I want to eat it
I feed you
That's disgusting
SongChacha, You'd better come to me soon
Before I get angry
Are you crazy?
Well, do you want another way?
He is coming
Honey, waht do you want to eat tonight
I'll cook for you
Great, I like your cooking best
What did you do last night?
Your hair's so messt
Song Chacha, look
You're belong with me
Kill me, now
I won't do that
Have you ever been in love?
Did you get kicked by the head?
Why we do it
You used to do this with him?
No
Then why would you
let me do this?
I'm not an actor
You're ridiculous
I'll tell others your secret
You
Lan Tian is coming
Help me, help your girlfriend
Wipe
You have to make
a very happy expression
About yesterday, thank you
That's okay
My mom doesn't know we broke up
And she doesn't know my dad died
After the accident
My mom lost bust
Don't worry
I know
I'm sorry
For the stuff
I
I'm sorry to you
Why you stand here?
This is the first time he said sorry to me
Did he changes?
Let's go buy lover's clothes
Bai Yongze
Where are you going
Is it inappropriate for me to wear this
You must war it
So that Lan Tian will be angry
And he will hold you and say
Song Chacha, you're mine
Where is Bai Yongze
He' ll be right out
This lovers' clothes
must be suitable for him, right?
See? He's angry
Really? Of course
But why doesn't he come out
Jinag Shi
Take Bai Yongze out
Tianshi
He locked himself up
Tell me what to do
You broke the door open
and the him out of there
Really? okay
I understand
Brother Yongze
If you don't come out
I'll break the door
One
Two
Three
Brother Yongze
Sit down please
What's up
I ask you
What
Do you have appointments
for Valentine's Day?
Does it has anything to do with you?
Just answer me
Do you like me?
You're narcissistic
You really out of all reason
You asked me first
Right?
So what's up
I wanna invite Bai Yongze
to participate in the event
You're not happy
Do you think I like you?
Are you sick?
I'm not him
Just talk to him
I'm busy
You're his coach, he need your agreement
Whatever, whatever
So, do you have appointments
for Valentine's Day?
Are you really sick?
Anything to do with you?
Whether or not
You're coming to the party
Why?
Make up enough people
You must be happy
Just let me go
Without my consent
What do you want
I never let you go
I heard you highly recommended it
Who said
The leader
I just said whatever
That's permission
Do you really want me to die
I
Rest assurd, I won't do what you want
A crazy woman
Answer me
When did I promise you
To let Bai Yongze go to the event?
Aere you trying to kill me?
Is the problem that serious?
Then you have dinner with me
On Valentine's day as an apology
The crazy woman
Should've been taken to the hospital
Brother Yong ze
Come here
Congretulation
For what
Brother Yongze
You're the hero of this event
And send flowers to girls
I'm jealous of you
Then you go
But
I just like Tianshi
Tet out
But
Are you jealous? Song Chacha
You shouldn't be jealous
It was an event
Song Chacha
You look terrible
Or, brother Yongze
How about you give the last flower
To beautiful Miss Song
And announce your relationship
Are you mad?
What's wrong with you
Think before you talk, okay?
Okay?
Are they couple?
Why can't announce?
We can, we can
Right
Yes
OK, that's settled then
On Valentine's Day
Yongze announced their relationship
Give me five!
Go
Am I something wrong?
This is a good chance
to make him jealous
Come on
I don't want to get him back like this
There is no U turn
That's too late
Why are you so worried
Of course
If you two were together
My future will be secured
Your future will be secured
So you can betray me?
Yes
What're you doing
Jiang Shi
The ring size is the 11th
By the way, mine is the 13th
Come on, come on
You see
I'll buy a ring for Tianshi
So, pick on for me
I don't get it
And not interested
Brother Yongze
Come on, please
Plase
How about this one
Are you having problem with aesthetics?
That two better
This two
this one?
I think
This one is the most beautiful
This one the iith
Brother Yongze, pay for it
Why
On Valentine's Day
You
Girls
They all like this
Jiang Shi, Jiang, you
Whether they announce it or not
They're all going according to our plan
Let the people around you
put pressure on them
Lan Tian
Did you know Yongze is going to
introduce his girfriend at the event
Really
Of course
Brother Yongze
Congratulations
What's up
Yongze
You said you'll
introduce your girlfriend
at the event, right?
She? How coule she fall
in love with Bai Yongze?
Really?
We'll know on Valentine's Day
Bitch
How could they know?
Someone's rumored about your affair
I heard
Bai Yongze will introduce his girlfriend
Really?
Looks like I'm gonna stay and see
That's what the public
is looking forward to
Li Bao, Li Bao, Are you on?
The public is looking forward to?
Reporter Xu，Let me make a story
So handsome
Bai Yongze is going to announce
his girfriend's identity
So lots of people came here
Really？
Ok
Ladies and gentleman
Good afternoon
Awwww
Why took me here
You are the protagonist
Do you want to let Bai Yongze down?
Welcome to the event of
Sweet data with Bai Yongze
Is anyone want to get a rose
From Bai Yongze?
Please come to the stage
Everybody go
Let's welcome Bai Yongze
Awww
Now
Bai Yongze will give
every girl on the stage
A rose
Thank you, thank you
I said I'm not interested
But we need support Brother Yongze
Later
He is going to announce
his girlfriend's identity
Now it's time
As the rumor goes
He is going to announce
his girlfriend's identity
On Valentine's Day
So who is she
Do you want to know?
Yeah
Are you looking forward to?
So
Let's welcome Bai Yongze
With applause
I can't talk now
Help, help me honey
What's up
What's up?
My ex-boyfriend is here
He knew I did the video thing
Li Bao
Help me
Li bao
Welcome Bai Yonge
Keep clapping
Mr, Bai Yongze, the time came
Mr.Bai Yongze?
Bai Yongze left the rose and ran
Ran?
Why?
It turns out
you got the gossip yourself
What are you talking about
Then why did he run
He's only playing at it
He doesn't like you
So he ran
Wanted to be Bai Yongze's woman
But you failed
Absolutely disgraceful
Stop making it up
Who manking it up
Absolutely disgraceful
Bitch
Watch out for thunder
What's wrong
The ring he prepared
isn't for Song Chacha?
For whom? Lan Tian
Did Yongze tell you anything?
Didn't he like SongChacha?
Did he like another woman?
Why are you so stupid?
What's wrong with me
Let me go
Chacha, maybe I'll regret it
No, I'm regreting now
But I have no choice
She lost a lot because of me
So I have to help her now
Don't pretend we don't know each other
Play lover's games with Bai Yongze
Now, you're hurting yourself
You should have known
at the beginning
What are you expect?
Song Chacha, how long did you know him
What's his merit
Li Bao, open the door, Li Bao
Are you okay?
Yong ze
When did he leave?
Before you come, half an hour ago
He threatened to kill me
You don't know how horrible
I was juet thinking about you
No message
I'll go
Just a little longer okay?
You stay here for a while
Stay with her
Okay
If he comes back
Call the police.
Thank you yesterday
He was completely convinced
Of course
I'm a professional actor
Bai Yongze and Li Bao spent
Valentine's Day together
Good job Li Bao
Turn on the TV
And paly a song
I need to relax
Why you are mediocre on TV
But good in life
Give me the remote
And clean the room
What's this
Why there is a ring
Is this Yongze's?
What's wrong with the activity?
Why are so many people checking out?
Dad, aren't you busy lately?
How do you care about
the Lan Tian's resort?
Then I care about you
How did you be the president
It's just a little bit of a problem
You know how much we loss?
If you want to do it, do it seriously
Or, go back to America
Dad, so sorry
It won't happen again
I can't trust you
Well, how is Lan Tian?
He is fine
Really?
I'd better go by myself
Yousaid
You weren't coming?
Now, there is the reason
God
If he know Dong Chacha is here
it may be end of me
Fire me? Why?
As a staff
Deliberately approach Bai Yongze
And ruined the activity
You think you'll be okay?
What are you saying?
Song Chacha ruined the activity?
In fact, it's all my responsibility
Thank you, but everything
is my responsibility
God
Bai Yongze was with Li Bao
last night
Well
His real girlfriend is Li Bao
Chacha, Song Chacha
Chacha
Sorry, it's mt fault
I thought
You and Lan Tian could
have been together earlier
I know
In fact, I'm just fine the are
I don't wanna be
self-deception
Stupid
Chacha
Well, just go in
We'll see each other, come on
Why didn't you ask me
what happened yesterday?
Met your girlfriend on Valentine's Day
That's normal
Anyway, I'm not your girlfriend
Why I ask you
What's your mean
I heart that you went find Li Bao
You should have told me
she is your girlfriend
If you told me
I won't let you to pretend my boyfriend
You're mistaken
Whatever
What's your mean
I'm a crazy woman
who haunts you now
and destroyed the activity
In a word
I was fired
You was fired?
Take aseat
Mr.Bai
I'll handle it
Okay
Yseterday's responsibility
lies with me
Why is Song Chacha responsible
Bue I heard it was her fault
It was a misunderstanding
What's your relationship?
What do you mean
I heard she is seducing you
try to get close to you
That's ridiculous
It' me
I am seducing her
Song Chacha and I are in love
I thought about to expose
that she is my girlfriend
There's no way to change
what I've decided
Whatever you say will be in vain
You can leave now
That's unfair for Song Chacha
If she goes, I’ll go
That's what you said
Okay
Do as you wish