Lan Tian
He's out?
Where can he go in the
minddle of the night?
This is......
Hey, big guy
Drinking time
What's this
Lan Tian, I'm adrift and isolated
Where are you
I never heard that he had a girlfriend
It must be fraud Email
I've received fraudulent emails before
Allow me
I'm so tired
I can't drink anymore
What the hell?
I forever am your patron god
To help you defend yourself from danger
Patron god?
Are you drunk?
You will learn it in season
Bai Yongze is Lan Tian's patron god
Are you crazy?
I was crazy
Be his patron god
It's like stabbing him from back
Damn it
If you didn't reply my email
I was going to give up
If you kept ignoring me
From beginning to end
Maybe we'll be different
Why gave me hope
Tell me what to do, Song Chacha
I gave her hope
Sorry, lamp bulb
How about Lan Tian
Yeah, I was changed
My feelings for you have changed
So you broke your promise
at the wedding
You just say it!
Afraid of me hunting you like a scoundrel?
Now, It's up to you
If you can't handle it properly
For Chacha
ther will be no way out
Lan Tian
I want to speak to you
Later
Some other time then
Anyway
You changed your mind
Yeah
I changed my mind
Changed
Where's Lan Tian
Lan Tian
He doesn't seem well today
You're not qualified to speak for him
Training is not to be absent at will
Lan Tian
Sorry
How are you
I'm fine
Then stand there
You've been overstretched
You need a break
Don't worry
Pay attention about your business
Yongze, I am disappointed
What?
I admire you so much
But you only care about him
I'm so disappointed
Lan Tian
Why am I here
You fainted on the ground
Doctor, is he just overtired?
Yes, he is not sleeping poorly
Depression
And muscles overwork
Just a massage
And cupping, He'll be fine.
Okay, thank you doctor
Well
Hold on, hold on
Are you crying?
Easy, he is still alive
Welcome, Mr Lan
So many people
I'm not used to
shch a grand way
Don't curtsy
Everybody
what is the matter?
It seems I am not welcome by someone
He had a good relatongship
with the last president
So he must be unhappy
Then you go with him
as you had a good relationship, right?
You just keep an eye on Lan Tian
To see if he really
cuts down the relationship with Song Chacha
What if Lan Tian
didn't disconnect
Cancer cells need to be eradicated
Even my kids
I'll make a cancer cell
Then,
You have resort
and I have the group Lan
Not answering the phone,
didn't stay at home
Is he here
Hello, blond hair guy
Is this the training center?
You really have keen eyes
One glance at me
I told you I'm an athlete, sister
Sister? Who is your sister?
Where is Lan Tian
Lan Tian? He fainted
In the medical room
What?
Why?
I didn't knock him out
Why are you yelling at me?
Where is medical room
Lan Tian, how are you
Are you hurt?
Where does it hurt?
Tell me!
You frightened me to death
Where does it hurt?
Why don't you answer me?
Tell me right away
Who are you?
What are you doing?
If I told Lan Tian the mail thing
He's gonna be pissed off
How do I, how do I
Or confess to Song Chacha?
You mean
you responded to the email
I was just kidding
I'm kidding too
I'm sorry
I'm so
She is
So unreasonable
It is very likely to happen
Better write a letter
Write a letter
Mom, where are you going?
Your uncle's in prison
We can't let him suffer
Can I bear to see him so?
Even if the cost is high
We have to get a lawyer
You go find Lan Tian
Tan Tian told me
Whatever difficulties we encounter with
He will help us
And support us
Mom
He has changed a lot
You met him?
You met Lan Tian?
He, he's right here
He's right here?
You came here
For him?
Where is he?
At the resort?
You take him home now
Or I'll try to find him
No, mom
He's a bit busy recently, maybe later?
Fine
Well, then we'll stay here.
I remeber her living around here
Mom, I've gotta go now.
Goodbye
It's just like bad guy's
Bah
Fortunately, I wrote a letter to told her
Sorry
Your loan has not been approved
I came here to finish nothing
Uncle Kong?
Chacha, are you with your mother?
No, what's going on？
I went home and found her out
She is not sane
Where would she go?
Got it, I'm calling her
Okay
Mom, Where are you?
I'm bored
So come straight to Lan Tian
Talk to him
your uncle thing
So you're at the resort?
NO, no, no, mom
I'll go with you tomorrow
I have arrived
I should see him
Mom, mom!
Mom, you can't see him
Hello
I want to find Lan Tian
You just tell him I'm Chacha's mother
He knows me
What's matter
I dreamed of crows
It's a bad thing
You should think differently
Look
Last night
I dreamt that I had won the first prize
But today, I'm still
giving you a physiotherapy
Fine
But I....
I always had a bad feeling
Did she see the letter?
Did she see any letter?
Why is there no response at all?
Was she mad after reading the letter?
Do it
What?
Don't waste time, just do it
Call Lan Tian
Why? Why tell him?
Can't we settle it privately?
I'll cooperate with you
Shut up, just call him
Now
Hi
Hey, It's a fine day, isn't it?
You met my mom
I'm asking whether you met my mom?
No, I haven't
Didn't you come to me?
Hey, lamp bulb
Hey
What's wrong
Mom, where are you, mom!
Mom
Chacha
Why are you here
What're you doing
I, I'm watching flowers
Why do they grow here?
Who is he
I, I'm
He's my valet
Let's go, mom
Valet?
When you have valet?
Huh?
He is a jinx
Let's go
Lamp bulb said I'm a jinx?
Ms.Li
Hello
We'll take this scene later
Is that all right?
Let me surprise you
That's Li Bao, a superstar!
Right?
Whatever
Brother Yongze
Yongze
She's coming, she'coming
My heart flew up into my mouth
I've heard you're secret training
You want to get back to your area?
I'm working right here
Meet you, that's good
Well, you go work
Yongze
Hey everybody
This is my gossip man
In private, we appreciate each other
And have a good relationship
Really?
I don't think so
Li Bao
I heard you work here
So I came to see
Is there anything funny
It seems that something has happened
What did I miss?
Brother Yongze
When will you give me
the breaking inside story?
I've got the editor
Don't keep me dangling
I told you I'd contact you in private
What are you doing here
Encumbrance, stop playing today
Formal training
Where are you going?
What does he mean
Look
I'll refund half your money
to get him out of here
Did we swim?
What do you want
Waiting for Yongze
Fuck you!
Sister
You work too hard, please drink some water
I'm tired of it
Well, drink some water
Why is he endlessly going after that?
Who?
Welcome to Westin resort
Reporter Xu
You're too bold
What if Yongze finds out
It's you
Oh honey, what're you doing here
I sent the message
You're sneaking around with reporter Xu
It's too suspicious
When do you give me the
breaking inside story?
I've got the editor
Dong't keeping me hangling
I analyzed it
No one can get my phone
Except you
So
Want to create a gossip?
Of course not, honey
He threatened me with the affair between us
Let me give him another one
I just revealed one thing
A little
You have to be considerate
that it's not easr for a woman to fight
So I want to protect myself
I know, I'm selfish
But I didn't send him the video
Did you know
Fraud, intimidation, libel
That's enough
to get you out of the
entertainment business
Sorry honey, I was wrong honey
Don't just care about your face
please take care of your dignity
As a girl
Kneel down easily to the power
It's not appropriate, is it?
And, I'm not your honey
Don't call me that
Anyway, I have a bad temper
No patience, you know about this
I don't like your attitude
towards swimming
Too casual
Look
He and I
only keep one
You can choose
I'll warn him again
Does he have anything on you?
It looks like something happened
between you and him, right?
He has something that I don't have
So I wanna hold him
Is that okay?
Fine
But I need to remind you
You're being far-fetched
It's gonna be tiring
Well,
You know all my notion
And I need remind you
You lalways works in fits, and starts
Come whenever you want
Go whenwver you want
You think you're an athlete?
Even though
Your family own the club
You have to pay attention to
how the coach feels
Lan Tian
You, you
You, you crazy woman, why are you here
Crazy, crazy woman
Hey, how did you know him
Who's the crazy woman
You old ruffian
Are you used to living there?
You made a good arrangement
Now I'm the president
So which of us
is incharge?
I don't like administrative work
But, he sends you here
To spy on me?
How is that possible
That
Absolutely impossible
Whatever
I'm not the one
that is easily controlled
well
Give me a drink
Cheers
Have a good time
at Yajule Qingshuiwan Bay
Sister Lan Xian
I'm here
What's up
I never thought
That one day, I'll run Lan Tian's resort
Really?
Why didn't Lan Tian run it himself
My father arranged all
On the one hand, Lan Tian wanna swim
I can help him
It can also enhance my
relationship with him
On the other hand,
Maybe,
He wanna test me ability
Tha sounds good
I'm not talking to you about family
Have you met Lan Tian?
Just like what you said
My relationship with him is over
We broke up
His feelings for me
have changed
Is that not good?
You have to adjust
So that you can face it
Anytime
anywhere
a famous saying goes like that
Time changes everything
But in fact
The most important thing
Is to change yourself
Only in this way
will everything change
But now
I don't wanna see Lan Tian
Everything doesn't do what people want
Otherwise, I would have
inheriter Lan's group
Sorry, my mom is waiting for me
I've to go
Wait
You don't need money now?
This is
No
It's a loan
But I have strings attached
I want you to work at the resort
Sister Lan Xin
Relax
I'm doing this for your good
I do need money
But I would rather endure hardships
than work in the place with Lan Tian
So I told you
You have to adjust
You're being brave now
But once you go back
You'll face to the debt collertors
And your mom is vulnerable
What if she doesn't accept it
And breakdown
What should you do
Just sit down
Do you know the reason why
Lan Tian gives up swimming
It's you
He afraid to remind you
of your brother Zhihao
when he was swimming
But now, he is swimming again
It means
There's not nuch left
of his feeling for you
Maybe for survival
He's so determined to choose this path
He's willing to let go of everything
in order to survival
Even love and self-esteem
Now think about it
He's pathetic
You don't have to turn me down so soon
If you don't make up your mind in the end
You can return it back
Nobody is all smooth sailing
If anyone wants to help you
You should feel glad
Think about it
Song Chacha, you must not let me down
I'm waitting to see the play
Sorry, lamp bulb
Why do I
Always do stupid things?
Mail and video
I screwed up
Mr.Bai
Here is your message
What message
Come on, eat more
Otherwise, It's wasteful
Am I a trash can?
Eat everything?
Sorry
For what?
For, the video stuff
And
What else?
The message
Well
Since you're Lan Tian's friend
I forgive you
Is it difficult to give up Lan Tian？
If I answer "Yes, it's"
Will you help me?
I'm kidding
I won't see him unless I'm crazy
I'll forget Lan Tian
Everything
Yes
You should told him
People like him
Not worth mentioning in your life
That's revenge
Anyway, before I got the e-mail
It's still a good memory
So, put these memories away
When I want to remeber
Take it out again
Well, what were you gonna say
Nothing
Keep drinking
I'm not drunk
You see, I can walk straight
Knock it off
I'll see you home
You kidnapped me
I warn you
You
Playing with fire
Threaten me?
Help
There's a pervert here
Enough, I am not a pervert
I'm freshmeat, okay?
Let's go home
Hey
Is this your house?
So you can sleep
Wake up
Hey, Song Chacha
Song Chacha
Did you send me back
Who else?
You don't know
how heavy it is to carry you
You better?
Stop joking
How coule I be drunk
Byebye
I have thought about it
I can't accept it
Sister Lan Xin
Thanks for your help
But I'not sure
If it's a good choice
You gave up a chance
Which you can prove yourself
You should ignore him
Live a good life
Let him know
You'll have a better life without him
Yajule Qingshuiwan
where to make you open-minded
here
You'll find a new beginning
Struggle rather than regret
Do I have a better way
to prove myself?
Yes, you should told him
People like him
Not worth mentioning in your life
Sometimes, forgetting an emotion
is like eliminating the
accumulation of food
You have to learn to put it down
Let's face it
If you don't get back yourself
The future will be worse
As for this
You had better think about it clearly
Sister Lan Xin, Can I change my mind?