Anyway
I can't leave like this
I am already here
It won't hurt to see him
I said it last time
I wouldn't just leave this behind
Do you know what this
woman wants to do to me?
Wait, who the hell are you?
What do you want from me?
Is it you who
made a copy of my phone?
What are you talking about?
Didn't you go through my phone
and send the video
to the journalist
I don't know what you are talking about
So, you threatened me
Right?
You crazy? I didn't do that.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
She said she didn't, she didin't
How do you know?
How you doing?
Ha~how am I dong?
You~
What do you expect?
I am fine, thank you?
Or sorry, do we know each other?
Should I just wait for you do nothing
and think about nothing
like a fool
Don't you feel guity?
Can we have a moment?
What the is going on here?
He said he didn't know who Song Chacha is
Didn't see that coming
You mentioned Lan Tian last time?
You know him?
I am asking if that asshole is with you
Lan Tian
Do you know is who Song Chacha?
You are really that Lan Tian
Lan Tian is the one who
is getting married to me
But he didin't show up.
There is a story of you
You cut our conection
when you went to America
I blamed myself for everything
I felt guilty because I
wasn't there for you
I was very upset
All I could do is to wait
What about you?
I didn't ask you to wait
What?
I fell in love with someone else
We can't go back anymore
So
So you just leave me alone in the wedding?
Why didn't you just tell me?
You are afraid I won't walk away?
Wedding? What wedding?
There is no need for this
conversation to go on
I am asking you, what wedding?
You reallly don't know
or you are pretending?
Such a great actor
Didn't you have your
father prepare our wedding?
And said our promise is a promise
and you wanted to get
married to me right now?
You went to the wedding without asking me?
Are you a fool?
I didn't know that
that wedding.
Because you said,
you will show up
whatever happens
Because even how ridiculous it is
I just want to see you.
The end won't ever change any more.
Because you fall in love with someone else.
We will get married
no matter what happens.
What if we break up before that?
Even you don't love me,
I'll still love you.
You are a fucking coward
I don't love you
I just fall in love with someone else
I didn't know that that wedding.
Because you said,
you will show up
whatever happens
Because even how ridiculous it is
I just want to see you.
Why is he standing there?
You will get sick
Go inside.
Just leave me,
I have to take care of you
if you catch a cold.
I told you to leave
Where are you going?
Lan Tian.
Book me a ticket to Beijing.
Right now.
What happened, mom?
Your uncle's lawyer called
you uncle comitted a few
crimes cocerned with
tax evasion and so on.
What?
But your uncle called
he would kill himeself
if we don't get him out
He will kill himself
What should we do?
What don't perple play by the rules?
It' s annoying.
Hello, dad
Yong Ze
Have you started training officially?
Yes, of course.
You are not watching TV, right?
How is taht possible?
Have you met your coach?
What's his name?
Eh~
His name is...
He does have a name?
Oh~ dad,
I have to go to training.
I'll call you back.
I gotta go.
Yong Ze?
How does he know?
Is there a security camera here?
What do you want?
Another one, illegal gambling.
Dad
Fine
If you don't do
what I say,
Cha Cha might be in desperate situation.
What? Are you ganna ask me
how could I get that wedding done?
I am telling you, if I don't do that,
you will be cheating on me.
And just like you went to see
Song Chacha behind my back.
I am warning you.
Don't mess up with her
since I agreed you to swim.
I prpmised you that before
We can't and
we are not together.
Then,
make a stand.
I am your son.
You gotta believe me.
Sometimes I don't even believe myself.
That's your business.
Wait
Lan Xin.
I will arrange you a position.
Position?
Not in here.
You go to Lan Tian's resort
to help him manage it.
What?
Why?
Because you broke my rules.
I agreed you to swim
on condition that
you can't meet Song Chacha.
Now you met her,
and broke my rules
You have to be punished.
I don't want to get involved
in your business.
But if you don't want to manage it,
I will have someone do that.
Isn't that good?
That's good,
Thanks, dad.
You are my god of wealth!
What is this guy doing?
He didn't answer my phone.
Hello, Oh, Dad
Yong Ze
No beer at night
Just relaxed, I am sober now.
That does no good to your bady.
Undestand?
Yes, yes, understand.
Ok OK OK
Don't stay up late, dad.
En.
My gosh.
Did he place a security camera here
You went to the wedding without asking me?
Are you a fool?
I didn't know that
that wedding
Because you said,
you will show up
whatever happens
Because even how ridiculous it is
I just want to see you.
Is that Fang Jingjing? That
winner of Olympic Games
What's she doing here?
She came to replace our coach
Such great news
It's said that she just
graduated from America and
she's doing research in university.
Guan Jie,
I find you well informed
Of course
I only focus on sports news every day.
You only cares acout eating.
Hello, I am Fang Jingjing.
Yes, Coach Fang Jingjing.
Thanks to Lan Tian.
We have her be our mentor
Let's welcome her.
Today, I'd like to give you a simple test.
Just relax and fill it.
And then,
I am gonna run some
brain wave test.
Please cooperate.
After all these things,
we will star our training.
Where is Lan Tian?
I called him. He said he
was busy with something.
Bai Yongze, do you remember me?
I don't forget
You don't have personal
relationship, don't you?
Go away.
Good, thanks for your cooperation.
I will let you know when I get results.
So, see you
Thank you, Miss Fang
See you next time.
Bye.
Enough
She is here to work
Not like you, just wasting time.
Coach Huang, can we start training?
What's the hurry?
You want everybody to
know you are workaholic
cumbersome
You still play by yourself today.
Get ready, rest of you
Jiang Shi, attention
Guan Jie, what are you doing? Come on
what are you doing, cumbersome?
Zombie? Floating on the water?
Come on
What should I do?
Take two more days off.
I have owed too many favors in my life.
You have to let me do something.
You just find a flat before moving out.
Don't be stubborn.
Do you still have contact with Lan Tian?
It's said you uncle's lawyer
is a acquaintance of his.
Maybe he can help.
I semm to talk too much.
I'd like to ask who
do you admire most between
you and Lan Tian?
You are everywhere!
Shut up.
I just asked and confirm it.
After all,
I don't want to
share my idol with too many people.
Because I am super possessive
I will kill you
I am crazy.
There is a video that can
prove your relationship
between you Lan Tian.
So you aren't interested in women at all
right?
What are you doing?'
If that video
comes out.
People will misunderstand us.
Who did this to me?
Only Song Chacha touched my phone
But what does she want?
OK, keep it that way.
That's right,
Yes
Yes,
Perfect.
Thanks everyone.
Thank you.
It takes a few hours to finish this.
Pull off
every announcement of this magazine.
Understand?
I mean, there is no others.
Since you mentioned, there were more
announcements when your rumors flew
And a lot of reporter
wanted to interview you.
Now..
Hey, gossip girl.
I did a exclusive interview
of Bai Yongze two days ago.
Now you know that he is in Hainan.
How would I know?
Rumor is rumor.
What is going on between you?
Why did I heard that he
had another girlfriend in Hainan.
Another one?
The only thing I am sure about
is they have a ambiguous relationship
When do you give me
the video of Bai Yongze and Lan Tian
that you show me?
I 'll be in touch.
Fine, in this world
a friend in need is a friend indeed.
I'll wait for your call.
Come on, drink some water.
Is this Bai Yongze？
He is famous agan.
And the editor say there is
a shotting of bikini in Qingdao
I pull it off
I am going to kill you right now.
You told me to do that!
Hello, I will take that bikini shotting
But, not in Qingdao
Let's change a place.
You reallly don't know
or you are pretending?
Such a great actor
Didn't you have your
father prepare our wedding?
And said our promise is a promise
and you wanted to get
married to me right now?
You went to the wedding without asking me?
Are you a fool?
I didn't know that
that wedding.
Really?
You fall in love with someone else?
But you still can help
That bulb again?
It's said you uncle's lawyer
is a acquaintance of his.
Maybe he can help.
What's she doing?
I am just crazy.
She looks so suspicious
I can't trouble uncle Kong too much
I gotta make more money.
Hello, I am Song Chacha
That one called you last time.
It's still the thing that
we talked about. That video?
I can send it to you right now.
But can you give me more money?
I am in a difficult situation.
OK, yes
I am sending it right now.
Because of money, right?
What?
Don't be innocent
I heard everything.
I don't know what you are talking about.
Let go of me.
I told you to let go.
Hey,
You, you ok?
Hello,
Hello, Bai Yongze
Hey, wake up.
Wake up, Bai Yongze
Is he ok?
We will see after doc checks him.
Damn it, what's Cha Cha's number?
Hello, who is it?
Cha Cha!
This is Lan Tian.
Where are you?
Which hospital?
Why am I here?
And why are you holding
my hands?
What do you want?
You are crazy.
This is hospital
And you won't let go of my hands.
Nothing good happen when I meet you.
I did this in case you run away.
Tell me,
Are you up to something?
You want to threaten me？
That's enough
You could be dead by now
if it weren't for me.
You like curing people, don't you?
What did I do
in my last life?
Where are you going?
What the hell do you want?
At leat wait until
we solve all problems.
If you beg for my forgiveness on you knees,
I maybe merciful to
forgive you this time.
Are you being delusional?
I don't know what video
you are talking about.
But mine, has
noyhing to do with you.
If don't,
Prove it.
What? You can't?
Or you won't?
What if I am right?
I will be your little brother
or your sidekick.
You are kidding me?
Hey, you
Why are you together?
Eh~lt's complicated.
Why now?
Bad luck!
Let's talk.
I have nothing to talk about.
Even I feel I shouldn't mind your business
If you didin't reply me with that e-mail,
when my father died,
I was gonna give up
If you could remain silent,
maybe wouldn't be like this.
So why did you give me hope?
What? Your father died?
You don't have bottom line, right?
How could your father? When?
How do you explain that e-mail?
What e-mail?
Maybe, you just don't care?
I won't ask you to remember
all of our memories.
I just want some respect.
Suddenly, I don't fell pathetic.
I just met my
rock bottom.
But you,
you are at the rock bttom your whole life.
You are much worse than
the Lan Tian I know.
Mr.Bai, you are wanted bydoctor.
Have a seat, please.
How do you fell? Better?
Much better.
According to results,
you are fine.
Then why do I feel chest tight
,flustered and fatigue
and angina.
Because being pressed and
mentally nervous can result in this.
Yes, it's pressure.
It's pressure
I suddenly stop
when I am runningfast.
I am not superman.
Of course I fell pressed.
It's all because I met that bulb
when I am in a desperate situation.
I promise to be your guardian angel.
Along with your brother.
Why did you say you don't know who she is?
Because I erased her from my memory.
You did?
Cha Cha, this is Lan Tian.
OK.
I thought I did.
At least there is some trace.
Yes, there was a time
when we were, just like,
meant to be.
That dramatic?
But you know what?
A lot of things are gone,
it's never going back.
Everything is like dust,
wind comes, it's all gone
Bullshit.
Dad
It can't be me, I didn't write this.
Lan Tian
I seemed to hear
he went out.
It's midnight
What's this?