VAV STUDIO .:. VIETTORRENT.VN
www.facebook.com/VAV.AudioViet
VAV STUDIO
© Copyright 2013, All rights reserved
IRIS 2
Final Episode
Yoo Gun.
There will be no end to
a revenge such as this.
I would like... this to be the end.
As you said, your excessive greed
to possess nuclear weapons...
has blurred your judgment.
I never said this remote
control switch...
was for detonating the nuclear bomb.
You...
Did you think my target
was Yoo Joong Won?
Baek San.
Father!
Thank you... Yoo Gun.
No!
Father!
- No.
- Get out of my way.
- You need to shoot me first.
- Get out of my way!
That's enough!
Do you think there will be
an end to this killing game?
Someday, this woman will
put you in danger.
- Stop it.
- Captain!
Park Tae Hee!
Secure the nuclear weapon.
We're leaving.
Move.
Yun Hwa.
Listen to me now.
You and I...
have chosen different paths.
Seeing you get hurt or die...
isn't what I want to see.
Don't...
Don't ever show up in front
of me again.
Are you really going to let
Jung Yoo Gun and Kim Yun Hwa go?
We're fine, as long as we have
this nuclear weapon.
What happened to the detonator?
It's ready.
Good.
Wait.
It's me.
Yoo Joong Won took the
nuclear weapon and disappeared.
What's the location?
The signal from the tracer died.
I need help from the situation room.
What should we do first?
I need the CCTV records from
where I was just a moment ago.
Tell me the location.
I'll send you the map file.
Yoo Joong Won took
the missing nuclear weapon.
What's the source of that information?
Was it from Jung Yoo Gun?
Yes, more importantly...
Yoo Joong Won intends to use the
nuclear weapon immediately here in Seoul.
What are you talking about?
On what grounds do you make
such a certain statement?
His goal isn't to the use nuclear weapon
in order to control us as the North did.
He intends to start a war
by detonating a nuclear bomb.
What about the location tracer
Jung Yoo Gun has?
Yoo Joong Won must have
found it and disabled it.
Things are getting worse and worse.
No matter what you have to do,
capture Yoo Joong Won.
Have the operation and
EOD teams on standby.
Okay.
There's a truck that left from
this location about 15 minutes ago.
Please follow that truck.
I'll go through all the
highways that lead into Seoul first.
Since they don't have the location
tracer, it might take some time...
but eventually, they'll find us.
Lee Hyuk Soo.
- Are you prepared for this?
- Yes.
I found them.
Where is it?
This image was taken a few minutes ago
just beyond the Seoul city limit.
Continue to follow their movement.
I'm going out there with the operation team.
Be careful.
Yeah, Soo Yun.
We found him.
[Seoul Interchange]
- Are you all ready?
- Yes.
Let's go.
They'll be coming out of the tunnel
about 200 meters ahead.
You wait here.
Don't shoot the back of the truck
since the nuclear weapon is inside.
Yes, understood.
Cease fire.
Only fire aimed shots at the culprits.
They are using the nuclear weapon
as their shield.
Are you okay?
I can handle it.
What's going on?
Joong Won.
- It worked.
- Good work.
Hurry up and get out of there.
But I think...
Lee Hyuk Soo.
They must have switched
the truck at some point.
Are you okay?
It was what he wanted.
This heroic death for
the unification is...
not something we should
be sad about.
I'm sure he left smiling.
Okay, let's stop cleaning now.
Do you have the result from your test?
Based on the radiation exposure
level detected from the bodies...
it's definite that the nuclear weapon
was in the truck and moved later on.
Didn't you say you found evidence
of an explosion at the IRIS clubhouse?
Yes, that is... you know...
What is it?
Yeah, well... there were two
deaths due to that explosion.
And the one of them is... Baek San.
And the other is Anthony Choi.
Are you sure... that it's Baek San?
It's a 99% match.
Then, this confirms Anthony Choi
was Mr. Black from IRIS.
Since he's dead, Yoo Joong Won took
the nuclear weapon and disappeared.
Did you say I betrayed my country?
I've never betrayed my country.
It's just that...
the futures you and I envisioned for our
country happened to be different.
Everything is ready now.
Then did we lose
Yoo Joong Won for good?
We're continuing to search for him.
A nuclear bomb is about to go
off somewhere in Seoul
but we don't even have
a clue as to where they are.
Why don't we send out a bomb sniffing dog
and increase the search and inspection?
That could create a lot of
chaos and confusion among people.
Find ways to minimize the
target search and inspection area.
I understand.
Some degree of guessing
is possible here.
The reason why Yoo Joong Won wants to
detonate a nuclear bomb in Seoul is simple.
He wants to maximize the casualties.
According to the 1998 report from
the U.S. Department of Defense
and the NRDC report from 2004...
Seoul would likely suffer maximum casualties
if a nuclear bomb was to fall in the Yongsan area.
Everything within a 1.8 kilometer radius
of Yongsan
will instantly evaporate
in the case of a nuclear bombing.
The Department of Defense,
the U.S. and Korea Joint Chief of Staff
and the Combined Forces Command
are all located there.
Within a 4.5km radius from the origin of the
bombing, 90 percent of the casualties fall in
Gwanghwamun, Myeongdong, Seoul Station,
Yeouido and Gangnam.
In the case that Yoo Joong Won
detonates the bomb above ground
it would greatly increase the damage
from the radioactive fallout
thereby Seocho and Songpa, and satellite
cities such as Ilsan, Suwon, Boondang
would be subjected
to the nuclear damage as well.
We'll close in on the Yongsan
area for the search and inspection.
Comb the area and
find him no matter what.
Make a statement saying that spy
activity has been detected in Seoul.
Start the search and
inspection right away.
Attention.
From this moment on, you'll be following
my direction regarding Yoo Joong Won.
In addition, Team Leader Jung has just been
pardoned by the authority of the president.
We'll be officially asking
for Team Leader Jung's support.
So communicate this to the
field agents as well.
Agent Kang Byung Jin will also
be freed from his confinement.
Bring him back to the situation room.
Okay.
Team Leader Yoo, please filter and
screen all the calls from the Yongsan area.
Okay.
Hyun Woo, dispatch the Radiation
Detection Team (RDT) to the Yongsan area.
Also request for a press conference.
- Let's try to minimize the margin of error.
- Okay.
[Renovation in Progress]
You can't come in here.
Open the entrance door.
Disconnect all the communication lines
to the outside.
Lock the entrance door again.
There are only five construction
workers and two security guards.
Fine.
- Gi Joon.
- Yes.
Place guards at each entrance and have
them report back every 10 minutes.
Yes.
- Park Tae Hee.
- Yes.
Set up the detonator.
Yes.
What's the situation now?
Currently, the search radius is
over four kilometers.
There is a high population and
building density in the area.
First, we need to think about
Yoo Joong Won's psychology.
There is no particular place that he
would hold a personal grudge against.
They're targets if they're national sites.
The Presidential House and
the U.S. Embassy.
We've been searching Yongsan
as the priority.
I'll check the Yongsan area so ask the RDT to
search the area around the U.S. Embassy.
Okay.
It's ready now.
The U.S. Embassy has been routinely
checking for radioactivity on their own.
No dangerous level of radioactivity
has been detected there so far.
Just in case, increase the number
of the police force.
Yes.
The simulation results for the U.S. Embassy and
the U.S. Consulate as nuclear targets came out.
Okay.
Increase the search force at the connection
route between Gangnam and Yongsan.
Why?
He started this whole thing thinking
that he's doing this for his country.
Rather than picking
a place personal to him...
he'd likely choose a place where
he could hit South Korea
symbolically and effectively.
What are you talking about?
I heard Mr. Black is dead.
Without IRIS's help, unification
is not going to come that easy.
If I detonate a nuclear bomb in Seoul...
If making Seoul into a sea of fire with a
nuclear bomb was enough to achieve unification
we'd have used the missiles
a long time ago.
We have 1.2 million liberation
soldiers of the Republic.
This is the time to act
and show what we've got.
How long are you going to continue this
psychological warfare of empty threats?
Captain, I'll become the signal
to the unification.
Please make a decision.
Fine. If you are that confident,
then give it a try.
Did he give his approval?
I'll definitely make this successful.
The time has come to prove our
loyalty to the Republic.
You have shown enough of your
resolve, sworn with your blood...
to die for the people.
But you are also those people.
To me... your lives are precious also.
Even if you decide to stop now...
you've done more than
enough in doing your part.
It's not too late.
If you want to return,
you should go back right now.
We'll join you in this fight
until the end!
It's been a while.
We got some intelligence regarding the
whereabouts of Yoo Joong Won.
Where is that?
South of Banpo Bridge,
the Floating Island.
If it's Banpo Bridge,
it's Yongsan's border.
Move all the operations teams
to the location
and the RDT in Yongsan should
head over to the location.
I'll get in touch with them right away.
Jung Yoo Gun.
I believed that you'd return.
We'll be leaving now.
Did you find him?
What are you going to do now?
- Are you coming with me?
- Of course.
I need to stop Joong Won.
Soon, the NSS and the police
will surround the area.
We expected that.
Then, when will you do it?
I'm sure Jung Yoo Gun is
on his way here.
He'll make a great buddy
on my way to hell.
Tae Hee, you should be in
the security room...
in case we get some
uninvited guests.
I'll kill them as soon as I see them.
Do that.
Start it now without any mistakes.
Be careful Byung Jin and Ji Hun.
Okay.
The RDT confirmed the radiation level.
The nuclear weapon is
definitely inside that building.
I don't see Team Leader Jung.
Do you think he went inside?
Probably.
Where are you going?
Take over for me out here.
I want to see what the situation is inside.
First we need to hear what
Yoo Joong Won's demands are.
I told you. Yoo Joong Won
doesn't have any demands.
When the time comes, he plans to
detonate the bomb to start a war.
Then, let's go together.
You need to be
in charge out here. Please.
Start it now.
A video file is being transmitted.
I think all the actors are
gathered now.
So then, I guess it's time to
raise the curtain.
Yoo Joong Won.
Once I push this button...
the nuclear bomb behind me
will detonate within five seconds.
You all most likely know whether
this bomb is real or not.
We're connected.
Director. This is Yoo Joong Won.
He wants to speak to the person in charge.
What's your demand?
We'll consider it, so just tell me.
Who is this am I speaking to?
Are you still alive?
I pay my sincere respect to
the tenacity of your life.
But I feel like it won't be
that easy this time.
Long time no see, Park Tae Hee.
Are you the only agent at the NSS?
Don't you think me alone is enough?
Direct all of our forces to the second islet.
Please be on standby.
Building a strong nation that won't
get controlled by other powerful nations...
That's my demand.
Can you satisfy my demand?
Do you think you'll be able to grant
that wish by using the nuclear bomb?
I am...
Yoo Joong Won from the Ministry of
the People's Armed Forces
in the Democratic People's
Republic of Korea.
In the name of the people...
we'll begin this holy war
for the unification!
Jung Yoo Gun.
Stop it.
I've been waiting for you.
Do you know what this is?
This is a heart sensor detonator.
Whether I press the button or I die...
either way, you'll all die.
The moment my heart stops,
the countdown will begin.
In our next lives,
whether we'll meet as foe...
or as friends...
I guess we'll see.
This won't make the unification happen.
A unification achieved with so many
sacrifices would be meaningless.
To those who are complacent, the reality
of unification may seem like a burden...
but to us who have been living under the
control and rejection of other nations...
this is the only way to survive.
You say you're the
representative of the people?
Don't delude yourself, Yoo Joong Won.
That's just... your pent-up anger.
Don't you get it?
My resolute step today will serve...
to recover the pride of the
people of the Republic...
and to give them hope.
That's enough, Joong Won.
Let's stop now.
Why are you here?
- Go. Go now!
- To where?
Where would I go by myself?
Let's go together.
Then I'll go.
This isn't the place for you.
Go back.
Stop nagging and go back now.
Yun Hwa.
I don't know about anyone else...
but I believe you understand me.
I know.
I used to think like you, too.
But...
I've changed my mind.
Yun Hwa.
Joong Won.
Let's not die.
If you press that button...
I'd die, too.
Why does it have to
be like that?
Let's live.
Even if it's hard...
if we do it together...
we'll be able to endure it.
Don't come near me.
I'm standing here as a soldier working for the
liberation of the people through unification!
Come to your senses.
Right now, you are about to murder
numerous innocent mothers and fathers.
You were such a good son
to your parents.
Your mother in heaven wouldn't
want to see you like this.
Joong Won.
Think about your mother...
and stop now.
Don't do it, Joong Won.
This isn't right.
Mother.
Joong Won!
Evacuate the hostages.
- Joong Won.
- Yun Hwa.
I'm sorry...
Don't die, Joong Won.
Don't cry.
Here...
You have... someone you have to....
meet... you must...
Okay.
Okay. Okay. So don't die.
Joong Won.
Don't die, Joong Won.
It fits perfectly.
Don't be sad.
Because I'm going to go
meet my mother.
Joong Won... no.
This...
It's lovely.
Joong Won.
Yoo Joong Won.
I think I do understand you.
Because I went through it, too.
But... I won't understand you today.
I'll see you soon, friend.
The countdown has begun.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I think I'll be alright.
Yoo Gun. Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
We have no way of handling this.
In a case like this...
what does the manual suggest?
Usually, we'd take the bomb to the
shooting range on an island to detonate it.
But this is a nuclear bomb.
It's me.
This is Jung Yoo Gun.
I have one last request.
Why are you trying to go yourself?
You can have the operation team
drop it in the ocean.
I'll finish it and come back.
That'll make me feel better.
Then I'm coming with you.
I'll be back soon.
Just think about what you
want for dinner tonight.
- Yoo Gun.
- Soo Yun.
I'll be back.
Team Leader.
Please be careful.
See you soon.
Get out of the helicopter.
Ready to take off.
Roger.
Take off.
Yoo Gun.
Director.
Team Leader Jung took off alone
without the helicopter pilot.
If I ever catch those who
are picking on Yoo Gun...
Bring all of them to me.
I'll kick their butts.
That's my Yoo Gun.
- What should I do?
- You look pretty.
- I'll just stay here so you go ahead.
- Will you be okay?
I'm not going to eat her.
Yoo Gun.
Why aren't you coming back?
Soo Yun.
I don't want to hear it.
Hurry up and come back.
I don't have much time, now.
You can just drop it now
and come back.
Please... please... I beg you.
Soo Yun.
You know what?
Because the person I love is you...
I was very, very happy.
Tell me that...
when you see me.
Ji Soo Yun.
I've missed you a lot.
I've loved you a lot.
Yoo Gun.
Soo Yun.
I'm going now.
Father.
I'm almost there.
Wait just a short while with mother.
I'll be there, soon.
Yun Hwa.
Sun Hwa.
Where have you been?
Do you know how much...
I've been looking for you?
I'm sorry that I came so late.
Let's go.
It's me.
I'm here again, Yoo Gun.
You didn't forget me because you're
with your mother and father, did you?
I'm going to come here
often to make sure.
Take care. I'll be back.
VAV STUDIO .:. VIETTORRENT.VN
www.facebook.com/VAV.AudioViet
© Copyright 2013, All rights reserved