VAV STUDIO .:. VIETTORRENT.VN
www.facebook.com/VAV.AudioViet
VAV STUDIO
© Copyright 2013, All rights reserved
Subtitles by DramaFever
It's an assassination.
Representative Kwon Young Choon
has disappeared.
Kidnapping
Representative Kwon Young Choon...
and killing the entire North Korean party.
This is terrorism
devised by the South Koreans!
I'll give you exactly
24 hours from now.
We don't have much time.
Where are you?
I followed the location of a cellphone
belonging to a smuggler.
- Yoo Gun.
- Put your gun down.
It's me, Soo Yun.
He didn't recognize me.
But it still doesn't change
the fact that he shot you.
If we run into him again,
I'll shoot him first.
The nuclear war in the Korean Peninsula...
Would you like to start a third world war?
Everyone knows that
your memory has returned.
Your name is Jung Yoo Gun.
The man who was captured
in the air-handling unit room CCTV...
and the man who shot you...
Was it Jung Yoo Gun?
Why the hell did you hide that fact?
Episode 11
Rie.
I told you not to get caught...
I told you to run away.
No!
It's nothing personal.
Get him out of my sight.
What're you waiting for?
Jung Yoo Gun!
Take the shot.
I'll make sure Yoo Joong Won
keeps quiet.
Until we know more,
let's keep this fact between us.
Jung Yoo Gun.
Try to remember me.
- Jung Yoo Gun.
- What're you waiting for?
- Jung Yoo Gun!
- Take the shot.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
If I didn't do this...
you'd have just let it go without
letting anyone know about it.
What good is it to confuse the Team
about an unconfirmed situation?
I'm doing this after
I've finished investigating.
This voice recorded file...
we analyzed it in detail but there was
no tampering or editing of any kind.
Jung Yoo Gun...
He's neither your subordinate
nor an NSS agent anymore.
He's now just a terrorist
and an assassin.
As you've all heard,
no matter what the reason is...
Jung Yoo Gun is now an IRIS operative
and the assassin who killed Park Chul Young.
Who knows...
what he's been doing while he was gone.
I understand Team Leader Ji
encountered IRIS operatives in Busan.
Was Jung Yoo Gun there among them?
- If you don't answer now...
- Yes.
Team Leader Jung Yoo Gun...
I saw him there.
But he didn't seem to
recognize me at all.
So what is it that you want to say?
Yoo Gun. It's me.
It's me, Soo Yun.
Don't you recognize me?
I'm saying that...
he might have lost his memory
due his gunshot wound.
Yes, that could be.
With a sudden loss of memory,
it could cause a change in personality.
- Section Chief Oh.
- Yes.
Didn't you say Jung Yoo Gun
was mostly likely dead?
Ah... well... the situation...
From this moment on,
whoever assists Jung Yoo Gun in secret...
that person will be considered a part of the
terrorist ring and be investigated.
And... Jung Yoo Gun disappeared in the
middle of the Baek San transport mission.
You're going to have to take
the responsibility for that.
Did he really shoot you?
Team Leader Jung did?
Let's talk about this later.
Later when?
If it was really Team Leader Jung
who shot Team Leader Ji...
and he's the one who killed
Park Chul Young...
this is a serious matter.
I can't believe it.
How could this be?
This isn't a matter of whether
it could or couldn't be.
Even if he was being used...
it doesn't change the fact that
he's a murderer and a terrorist.
They were using him because
he lost his memory.
He didn't recognize me at all.
It's not just anyone but
it's Team Leader Jung.
Don't talk so lightly about him.
Hey, look at this!
I'm sure you know who this is.
These are our terms.
It's simple.
Give us Baek San and
we'll hand over Jung Yoo Gun.
We pick the time and location.
If you accept our offer, IRIS will cease
all terrorist attacks on the Korean Peninsula.
But if you choose not to...
Jung Yoo Gun will be delivered
back to you in a body bag.
And we will unleash a reign of terror...
one you cannot possibly imagine.
You have one day to decide.
I'm a man of my word.
Section Chief.
When did you receive that video file?
Just a moment ago.
I tried to trace back the origin
but I failed.
Did you send it to the Deputy Director?
The Director and the Deputy Director...
I sent it to them all.
What do you think?
Do you think your friends will
give up Baek San to save you?
Perhaps they'll ignore the one
who shot their colleague?
Ji Soo Yun.
That's the name of
the person you shot.
She pursued me with you in Hungary.
She was one of your closest colleagues.
Perhaps you two were lovers?
Yesterday's friend became
today's enemy.
I wonder what will happen tomorrow.
I don't know what
you want from Baek San...
but the NSS will never
trade Baek San for me.
I don't think so either.
Unless they're stupid, why would they try
to rescue someone who's betrayed the NSS?
But it doesn't matter to me whether
they'll trade Baek San for you or not.
He remembers everything.
In that case...
we should kill him at the exchange.
Are you worried about
keeping him alive?
I've watched him for almost
a year now.
If he wants to get back at us...
I know what he's capable of.
You do not want
Jung Yoo Gun as your enemy.
My son came to visit his mother
and brought a big present.
- I'm not going to eat her.
- Bring all of them to me.
I'm going to ask you from the beginning.
I'm not going to lose those
who are precious to me anymore.
There is one thing I'm sure of.
If someone died by my hands...
that was absolutely necessary
for this country.
Show this video to Yoo Joong Won also.
If he wants to meet,
find a place for us to meet outside.
Act like we're cooperating with
them in finding Representative Kwon.
I'm sure Yoo Joong Won will be against
trading Baek San and Team Leader Jung.
The one Yoo Joong Won really
wants is probably Baek San.
I'm also against it.
Considering what happened so far...
there's no doubt Team Leader Jung was involved
in the assassination of the North Korean party.
He's a subject we need to arrest
and interrogate.
We don't want to exchange someone
as important as Baek San with him.
Wasn't the one who shot
you, Team Leader Jung?
If that's true, that means
he's our enemy now.
And he's very dangerous
as our enemy.
You'd better be careful.
But he's their hostage now.
How do you explain that?
We'll know soon enough.
You have one day to decide.
Would you be able to
connect me to Mr. Black?
There is no way to get in touch
with him from our end.
It might be possible through Japan.
Fine. I'll be waiting.
I sent the list of information
we need to get from the NSS.
I've confirmed it.
If we want to find out
what Choi Min got out of Baek San...
we may have to extract all of the
top classified information from the NSS.
Even if it takes time,
we must do it.
Also find the exact location.
Okay.
Are you sure it was
really Team Leader Jung?
I confirmed it with my own eyes.
But it appeared there was
some kind of problem.
He didn't even seem
to know who he was.
You shouldn't call a terrorist
'Team Leader Jung' now.
For a little while...
he must've had an issue
with his memory.
Team Leader Ji.
Getting worked up isn't
going to help the situation.
He kidnapped
Representative Kwon Young Choon.
And killed the entire North Korean party.
To exchange Baek San with someone
like that doesn't make any sense.
What if the North starts to fuss
again about launching a missile or...
That won't happen.
I'm speaking as the one
with full authority.
I'm all for exchanging
Baek San for Jung Yoo Gun.
I don't understand.
Assassinating your own representatives
and willing to go to war with us...
yet, you're willing to rescue
that terrorist?
We're not rescuing but...
extraditing the culprit.
We need to get him and
find out who's behind this.
Also we need to confirm whether
Representative Kwon is alive.
But we can't hand over
Baek San no matter what.
Why not?
I thought you got everything
out of Baek San already?
Bluffing... so you were
completely full of it.
Since you didn't get anything
out of Baek San...
you can't hand him over
to them, just yet.
Even if Jung Yoo Gun
comes back in a body bag.
The reason why IRIS is after Baek San.
Why is that?
Deputy Director.
As Yoo Joong Won said...
in order to make him stop launching
the missile, I tricked him a little.
Do you want to see Team Leader Jung
come back alive?
Then find out a way to rescue
Yoo Gun without giving up Baek San.
Otherwise there'll be no other
way to rescue him.
Let me see you for a second.
This is Ui Sang Chul's address
that you asked for.
You found it?
It was difficult.
His information was completely protected
as if in a witness protection program.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Did everything go okay?
- No.
Then what do we do now?
There isn't much time left.
Since they want something from us...
they won't harm Team Leader Jung
that easily, I hope.
I should be the one consoling but...
you seem much more optimistic.
It must be something very important.
Please go ahead and tell me.
We need further confirmation but...
Baek San revealed to me
what he's been hiding.
What was it?
There are five nuclear weapons which were
completed during the 4th administration.
This is no joke.
We do need to look into this further,
but he didn't seem like he was lying.
Are you saying that there are five nuclear
weapons hidden somewhere in this country?
Yes.
It appears the terrorists were
continuously attacking us...
in order to get that
information from Baek San.
Who else knows about this?
Up until this point, you, me and...
Yoo Joong Won are the
only ones who know about this.
Who are you?
By any chance...
do you live here?
Since you ask me plainly showing
that you are an investigator...
even if I do, I want to say no.
Exactly which agency are you from?
I'm Ji Soo Yun from the NSS.
Why is the NSS looking for me?
Do you recognize them?
It's been a long time.
Of course, I recognize them.
This is Yoo Sang Joon.
Is it true that Baek San
killed Yoo Sang Joon?
Where did you get this picture?
I got it from this woman
in the picture.
What about Sang Joon?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Your child's father
Yoo Sang Joon is dead.
You've done a lot of investigation.
But you put the first button in wrong.
Why are you trying to reveal this
now after all this time?
I hope you understand that
I can't tell you the details.
It's just that...
Her son, Jung Yoo Gun, disappeared...
in the midst of investigating
the secret behind his family.
Are you Yoo Gun's lover?
Please tell me.
Who killed Yoo Sang Joon?
Baek San killed this guy.
That's correct.
I told him to.
But his name isn't Yoo Sang Joon.
His name is Kim Jung Yong.
He was a CIA spy hiding in the
Central Intelligence Service.
I couldn't be sure but...
Ji Young and Baek San, they
probably think each other is dead.
Their era had shattered their fate.
A few years ago...
I wouldn't have talked about this
even if I were to get beaten to death.
There's something bad
growing inside my body.
They say I only have
several months to live.
That's why I'm telling you everything.
Who cares now.
Once I die, that'll be the end of it.
Then... who is Yoo Sang Joon?
This is him right here.
But isn't that...
Baek San?
Yoo Sang Joon changed his
identity to Baek San.
Jung Soo Min changed
her identity to Jung Ji Young.
At the time, that's what I did
for their protection.
Go tell Jung Ji Young and Baek San...
that I am sorry.
And tell that to the son also.
Jung Yoo Gun.
So he was alive.
It's good to hear that he's alive but...
I don't want to go along with
that kind of hostage exchange deal.
I feel the same way.
We don't want to
negotiate with the terrorists.
But instead...
you'll have to keep
the promise you made last time.
I informed the President about
the nuclear arms.
If we can go alone...
you promised to help me confirm
the existence of the nuclear arms.
I'll set a date soon.
I'll be waiting.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Captain, do you think
they'll agree to the exchange?
We have to make that happen.
Yes, Captain.
How is it going there?
I'm sending it simultaneously
as I'm downloading it.
It's all of the NSS's top
classified information.
If Choi Min has recorded the
information from Baek San somewhere...
it'll probably be in the
top classified file.
The duration of download is?
It'll be finished in two hours.
What about the team?
They're already on standby.
Good work.
I'll be in touch again.
The server condition seems
a little weird.
Why?
I think someone's accessing
the server from the outside.
Since when?
I'll find out.
It's already accessed the classified files.
- Notify the Team Leader.
- Got it.
What's going on?
Someone has accessed our main server.
Block the access, now.
If you do that, we can't retrieve
whatever information downloaded so far.
We can reversely infect
their file with a virus.
A reverse hacking?
It's little dangerous...
but if we want to destroy what
they have, that's the only way.
It's too dangerous.
If you fail, you know
what will happen, right?
We won't fail.
We just need five minutes.
Have you found out who he is?
Yes.
Do you still want me to...
Yes, I want you to continue to
keep this a secret.
We did it.
Okay, block the download.
The installation is complete.
Wait a minute.
- I found the location.
- Where is it?
It's the next building.
I think the hacker directly connected
to us through a cable line.
Mi Jin, send field agents to the
communication room in the next building.
Yes.
If you give us Baek San,
we hand over Jung Yoo Gun to you.
I heard it from the Deputy Director.
So IRIS indeed wants to trade
me and Jung Yoo Gun.
The Deputy Director and the NSS
are against the exchange...
but if you agree to it,
I'll try to do what I can.
Why... should I agree to it?
Because...
Then... who is Yoo Sang Joon?
This is him right here.
But isn't that...
Baek San?
Yoo Sang Joon changed
his identity to Baek San.
Jung Soo Min... changed
her identity to Jung Ji Young.
I don't want to believe it but...
it's because Jung Yoo Gun's
father is... you.
What are you... talking about?
Baek San and Yoo Sang Joon...
I know that they are the same person.
You said that Ui Sang Chul is still alive.
Did you go see him?
Yes.
Did you hear anything else
from him?
You mean about Jung Soo Min?
Is she still alive?
Yes, she's still alive.
Once everything is finished,
I'll arrange for you to meet her.
Tell me everything you heard
from Ui Sang Chul.
Then I'll agree to your deal.
But I do have a condition.
Let me plan the exchange mission.
I was like you before.
It's really strange.
You have this unusual power
to make me talk about things...
that I've never talked about
with anyone until now.
What?
Are you sure they didn't
get anything out of us?
Okay.
Ji Soo Yun.
Yes, Deputy Director.
How did you convince Baek San?
By any chance, did you offer him
a deal that I don't know about?
There is nothing like that.
If this exchange mission fails...
you and I both will be camping
out in an interrogation room.
I'll definitely make
the mission successful.
Fine. Tell Team Leader Oh about
the time and place for the exchange.
Reply to where the video
was sent from.
Start the operation as planned.
Yes, I understand.
Yoo Gun doesn't know that Baek San
and Yoo Sang Joon are the same person.
He seems to think that Baek San
is the one who killed his father.
You must have something to say to me.
Your life is also...
pretty pathetic.
It's twisted as much as it could be.
You're just like me.
No.
I'm different than you.
I didn't get used knowing
that I was being used.
I was used by you people while
my memory was compromised.
Your mind is completely intact...
and yet, you're still getting used by the
one you should be taking revenge against.
What are you talking about?
If you're talking rubbish,
I'm going to kill you.
You seem like you didn't know.
When I handed you over
to Park Chul Young...
someone tried to kill you.
I wonder who ordered to
have you killed?
I'm sure it was Rey.
We met because we needed each other.
And will use each other
as long as we need one another.
That's good that you knew.
But it's a little odd.
You joined IRIS in order to take
revenge against the North Korean military.
But now...
you've allied yourself with the North Korean
military hard-liners involved in terrorism.
Kim Yun Hwa.
I wonder what made you
change your mind?
Keep your mouth shut.
Don't you remember why
I joined IRIS?
Yeah, and you got your
revenge in Hungary.
It's not over.
It's only the beginning.
There is nothing I can do.
It's Mr. Black's orders.
I don't care.
Calm down.
The NSS has decided
to trade Baek San for you.
You must be wondering...
why do we want him so bad?
Why go through all the trouble?
Well, since you'll be dead soon...
I'll let you in on a little secret.
Hidden beneath Seoul are
five nuclear weapons.
And Baek San is the one
who hid them.
And once we get a hold of them...
we're going to detonate one
in Pyongyang.
And the other one...
Seoul.
Hey, Rey.
Listen to me.
You cannot do it because...
I'm going to kill you with
my own hands.
We'll see about that.
Two here and the
two additional snipers there.
Below the point, we'll have two
special scuba divers on standby.
As soon as we exchange Baek San
with Team Leader Jung...
Baek San will immediately
jump into the ocean.
At the same time, the snipers and
the operation team will start the shooting.
We'll then begin arresting the culprits.
After Baek San jumps into the ocean?
The scuba divers on standby underwater
will assist him to point X.
The mission plan doesn't
sound so bad but...
I heard Baek San devised the plan.
Yes.
I'm against it.
We still don't know what
Baek San has in store for us.
If the mission fails,
who's going to take the responsibility?
I will.
Everyone in this room probably knows
Baek San has no intention of rejoining IRIS.
If he did, he wouldn't have
surrendered to us in the first place.
I'm certain that he still wants
to be under our protection.
Since you are so confident...
we'll trust you this time.
But if the mission goes wrong...
you'll definitely have to
bear the consequences.
Have Yoo Joong Won
come to the exchange as well.
So that he can't say anything later.
Understood.
You're still up.
I can't sleep.
How about some wine?
You read my mind.
I'm sorry, Rey.
I was being too sensitive.
It's okay.
It happens.
When I handed you over to
Park Chul Young in Hungary...
someone tried to kill you.
I wonder who ordered to
have you killed?
You won't hear anything from me.
And...
those who ally with the
People's Republic are all my enemies.
Are you crazy?
What the hell are you doing?
Rey! Rey!
Sir! Are you okay, Sir?
- Don't let her get away.
- Yes, sir.
Get ready.
Yes, Sir.
Captain Yoo Joong Won has
arrived at the guest point.
SP1 ready.
At 11:23 am,
the sniper set up was complete.
The target will approach from 11 o'clock.
What about the rescue divers?
After inspecting for
any underwater hazards...
they've been on standby
for about an hour.
Okay.
Are you ready?
The question is...
are you ready?
We'll make the exchange at
12 o'clock sharp.
It's 30 seconds before 12.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Were you able to find a trace
of Baek San?
I'm sorry. We'll try to
find him as soon as possible.
When did your memory return?
Was it before or after you shot Soo Yun?
Thank you for coming back.
The Chairman of the National
Defense Commission has
ordered our immediate
return to the Republic.
We have to rush our operation.
Find out more about this woman.
We're discovered.
What the hell is your deal?
I'm going to kill whoever allies
with the North Korean hard-liners.
Let's take revenge together.
Yoo Joong Won and
IRIS have another plan.
We'll need to find Baek San
as soon as possible.
If Yoo Joong Won finds Baek San
before us...
something unimaginable could happen.
Mr. Black will try to form a
new group of operatives.
Help me get in touch with him.
Move in the shadows and find
Baek San and Yoo Joong Won.
VAV STUDIO .:. VIETTORRENT.VN
www.facebook.com/VAV.AudioViet
© Copyright 2013, All rights reserved