VAV STUDIO .:. VIETTORRENT.VN
www.facebook.com/VAV.AudioViet
VAV STUDIO
© Copyright 2013, All rights reserved
IRIS 2
Baek San is still inside.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Where is it?
Because one of the nuclear weapons
is still in his possession...
Because he's your father.
Isn't that why you're trying
to rescue him?
My wish is to maintain the denuclearization
of the Korean Peninsula forever.
Of course.
If you're willing to trust me...
I'll try to help.
I don't trust you.
If you ever fall out of Captain's favor,
you are a dead meat.
Kim Yun Hwa has been secretly
communicating with Jung Yoo Gun.
Jung Yoo Gun.
People like you and I aren't
meant to live long.
Let's settle this today.
Jung Yoo Gun will do anything
in order to catch Yoo Joong Won.
Where is he now?
Please stop it now.
You'll have to witness your loved ones
getting hurt and dying because of you.
Even with your own death...
you won't be able to atone
for the sins you've committed.
Episode 18
How are you feeling?
You passed out
as soon as you came in.
You were out for...
about 20 hours.
By any chance... is Joong Won...
Yoo Joong Won and Park Tae Hee
showed up later.
And unfortunately, they're still alive.
- Was there a call for me?
- Not just one.
Your phone was ringing every ten minutes.
It's not like I could answer or anything.
[Choi Min]
Thank you so much
for coming in person.
I'm Goo Gong Gil
the Presidential Chief of Staff.
I'm Anthony Choi.
We'll escort you from here.
I wonder whether it was the right decision
to choose a multinational corporation like Jeron?
It ranks top three in the world
in the defense industry.
The company seems
very clean on paper also.
Still... its headquarters are in the U.S.
They might see through our intentions.
I'm concerned that the U.S. government
might find out about our nuclear weapons.
That's not likely.
However, even if they figure
out our intention...
luckily, Anthony Choi,
the CEO of Jeron is Korean-American.
That's also the reason we chose Jeron
over the first and second ranked corporations.
Do you think it'll be okay?
He's arrived.
Please have him come in.
Nice to meet you.
It's an honor to meet you.
I'm Anthony Choi.
How may I help you?
Alone? You weren't hurt?
Yes, I'm fine.
How is Soo Yun?
She was discharged from
the hospital and returned to work.
Actually, Seo Hyun Woo
has been injured more.
Hyun Woo was?
Yoon Shi Hyuk has been
confirmed as the spy.
During the transport, he disappeared after
causing six casualties including Seo Hyun Woo.
How is Hyun Woo doing?
He received a gunshot wound
on his abdomen
but the surgery went well
and he's recovering now.
Team Leader Jung.
I need to talk to you in person.
I'll text you the location and the time.
The nuclear bomb that fell on Hiroshima
68 years ago killed about 200,000 people.
The nuclear bomb detonated
in Hiroshima was in the 16 kiloton class.
In order to help your understanding...
one kiloton equals the explosive
power of 1000 ton of TNT.
In other words, you can say about 16,000 ton
of TNT exploded all at once in Hiroshima.
Then after 68 years, I'm sure
the technology has advanced quite a bit.
What's the scale of it now?
Hypothetically, if a one megaton level
strategic nuclear warhead...
were detonated in Seoul, about
10 to 12 million people would be killed.
We approximate about 80 to 90 percent
of the buildings would be destroyed.
Indeed... it really is an incredible scale.
In Seoul's case...
because of the city's high population density
and many high-rise buildings...
the damage can be great.
You can't even compare this
to Hiroshima.
If you compare it that way,
you may think so but...
if the nuclear bomb dropped in
Hiroshima were denoted in Seoul now...
there would be more than one to
1.3 million people killed.
The nuclear bombs have
rather simple structures.
Even after 30 years, if the
detonator functions correctly...
the bomb could be used at any time.
Is that right?
But Mr. President...
To me, it sounds like you already have...
30 year old nuclear
warheads in your possession.
No. Where would we get a hold of
something like that all of a sudden?
If you consider Korea's latent
potential in nuclear technology...
you'd be able to produce
a warhead in just a few months.
Rather than relying on the assistance
of the allies in denuclearization...
I'd like for us to pursue becoming
a nuclear nation someday.
Why do you want that?
Ever since the North has announced
their nuclear program in 2005...
they've been making all kind of threats to
coerce us into giving them economic aid.
The four or six party talks
were all but an excuse.
Ultimately, their goal was
money and economic support.
Therefore, rather than relying on the allies
for the defense of this country...
I'd like to establish an independent
defense structure
so that a normal diplomacy can be carried
out between the North and the South.
Ironically, most South Koreans have become
insensitive to the status of their security...
due to the North's frequent
rhetorics and false threats.
If a cornered North Korea
indeed detonates a bomb in Seoul...
even if we win the war,
what could that victory mean to us?
Would you be able to help revive our halted
nuclear program for the good of this country?
This is a very sensitive internal matter.
Please give me some time to
think about it.
I hope you don't think
that you're under pressure.
Stop the car.
This is Yoo Joong Won.
I'm not sure how many,
but I think it's true that
Baek San handed over nuclear weapons
to the South Korean government.
Then, there's no way to secure the
nuclear weapons anymore?
Leave that up to me and
regroup your team for now.
We are short on weapons and operatives.
We've been discovered, so
we also need a new hideout.
I text you the location to meet.
I'll talk to you there.
Have you come to South Korea?
Is there something wrong?
Mr. Black is in South Korea.
We need to join him for now.
Captain. Do we have to...
Park Tae Hee.
Head that way.
You heard everything from Phillip, right?
I did, but I still can't believe it.
Did you really acquire four
nuclear weapons just overnight?
The President intends to use those weapons
to try to make us into a nuclear nation.
For the future of South Korea,
I need to stop that.
Will you be okay?
Yes, I've made up my mind.
Okay, then.
What would like to order?
What kind of alcohol do you want?
Alcohol?
I'm all set.
Man... just for something like that.
We'd like a bottle of soju and
just give us some appetizers.
Yes.
You can drink?
I'm not like how I used to be,
but I can still hold my liquor.
Soju, it's been such a long time.
Here.
What are you doing?
You don't know anything.
Soju taste much better like this.
That's enough.
Cheers.
What are you laughing at?
You think I'm funny?
Yeah, you are.
Soju is good because it doesn't
give you a bad hangover.
Do you know why I like soju?
How would I know that?
Because it doesn't give
you a hangover.
When I go outside all dressed up...
ten people will pass me.
When I look back...
I see 15 people looking at me.
I'm like, that kind of woman.
Oh, yeah... is that right?
I've never met anyone who boasts about
holding their liquor that actually can.
- Hey, waiter.
- Yes.
Did you add water into this soju?
Water?
Oh, no way.
Then why is it so bland?
I'm not getting drunk.
Sir, I think your girlfriend
has had enough for the night.
Who are you calling drunk?
Bring me a new bottle.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Ah, okay. Thank you.
What a strange guy.
I was just starting to feel it.
That's enough.
You know...
Mr. Jung Yoo Gun.
Do you hate Joong Won that much?
What do you want to say?
Do you have to kill him
to get your mother's revenge?
Then Joong Won and I...
Who should we take our revenge on?
It's not like I can kill all the
North Korean military hard-liners.
Joong Won was a really good son
to his mother.
Do you know how much he
chased me around?
Do you really have to kill him?
If Joong Won dies...
I'm going to be... a widow.
You successfully escaped the NSS.
What happened to your leg?
You may use any rooms on
the first floor.
What about Mr. Black?
We're going to have to
get along for the time being.
Let's not waste our time
on useless quarrels.
You're here.
Why did you want to see me?
You said you met with Baek San.
Can you tell me where Baek San is now?
Now is not a good time.
The last of the nuclear weapons
Baek San has...
if we don't take care of it soon, innocent
people may have to pay a big price.
He probably won't use it like that.
Then where does he intend to use it?
He intends to use it
as bait to capture Mr. Black.
I want to... believe what he said.
Mr. President and Director Kang think we
should arm ourselves with nuclear weapons.
Do you also feel that way?
I'm not sure.
Under normal circumstances, I would have
agreed with the denuclearization.
But at a time when the North is unwilling
to give up their nuclear program...
I have to wonder if insisting on
denuclearization on our own, has any meaning.
You'll see that nuclear weapons will turn
the earth's clock back to the Stone Age.
So I'm going to hand over those
four nuclear weapons...
So what I mean is,
Yoo Joong Won nor IRIS
should never get a hold of the last
remaining nuclear weapons.
I understand.
That's the reason...
that I'm still alive.
- Can I ride it?
- Of course.
What is it this time?
This is the hard drive that
Baek San used to use at the NSS.
Let me know what's in this hard drive.
You can only get the content through
to the NSS's main server.
Ever since Director Kang returned,
things have been a little different at the NSS.
You are treated like Yoo Joong Won
as far as the priority on the wanted list goes.
I won't be putting you in
an awkward spot after this.
I'm sorry about everything.
And...
Damn!
Don't even think about
doing anything funny.
We'll no longer treat you
as the former A Team leader.
Director Kang Chul Hwan has given
permission to use firearms.
I know you were very close
to Representative Kwon.
The unification of the North
and the South...
Please help us out.
The unification will happen
without you worrying about it.
Let me finish up that plan.
How are you going to do that?
Soon, I'll be able to secure
a nuclear bomb.
As soon as I have the bomb...
I'll detonate it at the Gwanghwamun
in front of the U.S. Embassy in Seoul.
At the same time, you should march
south to occupy major footholds.
Captain Yoo Joong Won...
can I trust you on this?
The unification of the North
and the South...
is like my life.
Then try it. But...
we'll be following the timeline
according to our unification plan.
So you'd better hurry.
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
It's been a long time.
It's been three years
since I saw you last.
It's been that long already?
What about Yoo Joong Won?
He's been waiting for you.
Tell him to come and
have a cup of coffee.
Have a seat.
I'm just coming back from
the Presidential House now.
It might be easy to get
nuclear weapons in our hands.
Are you sure?
Do you know where...
I intend to use those
nuclear weapons?
Aren't you planning a full-scale war?
No matter which side wins,
with all the war munitions...
you'd leave an astronomical
figure in profit.
If your country wins...
I'll be able to get all the
uranium mines in the North as well.
Of course.
If we could only secure one nuclear
weapon... how would you use it?
Of course, I'd detonate it
in the South's capital Seoul.
With that as a start, the army of
the Republic will march down south.
A signal to a unification war.
If the plan becomes successful...
your country will have to elect a
new leader for the unified Korea.
That's the blueprint I've been drafting
with IRIS's headquarters.
When that happens...
I can make you a pretty high position.
I'll definitely make it successful.
Captain.
Did it not go well with Mr. Black?
Does it matter whether
it went well or not?
We are together to prey on
each other anyway.
As you said, someday we'll
end up getting eaten by them.
Captain.
Don't try to make a big deal out
of what's been decided already.
- I do have plans.
- This might put you in danger.
I'm doing this risking my life.
If I were afraid of losing my life,
that means I'm not doing my job right.
I'll be back soon.
Your wound hasn't healed, yet.
It'd be too much.
It'd be nice to sit and wait but...
unfortunately,
time is not on our side.
I'll escort you.
No, I'm just going to look at
the place and come back.
Don't follow me.
Team Leader Ji.
The thing is...
Byung Jin went outside and was
brought back in by Internal Affairs.
Internal Affairs?
I don't know the details, but it was
an order from Section Chief Hwang.
Did you confirm it with
your own eyes?
- Yes.
- And this...
What's this?
It's agent Kang Byung Jin's belonging.
I think he received it from
Jung Yoo Gun.
Good work.
You can go now.
I was going to call for you anyway.
What's going on with
agent Kang Byung Jin?
Kang Byung Jin was discovered
helping Jung Yoo Gun.
He's currently in our custody.
Team Leader Jung?
Jung Yoo Gun...
is neither a Team Leader
nor an NSS agent anymore.
He's just a criminal we need to capture.
Do you have anything more to say?
I'll interrogate agent Kang Byung Jin.
Okay. You can go.
[Ji Soo Yun]
If you heard from him,
you should have let me know first.
Then things wouldn't
have turned out this way.
He made me swear
not to tell you about him.
Team Leader Jung did?
I think he was doing that
because he was worried about you.
He knew you were kidnapped
by Yoo Joong Won.
I told him you're fine and unharmed.
Did he say anything else?
About Baek San or
the nuclear weapons?
What is it?
He mentioned something, saying that
he couldn't judge the situation.
He asked me to follow
Deputy Director Choi Min's movements.
Deputy Director? Why?
I'm not sure.
We'll soon be receiving an order
from the Presidential House.
You want us to move all
the nuclear weapons to the K6...
you mean to Camp Humphrey?
Yes.
If you want to keep the promised
timeline, you'd better hurry.
Yes.
[Agency for Defense Development]
Tune into the frequency
I told you earlier.
We're leaving, now.
I have something I need
to report to you, Director.
Oh, what is it?
Deputy Director is moving the four
nuclear weapons to a different location.
- What?
- A different location?
I just finished talking to
the Agency for Defense Development.
They confirmed that she just left.
- With all four of them?
- Yes.
I'm in charge of those nuclear weapons.
Without my permission,
where is she moving them to?
To Camp Humphrey.
Deputy Director intends to...
hand them over to the U.S. Army.
Mobilize a unit to stop her now!
Recover those weapons to
the original location.
As soon as you find her, arrest
her and bring her back here.
From this moment on,
Choi Min is relieved of her position.
- Go now!
- Yes.
Director...
What are you doing?
That's what I should be asking you.
This is not a situation
you should get involved in.
No, it doesn't matter how those
nuclear weapons are going to be used.
But my job is to stop the unauthorized
transport of those nuclear weapons.
You've gone too far, Deputy Director.
Possessing nuclear weapons
without the approval from the allies
means breaking our alliance
with the U.S..
Are you a Korean or an American?
I'm neither a Korean nor
an American at this moment.
I'm only a person who wants to prevent
a disaster that's imminent to our future.
How long do you want to rely on
the allies for our national security?
Once we become a nuclear nation...
we don't have to play
the North's stupid games.
Do you really think
the best way to prevent a war
is to arm ourselves with nuclear weapons?
Whether it's for the best or not...
that's not for you to decide.
You tried to hand over these weapons
without the President's authorization
to another country's military unit.
From this moment on,
you've become a traitor forever.
Yes.
This is Ha Seung Jin.
I had no idea you'd act so recklessly
without talking to me about it at all.
Mr. President. You may
regret this moment forever.
It was a decision made as the head
of the state after giving it much thought.
I won't hold you accountable
for anything.
But you'd better return to the Pentagon.
Put the gun down.
The trucks will return to
the Agency for Defense Development.
Please go back.
I'll escort you back.
Wait for me outside.
I'm sorry, Deputy Director.
No, you don't have
to feel that way.
I still believe my judgment
was correct.
Even though I failed...
the nuclear armament of this country...
will lead to a nuclear arms race
in the entire Northeast Asia.
A war could begin over
a real trivial matter.
Nuclear weapons can make us lose
everything with a single mistake.
Yes, I don't disagree with
your thoughts on this.
It's just that...
I had to be faithful to my duty.
Yes, I just don't want you
to misunderstand me.
Because I have a dual-citizenship...
don't think that I'm on the U.S. side to
stop the nuclear armament of South Korea.
- At least I don't want you to.
- Yes.
Team Leader Ji.
You trust Jung Yoo Gun, right?
What?
The only person who can help
Jung Yoo Gun from now on is you.
Jung Yoo Gun is not in a normal
condition due to the injury to his head.
That's why he may be keeping
his distance from you.
He believes the people close to him are going
to be in danger or get hurt because of him.
What happen to his mother
and your brother...
he blames himself for it.
There is a number that isn't stored
in the phone Director Kang Chul Hwan took.
That's Jung Yoo Gun's cellphone number.
After much time has passed...
there might be a day people
would finally understand me.
When that time comes,
come and visit me in the States.
Yes.
And...
you'll be repatriated in Washington D.C.
after the 9pm flight tonight.
It was decided faster than I expected.
Before I leave, would it be
okay to stop by my office?
I have many things to organize.
I'll make sure you can do that.
Thank you.
It's me Team Leader Jung.
Yes.
I'll be returning to the States
on a flight tonight.
Don't you regret it?
I told you. The justice I believe in is the
denuclearization of the Korean Peninsula.
Thank you for everything
and you've worked really hard.
While you were working with me...
you went through so many
hardships and suffering.
And you were the best agent I've ever
worked with in the U.S. and Korea combined.
Don't forget to take care of yourself.
Thank you so much for...
trusting me always.
And Team Leader Jung.
If everyone has their own
idea of justice...
I think your father sacrificed himself
for the justice he believes in.
Be good to Ji Soon Yun.
I wish you two a happy life together.
This is Ji Soo Yun.
Hello?
Soo Yun. It's me.
Are you doing well?
Yes.
You're doing well, too, right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Director Kang Chul Hwan
called just a moment ago.
He told me about
Deputy Director Choi Min.
Where are you now?
Let's meet.
Let's meet and talk.
Before that... I have a favor to ask.
What is it? Tell me.
There was a hard drive
I asked Byung Jin to analyze.
Byung Jin is...
He was arrested right
after you met with him.
I heard.
But fortunately, I don't think the Director
is aware of the existence of the hard drive.
I think Section Chief Hwang has it.
There is information about IRIS
and Baek San in that hard drive.
You need to get it back.
Be careful.
Hi.
It's me. I found it.
I'm sorry that I had to
ask you to do this.
Don't say that.
Let's meet today.
Let's meet and talk.
- Okay, and also...
- Yes.
I heard Hyun Woo has been injured.
Take good care of him.
I will. I'll see you later.
Seems like it's been a while
since you last talked to her.
How come you look like that?
Men are always like this.
They always do things they're
going to feel sorry about later.
Where are you going?
You're not even well.
I'm going to get some fresh air.
I'll come with you.
Am I freed now?
No, we're just going to move you.
This has no added sugar.
It'll be good toasted.
Thank you.
How are you feeling?
Fine, thank you for everything.
I haven't done much.
I'd like a bowl of soup and
a cup of coffee please.
Yes, sure.
If you eat that, you'll be freed.
I know you're disappointed in me.
You know in this field...
we often have to do things
we don't want to do.
I'm not going to say sorry.
When I heard it from someone else,
it didn't make me feel all that great.
I want you... to just trust me.
That I'm trusting you as
a colleague.
That I'll be there for you when
you're going through tough times.
Please just trust me.
Just as you've done so far.
Okay?
Finish it before I detain you again.
Okay.
Is it good?
Why did you come in here?
Are you going to buy clothes?
How can I help you?
The men's section is over there.
No.
Ah, are you looking for
your girlfriend's clothes?
Please come this way.
You were going to buy my clothes?
Yeah, look around and
pick one you want.
What do you think about this?
You still don't know my taste?
I always want black.
Real chic like this.
I think this looks nice.
What do you think about this?
Because it's black?
Let's go.
Clothes all of a sudden?
Is today some special day?
Since I owe you a lot...
For something like that...
[Yoon Shi Hyuk]
Yoon Shi Hyuk.
Seo Hyun Woo.
Where are you now?
Well, I wonder where...
Hey, Hyun Woo.
Because of the bullets I got
from you, my butt is still hurting.
You know that?
Yeah. This is Team Leader Ji.
Can you trace the location of the
call Seo Hyun Woo just received now?
It's urgent.
I always return what I get
from others.
I'll return your bullets three times over.
You should look forward to it.
Where are you now?
Did you find him?
Yes.
Where is it?
- It's your place.
- What?
Yes, Soo Yun.
Yoon Shi Hyuk called.
He was traced back to
Hyun Woo's place.
I'll head over that way now.
Be careful since it might be a trick.
He was definitely here
not too long ago.
I wonder why he was here.
He's trying to get back at me.
Subtitles by DramaFever
It's an honor to meet you.
I'm Anthony Choi.
How may I help you?
What are you doing?
From this moment on,
you've become a traitor forever.
If we could only secure one nuclear
weapon... how would you use it?
Of course, I'd detonate it
in the South's capital Seoul.
With that as a start, the army of
the Republic will march down south.
VAV STUDIO .:. VIETTORRENT.VN
www.facebook.com/VAV.AudioViet
© Copyright 2013, All rights reserved