VAV STUDIO .:. VIETTORRENT.VN
www.facebook.com/VAV.AudioViet
VAV STUDIO
© Copyright 2013, All rights reserved
Iris 2
Episode 19
He was here not too long ago.
What was he trying to do?
He's probably trying
to get back at me.
Jung Yoo Gun, Ji Soo Yun
and Kim Yun Hwa...
Hyun Woo must be happy.
What's the reason Yoon Shi Hyuk
is doing this to Hyun Woo?
While trying to escape, Yoon Shi Hyuk
got shot by Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo thinks Shi Hyuk is
trying to get back at him for that.
Anyway...
are you really okay?
Yeah, I'm doing fine.
What's going on...
with Kim Yun Hwa?
She's been helping me
to capture Yoo Joong Won.
Can you trust her?
If she isn't with me...
she has nowhere else to go.
About that hard drive...
You can retrieve the information inside
there only through the NSS's main server.
I'm sorry about asking for
such a difficult thing.
Please don't be.
You don't need to say that.
You really aren't going
to come back to the NSS?
I'm currently on the wanted list.
Wait for me until...
I catch Yoo Joong Won, Soo Yun.
After that, I'll turn myself in.
Thank you and...
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go.
Yoo Gun.
Please take care.
You, too.
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
Hey.
I'll take you to a hospital.
No, not to the hospital.
Take me back home.
- But...
- Just listen to me.
Good work.
I'll see you in the morning.
Why couldn't they fix
the broken surveillance camera...
Yoo Joong Won!
Do you think...
I suggested you the way of patriots
because I've got extra time on my hands?
I'd made myself clear that...
you'd regret it.
Yoo Joong Won.
Do you think you'll be okay after...
Mr. Black is looking for you.
Where have you been?
I eliminated the Director
of NSS Kang Chul Hwan.
You did an unnecessary thing.
Earlier today, Deputy Director
Choi Min tried to...
hand over the nuclear weapons
to the U.S..
And Kang Chul Hwan and Ji Soo Yun
apparently stopped her.
Kang Chul Hwan isn't an obstacle
to our mission.
If you use him well,
he could be a great help to us.
But Kang Chul Hwan refused
our offer to join us and...
he's been dying to capture us.
There are more than just a few trying to
capture our hidden IRIS operatives out there.
We can't eliminate them all.
The key is to use them without letting
them realize that they are being used.
If you act alone again
without my permission...
that'll be the end of
our relationship.
Keep that in mind.
Yes.
The President must be really pressed.
He informed me of further details.
They secured four nuclear warheads.
Baek San still has the last one.
I'm supposed to meet with
Baek San tomorrow.
There is something I want you to do.
What? You have something to say?
When I saw you again...
you were very agitated,
so I've held it on to it until now.
If not now, I didn't think I'd
have the chance to give it to you.
Joong Won.
It must be so tough for you.
Whether you're not skipping any meals,
or where you've been sleeping...
I lose sleep at night thinking
and worrying about you.
This morning, people from
the security command came by.
They turned your room upside down
searching for something.
I asked what it was about but they
just got angry and didn't tell me anything.
The people are saying something
bad must have happened to you.
I just hope that it's nothing serious.
I'm so sorry that your mother
can't be of any help to you.
I'm not sure if it's the right thing do
to tell you this when you've
got so much on your plate.
My health has deteriorated
a lot lately so...
I can't help thinking that
I may not be able to see you again.
I wanted to see you
get married before I die.
Joong Won, even if I don't get
to see you again, don't be too sad.
We all have to die at some point.
I've saved all the money
you sent me.
What would an old woman like me
need to spend all this money on?
Behind the house, under the big jar...
I kept all the money there inside
a plastic bag so that it wouldn't get wet.
That should be able to get you a wardrobe
and several beddings when you get married.
And I was going to give you the jade ring
your father gave me to your bride.
Just in case,
I want you to hold on to it.
I trust that everything will
turn out fine.
And don't even think about
avenging your brother.
Think of it as Heaven's will.
Please be well.
I wish for your happiness.
Love, your mother.
Mother...
Yes.
It's me.
Were you able to look inside
the hard drive?
No, not, yet.
Now, I'm not in a situation where
I can get help from the NSS.
I see.
Once you see the information
in the hard drive...
you'll be even more disappointed in me.
All the things I've done are
stored inside that hard drive.
Yoo Gun.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I couldn't leave
you any good memories...
like most fathers leave for
their children.
Can I ask you a favor?
Go ahead.
Please don't get involved in
this any longer.
Now, just return to your normal life.
Go back to Soo Yun and...
lead an ordinary life.
Yoo Gun...
I really... really am sorry.
I know it's late but...
I'm truly thankful that...
I got to know you finally.
Father...
Are you awake now?
Yeah.
What are... all these?
Do you know how worried I was?
You were suffering all night.
But I had no idea what was wrong.
Why don't you try taking something?
These are all the non-prescription
extra strength painkillers.
I'm okay now.
Really?
Excuse me.
How are you feeling?
I have a broken rib,
but I can handle it.
You were very lucky.
But how did you know Yoo Joong Won
would be after you?
You don't normally wear
a bullet proof vest and...
Some time ago, he tried to persuade me
to join him. Of course, I refused him.
I thought he would try to
retaliate in some shape or form.
As you said, I was very lucky.
Hi, how are you?
I'm Anthony Choi from the
Jeron Research Group.
I was put in charge of this research
by the President of South Korea.
In order to secure and transfer
the original nuclear technology...
the research teams from Jeron and
the Agency from Defense Development
will be collaborating
until the end of this project.
Was it the President's order to move
one of the nuclear weapons?
There was a request from Jeron.
I think the President is rushing things because
of the incident with Deputy Director Choi Min.
Let's go.
There's about 13 kilometers until
we get to the target location.
Okay. Be on standby.
I got it.
What is it?
One of the nuclear weapons
is getting moved.
It's me. Are you okay?
I was worried because you
weren't answering your phone.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I do have something I
need to confirm.
What is it?
One of the nuclear weapons is getting moved
from the Agency for Defense Development.
Do you know anything about this?
I heard it from the director
a short while ago.
Once the Pentagon finds out about
the nuclear warheads through Choi Min...
some measures will be taken.
So they're going to separate all four
warheads to carry out the research.
But how did you find out about it?
For safety purpose, the Deputy Director
has put a tracking device on each warhead.
Then where are they going to carry out
the research after they've been separated?
I heard the President consulted
an armament manufacturer called Jeron.
An armament manufacturer called Jeron?
Yes, Anthony Choi, a Korean-American, is
currently the CEO of the company.
So what's the status with the hard drive?
I haven't been able to access
the main server room, yet.
As soon as I have the info,
I'll call you.
Anthony Choi.
We'll be carrying out a
security inspection.
Fine.
Yoo Gun was right.
So it was you, Yoo Jong Chul.
Your son makes me want
to recruit him.
Just as much as when you were young.
I regret killing all those nuclear scientists
not even knowing who they were.
It's a shame that I couldn't kill you,
the one I really should have killed.
I should have realized what kind of person
you are and come back to my senses sooner.
Don't tell me the Baek San
I know is regretting now, is he?
It's not a regret...
but if something was done wrong,
I feel like I should make it right again.
Stop doing this thing you are doing
with the Hawk faction in the North.
My plan is very simple.
This country has been in
a state of truce for too long.
Ironically, the ones who are
living in this country...
have become immune
to the fear of war.
Are you planning a war?
I'm trying to end the ongoing war.
I told you just a moment ago.
This country is currently
in the state of truce.
It's still technically in a war
that has yet to end.
Should we get to the point now?
Hand over Yoo Joong Won to me.
Then I'll hand over the last
nuclear weapon to you.
I didn't expect that you'd be so easy
and not put up a fight at all.
By any chance,
is it because of your son?
You can have Yoo Joong Won
anytime after I'm finished with him.
But I'm skeptical that you'd actually
hand over the nuclear weapon.
I have no other objective.
The exchange between Yoo Joong Won
and the nuclear weapon.
That's all.
I'll be in touch again.
We're being tailed.
Do as planned.
Yes, I understand.
Let me stay with you
until the end.
No, you've done a lot of work.
Thank you for everything.
Without your help,
I couldn't come this far.
Go to Japan.
Find Matsumoto and he'll help
you get settled in Japan.
- Director.
- Do as I tell you.
And do not tell Yoo Gun
about my movements.
I've transferred all the files from
the hard drive into here.
Thank you.
Do you have anything else you need?
This morning...
I got a call from Baek San.
I felt like he was planning
on doing something today.
Did you... let him hear you
call him 'father'?
Mr. Jung Yoo Gun,
this is Jang Chul.
I'm the one who's been assisting
Director Baek San.
What's going on?
I need to see you now.
The Director told me not
to tell you but...
I thought you should know.
Call the ADD and find out
whether there are any survivors.
Sure, I'll do that.
The nuclear weapon has gone
missing during the transport.
What?
Where is Team Leader Yoo?
She's at the Agency
for Defense Development (ADD).
What the hell is going on here?
The nuclear weapon transport team
came under an attack and went missing
during the transport from the ADD
to the Jeron research center.
How many casualties?
Everyone from the Jeron research
team and all of the soldiers.
They look too much alike.
Wait for me here.
I'll be right back.
The Director made me
promise not to tell you but...
I thought you should know
about it since you are his son.
What the hell is going on?
Director went to go meet Mr. Black, now.
I told him I would escort him but...
I think he's trying to lure Mr. Black in.
Lure him in? To where?
I think he'll be going to the place
where he's hidden his nuclear weapon.
Did something happen?
Yeah, Soo Yun.
Yoo Gun, do you still have the tracing
device for the nuclear weapons?
Yeah, why?
One of the nuclear weapons
has gone missing.
And Anthony Choi is making a strong
protest against the current situation.
Soo Yun. Listen to me carefully, now.
Anthony Choi's real name
is Yoo Jong Chul and....
he is the nuclear scientist that disappeared
during the 4th administration.
He's Mr. Black.
Anthony Choi is... Mr. Black?
According to the information
I got from the National Archives...
In 1979, after President Park's death...
Director Kim Jung Yong from the
Central Intelligence Service and the CIA...
made a hit list consisting
of five people.
At the time, Baek San killed three on the list
without even knowing who they were.
In 2009, scientist Yoo Jong Won
was killed by Baek San again.
But, the one who ordered the killing was
Yoo Jong Won's brother Yoo Jong Chul.
That Yoo Jong Chul is Mr. Black.
In other words, he's Anthony Choi, now.
Out of the five nuclear scientists,
the one who survived was Mr. Black.
From the information you sent me,
I confirmed that they are the same person.
I'm sure the one who hijacked
the nuclear weapon was Yoo Joong Won.
And Anthony Choi is behind that.
Where is the nuclear weapon
that's been hijacked, now?
If they've discovered the tracing device,
the current location could be a trap.
I'll find out first and call you later.
Anthony Choi is...
Mr. Black of IRIS?
How can that be?
We suspect that Yoo Jong Chul,
who's disguised as Anthony Choi
has planned this whole thing with
Yoo Joong Won from the beginning.
Our current utmost priority is to locate
Anthony Choi and Yoo Joong Won.
That means... I arranged to have
our President and IRIS meet
and basically handed over
the nuclear weapons to Mr. Black?
Ji Soo Yun.
You are in touch with Jung Yoo Gun, right?
No use denying it.
I already got his contact number
from the Deputy Director's cellphone.
I've asked him help locate
the missing nuclear weapon.
Team Leader Jung has the tracer that
could locate the nuclear weapons.
Then you can contact Jung Yoo Gun to find out
the location of the missing nuclear weapon?
Currently, Team Leader Jung is in
the process of confirming the location.
I'll continue to be in
communication with him.
Since the time the
nuclear weapon has gone missing...
we've been tracing its movement through
the CCTVs in the surrounding areas.
Right now, our utmost priority is
the recovery of the missing nuclear weapon.
Cancel all other missions in progress
and focus on this mission.
Call Jung Yoo Gun and
make him join the team.
I'll make sure to have him
pardoned and...
until we are 100 percent sure...
we'll keep Anthony Choi's identity
as classified information.
Put down the gun.
If you want to die together,
you can tell me anytime.
If you keep quiet and follow me,
I can show you something.
Lift up the rug.
Report it to Mr. Black.
Tell me.
I've confirmed... the nuclear weapon.
But he's holding a remote control
device with a switch.
Is Baek San there?
Let me talk to him.
You did an unnecessary thing.
I do need a confirmation.
If you hand over Yoo Joong Won,
our deal will be finished.
What's the remote control
device you are holding?
You wouldn't be thinking about
a suicide bombing, would you?
This is the only weapon I have.
Your safety house is within
a 10 kilometer radius from here.
If you are thinking about playing
tricks, give it up, now.
You'll also disappear with me.
You already know where I am.
You're indeed Baek San.
Then, is our deal on?
Come on over to me.
I'll hand over Yoo Joong Won.
Is the device working now?
It is and I'm getting close
but it's little complicated.
I'll have the EOD team
watch all the major highways.
Okay, hurry up.
Magnify the front passenger seat.
Okay.
It's Park Tae Hee.
- Park Tae Hee?
- She's in disguise but I'm sure.
Open it.
It's going as we planned.
When's the D-day?
Rather than that...
we need to hurry up and prepare a
detonator for this bomb as soon as possible.
How should we prepare it?
According to the plan,
prepare it two different ways.
I understand.
At least once...
No, I wanted to call you
as my heart desired, Yoo Gun.
My son... Yoo Gun.
The moment I saw you
for the first time...
my desire to live became stronger.
I really have... ended so many
lives with my own hands.
But now that, I'm thinking about paying
for the crimes I've committed...
it's not that easy.
The moment I found out that
you and your mother were alive...
for the first time in 30 years...
I wanted to live.
If the opportunity arises...
I'd like to meet you again
as a father and a son.
I want to become a good
father to you.
What in the world are you planning?
Let's go.
What about the nuclear weapon
Baek San has?
We've confirmed the location.
Where is that?
We can't tell you that.
What?
This is Mr. Black's order.
Are you okay?
How many operatives are there
whom I can trust to be on my side?
Other than the seven including
Hyuk Soo and Chul Min...
everyone else is part of
Yoon Shi Hyuk's team.
What are you going to do?
Actually... after Mr. Black has secured
Baek San's nuclear weapon...
he might try to corner me with it.
He's underestimated
Yoo Joong Won.
I don't have a good
feeling about this.
I need to have a plan just in case.
Are you waiting for someone?
It's here.
Have you been waiting long?
We need to find where
Baek San is first.
We'll split up to look for him.
Whoever finds him first
will call the others.
Okay.
Where is Mr. Black?
Who are you?
A guest.
Where is Yoo Joong Won?
He's in the first room on the right
on the second floor.
If you want to use the nuclear weapon
you should use it for something
more productive.
To catch a small fry like me,
you want to drain the whole pond?
There is no need for self-deprecation.
If you're gone, that will pose a
big problem to IRIS's plan.
Even if your nuclear bomb goes off,
it'll have no effect on the IRIS headquarters.
You must know that better
than anyone.
Do you really think so?
As I've said before,
I've secured one already.
The South Korean government
has handed it over to me personally.
Their greed to possess nuclear
weapons and...
their excessively cautious attitude
to keep things secret...
has placed the nuclear weapon
into my hands.
Then... that means...
you don't need this.
Wait a minute.
I'll hand over Yoo Joong Won.
So hand that device over to me, now.
Yun Hwa.
Why the hell are you doing this?
Don't misunderstand and just listen.
This is because I'm worried about you.
I'm trying to stop you
from getting killed.
Come to your senses and
say something that makes sense.
You've been helping Jung Yoo Gun
who's been after me.
And yet, you say
you're worried about me?
You want to stop me
from getting killed?
Is that something...
you could say while aiming
a gun to my head?
I've been thinking a lot about how
to end the fight that one has to die for.
And there is only one conclusion.
A conclusion?
Stop what you are trying to do.
Helping IRIS to instigate a war...
if you can just stop that,
I can convince Jung Yoo Gun.
What?
You know very well why
Jung Yoo Gun is trying to kill you.
You...
killed Jung Yoo Gun's mother, I heard.
Think about it from his position.
You love your mother more
than anyone.
You know what made me
hold a gun at first.
My mother who suffered a miserable death.
My sister whom I don't even
know is dead or alive.
I came this far to avenge them.
And then, I even ended up
pointing a gun at you.
Since I swore all the hardliners
from the Republic are my enemies...
even you became my enemy.
Why do you have to become
my enemy?
Joong Won.
As you said before, let's just go some
place where no one will find us...
and just live there in hiding.
Not in this country where you can't
survive unless you step on someone else.
Let's find a place where there
is no greed.
Let's go live there, Joong Won.
Do you think the Director is in there?
We'll have to see.
What do we do now?
We need to find Baek San first.
We need to hurry before they come.
Captain, Baek San's location
has been discovered.
I'll be right there. Gather the
operatives and locate the intruders.
Yes, I understand.
We have intruders.
You were tailed.
Long time no see.
Team Leader Jung.
I really wanted to fight you
at some point.
I guess that's today.
Where are you now?
- What the hell are you...
- Your father is safe.
If you wish to see your father, come to the
basement under the center staircase.
Choose now.
Hand over that remote control
and leave here with your son.
Director!
Would you like to try convincing
your father?
Many innocent people are about
to evaporate from a nuclear bomb.
Yoo Gun.
There will be no end to
a revenge such as this.
I would like... this to be the end.
Yoo Joong Won is right there.
Hand that over to me and
take Yoo Joong Won with you.
As you said, your excessive greed
to possess nuclear weapons...
has blurred your judgment.
I never said this remote control...
is to detonate the nuclear bomb.
You...
Did you think my target
was Yoo Joong Won?
Baek San.
Father!
Thank you... Yoo Gun.
No!
Father!
Subtitles by DramaFever
It disappeared.
Yoo Joong Won took it.
Are you prepared for this?
His goal is to detonate the
nuclear bomb to start a war.
Find it no matter what you have to do.
If you need Team Leader Jung's help
in finding the weapon, get him involved.
When are you going to end this psychological
warfare that always ends with threats?
We have 1.2 million liberation soldiers
of the Republic.
Fine. If you succeed...
you'll all become the heroes of
the Democratic People's Republic of Korea.
I'm definitely going to make it successful.
Soon, the NSS and the police
will surround the area.
Without a doubt,
Jung Yoo Gun will be here.
He'll be great as a buddy to accompany
on my way to the other side.
You are the representative of the people?
Don't delude yourself, Yoo Joong Won.
That's only your pent-up anger.
- Joong Won.
- Why are you here?
Let's not die.
Even if it's hard, let's live.
We'll start this holy war for
the unification.
VAV STUDIO .:. VIETTORRENT.VN
www.facebook.com/VAV.AudioViet
© Copyright 2013, All rights reserved