Agent Hyun Jun, who is the best
in the Special Forces team,
falls in love at first sight with Seung Hee...
And Sa Woo, who was introduced to Seung Hee
by his hometown friend Sang Hyun,
also falls in love with Seung Hee at first sight.
One day, Hyun Jun and Sa Woo
are captured by suspicious men,
and go through rigorous tests and
special training to then join the NSS.
Not knowing that they had fallen
in love with the same woman,
the two meet Seung Hee again
on their first day at work.
Although Hyun Jun and Sa Woo find out that their meeting
with Seung Hee was set up and feel uncomfortable,
they fail to put aside their romantic feelings.
Hyun Jun kisses Seung Hee unexpectedly, and
their secret relationship within the NSS starts.
Hyun Jun and Sa Woo safely finish their first mission.
Also, after they are given a break from work,
Hyun Jun and Seung Hee leave for Akita
on a trip for just the two of them.
Sa Woo is sent on a mission by himself to assist
the North Korean nuclear physicist, Hong Seung Ryong,
to defect...
Episode 4
Wh-who are you?
Wh-what?
You know what it is.
Give it to me.
Why are you doing this?
What is this thing that
you're telling me to give?
Hey, Mr. Black.
Dr. Hong has been terminated.
He didn't have it either.
I think they took it.
Keep me in the loop.
What is that?
Uh. It's nothing.
What do you mean it failed?
Hong Seung Ryong and our three agents...
Who were supposed to bring him back are dead.
Is it a move by the North?
We're analyzing it right now.
What is the possibility that they knew,
about the fact we would allow Hong Seung Ryong
into our country after he defects?
As of right now, we haven't observed
any action taken by the North.
I feel regretful letting this chance
to acquire knowledge regarding the North's
nuclear weapon development pass by.
Deal with it quickly, so that the
situation doesn't get magnified.
Yes.
Where is Choi Seung Hee?
She's with Kim Hyun Jun
and Jin Sa Woo in Balaton,
waiting for orders to fly back.
Should I contact her?
Leave it.
What's it called again?
Goulash.
- Is it good?
- Yeah.
You want to try some?
How unsophisticated.
Hey, you. Shouldn't you get used
to eating things like that?
If she protests about my eating habits,
then I might as well give up on her.
Excuse me.
One more goulash please.
- You can't eat it, right?
- It's yours.
No, no, no.
She was just kidding. No.
Yes?
Yes. All right, sir.
What was that call?
Said there's a mission.
What mission?
I don't know. They just sent me the meeting location.
Why do you look so surprised to see me?
No one told me you would be coming.
Hong Seung Ryong is dead.
All the team members are dead.
From what we can gather right now,
we predict that it was a retaliation from the North.
Let's walk.
Have you ever heard of the
"Pan-European Picnic" by any chance?
In 1989, Hungarian communists opened their border
to allow thousands of refugees to leave for the West.
After that, the fall of the Berlin Wall happened,
and that's how the Cold War ended.
You are being given an independent assignment.
Just how this place, Hungary, had played
a major role in unifying Germany,
the success of this missing will have a major impact,
on the unification of the Korean Peninsula.
Can I... ask you something?
Sure. What is it?
When did you get so close with Hyun Jun?
I didn't even notice at all.
I just... think I had a thing for him from the start.
It wasn't until the day we went to
Vice Director's house for dinner,
after Hyun Jun had joined
that we got really close. That day...
It's because that day we had our first kiss.
What kind of a mission is it?
It's a solitary mission.
What about us?
They said to just to enjoy your vacation.
I don't have much time left to
be together with Seung Hee.
Aren't you busy?
I got it, man.
What kind of a mission is it
where you have to be alone?
It's nothing much.
Isn't this pretty?
That one's also pretty.
This? This one's very unique.
How did they make it?
Let's go.
Hello.
- Hi.
- Please pick a card.
- Tarot Card.
- No, thank you.
Hey, try it!
No. I don't want to. If it comes out
with bad things then we just feel bad.
Then we just won't believe in it. I'll try it.
- Pick one more card.
- One more.
Pick one more card.
The wheel of fate is in perfect position.
You cannot avoid destiny.
She says our encounter was one of fate.
No, that's okay.
I already heard what I wanted to hear.
No, no, no. That's okay. I already heard what
I wanted to hear. Two forints. Thank you. Let's go
Thank you. Bye.
It wasn't until the day we went to
Vice Director's house for dinner
after Hyun Jun had joined that
we got really close. That day...
It's because that day we had our first kiss.
Is your work early in the morning?
Why?
Do you know? You were nervous all day today.
What are you talking about? Me being nervous?
Don't worry. I'll come back soon.
Come back safely.
All right.
Good night.
Hyun Jun!
Didn't you sleep?
Yeah. You're awake already?
Yeah...
What kind of a mission is it?
EX.
(*EX: a mission to assassinate an important figure)
And the target?
The Vice Director is here in Hungary.
Go ask him if you're curious.
Hey, Sa Woo.
Yeah.
- If somehow things go wrong...
- Don't talk bullshit.
Why are you nervous all of a sudden today?
Man, I'm hearing that phrase a lot today.
What are you talking about?
Me, nervous?
Make me some coffee.
I wanna take a shower.
Sure.
Who is the target of the assassination?
Yoon Sung Chul.
Do you mean the party leader of the Supreme
People's Assembly in North Korea?
Yeah.
I'm not sure if I can ask something like this, but...
What's the reason?
ICBM*
(*ICBM: Intercontinental Ballistic Missiles)
To this day, the North has been painstakingly
developing technologies related to missile launchers.
Now they are just an inch away
from finishing a missile,
that is capable of attacking
the United States directly.
That last inch is a nuclear warhead.
For that reason,
Yoon Sung Chul is here in Hungary,
to have a secret meeting with the former Soviets.
We can't... just watch North Korea,
become a country with
a nuclear capability. Can we?
Right now, the total number of security agents
here in Budapest, including me, is twenty.
The NBH* and the police are cooperating with us,
(*Nemzetbiztonsági Hivatal;
National Security Office, Hungary; since 1989)
and we're planning on having 15 of Il Chong Gook's
body guards accompany him on the plane.
Starting this second, I'm raising
the security level to rank 1.
What is the reason, sir?
There was an intelligence report
of a planned assassination attempt.
Excuse me.
Please take a picture of me.
- Oh! Of course
- With the building.
- Okay.
- Once more please.
With this building? Oh, okay.
Here you are.
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome.
What is there for us to do right now?
We should... meet the Vice Director first.
The Vice Director is here?
Yeah. I only heard it from Hyun Jun.
Then Hyun Jun's solitary mission is something
he received directly from the Vice Director?
Yeah.
Give me a report on the surrounding area
of the square every two hours.
Yes.
What about the snipers' positions?
We've acquired positions where two
triangulation points overlap.
What about over there?
We're planning to close off the building itself.
What about the employees' admission passes and ID?
I checked them, sir.
I also checked the people who came
here during the last 30 days.
The movement of South Korea's intelligence
agency is also something to check for.
And of course, check to see if it's possible to disrupt
disrupt the U.S./South Korea communications via satellite.
Yes, sir.
Place a sniper here, as well.
Yes?
Even official Hungarian agents were sent in
and the security has gotten tighter.
The North's agents are already in position, too.
I see. I will contact you again.
Is there something wrong, sir?
It's nothing.
What is TK1's mission?
Do we have to provide assistance?
Vice Director.
Just wait a little while.
Think of this as a vacation and relax.
Yes.
There is no change in plan. Finish it.
I understand, sir.
Maybe something's gone wrong?
This is the second day we're on standby
without even knowing what the mission is.
Isn't there anything you know about Hyun Jun?
- Don't worry. He'll do well.
- Hello.
Did you get a new boyfriend?
No.
Bye.
Wait, wait...
The second card left out.
The most fatal tower.
Perfect position.
Something scary is coming.
What is she saying?
It's nothing.
What can I bring for you?
Espresso, please.
Thank you.
- And a... glass of water, please.
- Okay.
Why don't you eat something?
I'm all right, sir.
Have you heard of something called "khleb"?
It's a black bread that the Russians eat.
When I was studying abroad in Russia at the age of 22,
I used to live off that tasteless, hard
bread for a month every so often.
During Moscow's winter nights that
was cold enough to freeze your stomach,
I spent my days shivering in a room without
any heating, because at the time,
I had thought that the reunification of the
North and South was right in front of us.
I persevered, relying on that fact, but...
All right.
Situation report.
Standing by.
One minute to go.
Final report.
Standing by.
On standby.
P5, report again.
All agents maintain current positions
and keep a close eye on P5.
He is getting out of the car now.
Enemy agent! Cover the minister!
Enemy agent!
Minister!
Sir, are you all right?
Ambulance!
It's the emergency staircase on
the north side. Find the exit!
Yes, sir.
Get him!
Yeah. Continue the pursuit.
He's over there.
Stop the car!
Block all the subway stations within a 3 km range.
He's an Asian in his 30's.
Request an immediate search from the police.
You!
What are you doing?
There's this guy bleeding...
Which one? Where?
Mission accomplished.
They're currently on the hunt for me.
I've been shot and in danger of being caught.
I request assistance.
What are you talking about right now?
Don't you know that if we send in more agents,
at this point in time we're in
danger of exposing our identity?
I do know, but...
In my current state,
it is impossible for me to make my escape.
The only thing I can say to you now is...
We cannot send anyone in to help you.
Vice Director, there's an important reason
for me to live and return home.
Please help me.
Vice Director.
Were you looking for me, sir?
TK1 has sustained an injury during his mission.
It'll be bad if he's caught.
I think he's somewhere in this building.
They say this statue has a sad story.
A very beautiful woman named
Tachiko used to live here,
but she drank from a mystical
spring and fell under a spell
and she became the dragon that
protects this Lake Tazawako.
And Tarou also became a dragon that
protects the Lake Towada way over there.
The two of them who were separated like that,
meet here in this lake,
when winter comes to share their love.
They say it's because of their
unchanging love for one another,
that this lake never freezes over.
So what you're saying is that,
these two people just wanted to love one another,
but they've turned into monsters in different places.
Monsters?
That's right.
Monsters.
That makes it even sadder.
What?
The work we do.
Because if we keep going like this,
it feels like you and I also will become monsters.
Should we just give up?
Now we can't do that even if we wanted to.
Would you like a drink?
Where are TK1 and TK2 right now?
Please tell me.
Vice Director!
Fly back to Korea on the first flight available tomorrow.
It's an order.
Yes?
Yes. Call them up immediately.
(Classified information)
How credible is this text?
This report was a special report sent to the
Hungarian news agency based on witness testimonies,
so we have determined
this is true.
I somewhat understand that
Yoon Sung Chul's assassination was
a military action carried out by the North
to change its political structure.
However, how does this outrageous statement about the
intervention in this unrelated matter make any sense?
Then...wait. Does that mean the assassination
was ordered from our side?
That means... it's associated with the
conservative party from our side,
that wants to maintain the level of
tension between the North and South.
Since this information is something
that came from a credible source,
we're checking every channel on the
news to confirm this information.
Where is Vice Director Baek San?
Right now he's in Hungary.
Shouldn't we find out about the truth of the situation,
to come up with an appropriate response?
Before the press releases
its reports on assumptions,
we have to comprehend
the nature of this situation completely.
Yes.
Im Il Yong and Ahn Jae Bum.
- They're in Ukraine, right?
- Yes.
Tell them to go to Budapest and work with
their police to determine the military's actions.
Yes, sir. I got it.
Yang Mi Jung.
What are you doing right now?
I'm requesting assistance acquiring information
from the U.S. and Japan's intelligence agencies.
Gather information on all the blogs and internet
forums run by Hungarians in Budapest,
and all the other unofficial
information going around.
Yes, sir. I got it.
Is his location confirmed?
Room 204 was rented out three days ago,
it has an unidentified tenant.
What about the other rooms?
That's the only person on the second floor.
Were the orders given out?
Yes. There are no problems there.
Move.
What?
Things are bad.
Let's talk later and get out of here first quickly.
If we go to the private airspace
we dropped off Hong Seung Ryong,
we should be able to escape.
Hey, Sa Woo.
I'm sorry.
It's an order.
If I don't get him,
then you chase him down until the end.
What is the reason?
Where is Kim Hyun Jun's desk?
What are you doing?
He's under suspicion of being a spy.
If you're with me, then both you
and Sa Woo will be in danger.
I can't leave you like this.
Seung Hee.
Hyun Jun is dead!
This is a fact that everyone
in the world knows about!
You're the only one who doesn't know that!