Sa Woo sees the necklace left behind and deduces
that Hyun Jun is a part of the terrorist group.
The terrorists leave false clues to cause Sa Woo and
the security team to vacate NSS in pursuit of the wrong leads,
and they then take over the NSS building.
Seung Hee arrives after the overtake
and after fighting a terrorist member,
comes face to face with Hyun Jun in a mask
Don't move!
Episode 11
Throw your gun away!
Hurry up and throw your gun away.
Don't move.
Throw your gun away.
Hyun Jun!
Hyun Jun, wake up.
The explosive is ready.
Proceed.
Detonate!
The entrance has been opened.
We're getting out of here now.
Everyone get ready.
We understand.
Everybody keep your heads down,
and don't make a move.
Shouldn't we do something?
Let's wait.
There's no one here.
This is our chance.
The bomb has been set.
I got it.
Come to area 2.
A3,
respond.
Where are you?
In the 3rd basement level.
We're on our way.
Hyun Jun.
Hyun Jun!
That was Seung Hee.
Seung Hee is alive.
Seung Hee was alive all this time.
Hyun Jun!
No.
We have to get out of here now.
Move.
The entrance is open.
They'll be all over the place.
Move.
Turn around.
We must leave now.
This isn't the time.
What did you do to Seung Hee?
Don't worry.
She was only knocked out.
I have to see Seung Hee.
Then what?
Then what will you do?
After you see her, what can you do then?
If you're caught here,
no one will believe you.
You have to get out of here first.
Think about what brought us here,
to this point.
What are you doing!?
What were you doing here?
We were chasing the person who made outside contact.
The entire NSS team,
will be here any minute.
We must hurry up and get out of here.
I got it.
Follow me.
Didn't you hear?
You'd better move!
Let's go.
Let's hurry.
Where's the rest?
They're not responding.
They're entering now.
Get ready.
Cut it.
Stop the shooting!
Stop shooting!
This place is clear.
Are you all alright?
We're the only ones here.
Where's Team Leader Choi Seung Hee?
Didn't she go with the team to investigate?
I'm certain she was here.
I think you need to come see the control room.
Why?
There's a time bomb.
The timer has started already.
TK2,
a bomb is counting down to detonation.
What type is it?
It's an A Composition RDX bomb with exploding wire detonator.
How much time is left?
Five minutes, 21 seconds left.
Can you disable it?
I'll give it a try.
"The Emergency Tactical Team has arrived.."
Everyone in the building, listen to me.
Everyone is to evacuate this building,
with help of the Emergency team within 4 minutes.
Ah!
Oh!
Oh, where is Choi Seung Hee?
You've seen Team Leader Choi Seung Hee?
She saved me then took off.
Where did she go?
I wouldn't know that.
Team Leader!
I think we can have everyone evacuated within two minutes.
The 25 people hurt on 3rd floor are being put in ambulances.
Have you seen Team Leader Choi Seung Hee?
I haven't seen her.
How much time do we have?
There's 2 minutes and 20 seconds left.
Do you think it's possible to disable?
The wires don't look to be explosive.
Let's double check one more time.
I think it'll be fine.
Pray.
How's it coming?
We've successfully disabled it.
Seung Hee!
Even though we loved each other,
Here we are parting.
Even though we're under the same sky, in different places,
please don't forget me.
Emergency Team!
Your laughter that I hear whenever
Seung Hee!
Open your eyes!
The cold wind brushes the tip of my fingers.
You're two eyes that reflected my face,
Because I'm lonely, I cry and cry again.
The words I couldn't say
Don't Move!
because my lips froze
Throw your gun away!
Even though we loved each other,
Here we are parting.
Even though we're under the same sky, in different places,
please don't forget me.
Is something wrong with him?
No.
Why?
Ever since the attack on NSS,
he's been acting strangely.
He killed people who were his friends until recently.
Of course he would be upset by that.
I'm sure he'll be fine,
so don't be too concerned.
Everyone is thinking you're acting strange.
I know how confusing it must be for you right now,
but if you don't control your emotions,
things will become complicated.
Because we sent everything to the emergency protocol server,
all the systems are being restored.
Good job.
You were something to see.
In what way?
How could you think clearly enough to use
the emergency protocol in that situation?
Isn't it just the basics?
I just saw white and my mind went blank.
Computer operator should fight with computers,
not with a gun that he can't even use well.
Hey!
Mi Jeong is right.
That gun could have put everyone in greater danger.
At last count, there are 19 dead and 6 hurt,
but I think the number of fatalities will grow.
The deceased are all agents in the Security Division.
The damage was as great as it was due to the
security teams that were out on the investigative mission.
What have you found out about the terrorists?
We've turned the dead bodies over to the lab for further evidence.
They entered at the time when most
of the security agents were out.
They didn't use the high security elevators,
and the fact that they knew how
to shut down the emergency system,
leads us to believe they've studied us thoroughly or,
someone involved with NSS did it.
What was their target point within NSS?
It was the R and D room.
R and D room?
Precisely, an object under high security
in the R and D room was their target.
I haven't said anything to anyone about this yet.
Yes.
I'll be right there.
Who was that?
The Blue House.
How could this possibly have happened?
The very people that should protect us from the terrorists
opened up their innermost room to the terrorists.
"How can this be possible?"
Did you find out anything about those that attacked NSS?
We're in the midst of finding out.
Shouldn't we call for a congressional session to determine
the Director's responsibility in this matter?
The North Korean Leader is down here right now.
If this gets out,
what kind of humiliation will this be for our nation?
The President would like to see you.
I will take full responsibility for this and resign.
Resign when you will,
but you still need to address the issue.
We've begun the investigation to find
out who the responsible party is.
More importantly,
did you find out the reason why they entered NSS?
If they are bold enough to attack NSS,
I have to believe they had a specific reason.
There was something,
that was not included in the report.
What was that?
An important piece of equipment that the NSS was protecting,
has gone missing.
It is a highly specialized piece of an explosive device.
What do you mean by explosive device?
It's a detonation device,
used with uranium,
to complete a nuclear bomb.
Did you...
just say a nuclear bomb?
The device that was in NSS protection,
did not include uranium.
Uranium is not something that can be readily obtained, but,
if someone were to get their hands on it,
it would become a nuclear bomb,
that they can let loose at any time, any place.
Are you saying the terrorists..
have a nuclear bomb in their possession?
It would be safe to assume that.
Where are you?
We got out safely,
and are awaiting for further instructions.
What is the damage?
We lost 3 men.
To carry out our next mission,
we will need additional men.
Stand by until I contact you again.
I understand.
We need additional men.
Yes, sir.
Shortly,
a uranium capsule will be brought here.
You will have to assemble a nuclear bomb.
Can you do it?
Yes.
Everyone is wondering what this is.
It's not the time to let them know yet.
Keep it a secret.
I understand.
What?
The person that killed Ki Dong and Young Soo...
was a girl?
Yes.
She was even the person that was in contact with the outside.
Stupid fools.
How could they have gotten killed by a bitch?
What happened to her?
Did you kill her?
No.
Do you remember her face?
Everyone,
until we receive word on our next mission,
we wait here.
When will that be?
I don't know that myself.
Where is he?
He's outside.
Don't leave him alone,
and keep your eye on him.
Yes, sir.
Starting right now, today,
drop the polite talk outside of the organization.
You won't regret it?
Regret?
What regret?
Drop it.
Got it.
Choi Seung Hee.
It's awkward, but feels pretty good.
I like it, I like it.
There's a wind is blowing inside my heart
Your image is being erased
While having a dream called regret,
I stand here missing you.
I lasted a day because
you said you love me
I lasted a month because
of that gaze staring at me.
I loved you, I loved you,
but my wound has spread, so I can't go
I can't stay true to these words, "I love you"
No matter what the reason,
I cannot do this.
The day I leave you,
If you can't, I have to find someone else.
Send Choi Seung Hee in.
I'll love you, I'll wait for you
You remember all the times we spent together
The words I couldn't say,
If one's ambition is controlled,
his sense of loyalty of responsibility,
the words I wanted to say
there is nothing for him to lose.
I'll say them now
In that sense,
my choosing you was the right decision.
I love you
Don't you think so?
It's me.
What is it?
I have something to say to you in person.
I don't have the time today.
Do it another time.
Right now.
I have to see you right now.
What's wrong with you?
Have you been drinking?
Yes.
It's too hard to get through this with a clear head...
so I had a little to drink.
I had a drink thinking of Hyun Jun.
I had a drink thinking of Choi Seung Hee.
And while I thought of you,
who turned my life upside down,
and while blaming you,
I had another drink.
After those drinks, I find myself a little drunk.
Why did you pick me?
Why did you pick me and make me stand at the edge of the cliff?
Jin Sa Woo, you listen to me carefully.
It was me that chose you,
but the one that made the decision was you.
So who are you trying to blame?
If you ever say repeat those worthless words again,
I will not forgive you then.
Section Chief!
Any results back on the dead terrorists?
Not yet.
Are there any developments on finding out who the terrorists were?
No.
But one thing for certain is,
that someone from the inside,
helped the terrorists.
How they knew our security system,
and penetrated the building,
but the most telling is,
that the terrorists knew our emergency shutdown system.
That's something that no one outside of NSS knows about.
If it's someone from within NSS,
then who...?
There's not enough evidence yet to identify that person.
How is Seung Hee doing?
She should be released soon.
Any progress on the findings?
The lab is going through the uniforms the terrorists had on,
but so far, nothing concrete.
Has the reason for them attacking NSS been determined?
See me outside for a minute.
A bomb device?
It has an error rate of less than 1 in a million.
It's even passed the nuclear testing phase.
If it passed nuclear testing,
then are you saying it's a nuclear weapon?
If it's used as a nuclear device,
then it does become a nuclear weapon.
If it goes off in the city of Seoul,
then the Blue House,
the National Assembly building, all of it will be in danger.
The total number of fatalities,
can be as high as 150,000.
This is only known as far as the middle level,
so keep it to yourself until you're further instructed.
Yes.
I'll be right there.
Isn't there a possibility that it will be taken...
out of the country?
If it does,
then it becomes a greater problem.
Our government will face international criticism and,
economic turmoil that we will not be able to withstand.
From this moment on,
the entire NSS organization's focus
will be on finding the people that took this.
The National Security team will focus anyone
who had anything to do with nuclear development.
Yes, sir.
The Terrorist and Security Teams will set this at top priority level.
The discussions with the North Korea officials for the meeting,
are moving along smoothly.
Before the visit,
please schedule a personal meeting with them for me.
Yes, I understand.
Is there something else?
Ah, yes.
There is something I don't quite understand.
Yes, go ahead.
By any chance...
did you receive a separate report
from Director Baek San that I don't know anything about?
In the report,
there were only reports of the damage
and nothing about the reason for the terrorist targeting NSS.
Looking at it from a practical view,
there wouldn't have been
any obvious reason for them to have attacked NSS.
There is,
but I don't believe it's time to share with you yet.
Ah, yes.
If the President has made that determination,
then I have nothing to say on that matter,
but,
what I would like to say to you is,
don't trust Director Baek San too much.
It's me.
The only person at the Blue House who knows is the President.
I guess we can assume,
the summit meeting will go on as planned.
Yes.
Even under the threat of the nuclear weapon,
he doesn't seem to be wavering in his decision.
Yes.
I will be in contact again.
How many outside entrances are there?
There are a total of six.
Are there any areas of public access,
that are not covered?
Every spot is monitored by security.
Will it be alright,
to have our own security agents on watch?
As you would like.
Who do you think are the terrorists?
Is it possible...
that they're North Koreans?
With the summit approaching,
I don't think they would take the risk.
What is the President's reaction?
He isn't wavering,
from his desire for this meeting.
We've finished the walk-thru of their security.
Please have a seat.
How was it?
After having walked through?
To facilitate the meeting and to sleep and eat,
there seems to be no problem.
But, the number of security personnel...
If it's about that,
the President's security team, as well as the National security team,
and doubled police staff will be made available.
The citizens in the South are different from those of the North
so we need to ensure complete security for this meeting.
When your former president, Kim Dae Jung visited us,
the citizens that came out to welcome him,
were polite and well behaved.
What I mean by that is there was no danger of any action
on the part of the citizens against our visitor.
But South Korea is different.
This is the middle of Seoul.
There will be people to welcome our Leader,
but there will also be people who will oppose.
It seems risky for us,
to dismiss the army.
During the meeting,
there will be plenty of police and security
presence outside of the hotel.
June 3, 1993...
do you remember what happened on that date by any chance?
The South Korean President,
was pelted with an egg at Kimpo airport.
If something similar were to happen at this event,
I don't believe you will be able to recover from it.
Hey!
What was it that we took from NSS?
I don't know.
Tell me what it is, you bastard.
I really don't know.
Shit.
Three people died already,
and we don't know what we're doing?
If you have a problem, talk to the Cap about it.
Why are you taking it out on me?
This bastard... you're really...
I'm not going to do anything stupid,
so you don't have to look so nervous.
The reason I believed Seung Hee was dead,
was because the car she was in,
blew up in front of my eyes.
When I saw that,
I couldn't think of anything else.
Now, I just have to do what I'm supposed to do.
This is the file that was in Baek San's storage.
Hurry up and find out what the contents are for me.
Okay.
Can you make any guess on
what it was we took from NSS?
What're you doing?
Oh, nothing.
If you're bored, let's play some cards.
I'm fine,
so don't worry about me.
Did you find out?
What was it?
Everything about Baek San's involvement with IRIS was there.
Any time there was any major event,
behind it was,
IRIS,
and Baek San.
When South Korea was developing nuclear arms,
how they got rid of the participants,
and among that,
there was information about your parents.
What are you talking about?
Kim Jung Kook, Yoon Mi Yeon...
aren't they your parents?
I have no memory of anything about my parents.
When I went to the orphanage,
I was about 7.
I thought they died in an accident
but I don't know who they were or even their names.
Tell me, so...
They were both...
nuclear scientists that were involved in
the nuclear arms development.
What is your name?
Kim Hyun Jun.
And the person that caused the accident to kill them
was Baek San.
You survived the accident and
the person that took you to the orphanage,
was Baek San, as well.
Even after that,
he kept his eye on you as you grew up.
Team Leader!
How are you?
I'm okay.
You should have taken some time off.
What's going on?
They're still examining the bodies.
Were they able to make identifications of their faces?
Of course.
Anything out of the ordinary?
Out of the ordinary?
Just,
if they were able to find out anything from the bodies.
The lab hasn't been able find anything out yet.
There's something big going on,
but we don't know what that is yet.
Do you see it?
Yes.
What it is?
I can't really tell.
Tsk, you worthless...
get out of there!
Hmm!
Oh,
are you out of the hospital already?
Yes.
Are you very busy?
Well, we haven't found anything definite yet.
These guys...
they took care to make sure they didn't leave any traces.
But then, they have to be that competent
to have penetrated NSS.
What?
Do you have something to say?
That program you mentioned before...
Mmm.
What, what?
The program that uses the skeleton outline to define a person...
Ah, ah...
you guys go take a break.
Okay.
Sit.
Go ahead.
You said that web cam image
was 74% certain that it was Hyun Jun.
I did say that.
Then,
can't that be conclusive that it was Hyun Jun?
Tell me please, Manager.
That is...
Sa Woo was so adamant that it wasn't,
and I didn't want to add to the confusion so I let it go,
but at that rate,
it's safe to assume that it was Kim Hyun Jun.
Jeong In,
let me see you for a sec.
When you were held hostage,
you saw the terrorists, right?
I did see them,
but they all had masks on so I didn't see their faces.
Did...
you see the report about me
when I was facing that terrorist?
Yes.
The report said that the terrorist that was facing me,
killed his comrade by mistake.
But I don't think that was a mistake
but an intentional act to save me.
What are you talking about?
Why would that terrorist...?
I think he was...
Hyun Jun.
What?
The information you got from Hungary
about Hyun Jun's death,
was that reliable information?
Seung Hee,
what's wrong with you?
I know it sounds crazy to you,
but let me ask you for one more favor.
Please double check that information from Hungary.
It's connected.
What is the time allowed?
The time it takes to switch from live monitoring to taped
is maximum 60 seconds.
You can exit now.
If you go out through the emergency exit,
there is a utility elevator.
Everyone's worked hard.
There was nothing conclusive
found on the dead bodies.
There wasn't even a tattoo on the bodies.
What about the fingerprints?
There were none.
What do you mean none?
I mean the hands did not have any prints.
The labs took the frontal pictures and the dental imprints
and came up with nothing.
We even checked against the international database
but still came up with nothing.
Anything from the items they left behind?
The same thing.
All the items were common items with nothing
noteworthy to create any leads in identifying them.
Even their weapons, nothing to narrow down.
But,
one thing we did get was from the dust off of their clothes.
There was something unique about it.
There was a trace of hydrated compound.
I thought it was strange,
so I studied it further...
and found that to be Actinolite.
Aish...
try and talk in our language.
Asbestos!
It was found in their clothes and shoes,
but...
not in their lungs or esophagus.
That means,
they came in contact with it recently.
Then that would mean after they entered the country,
they were in a place where they came in contact with it, right?
Bravo!
Yes, we can assume that.
Asbestos is common in places of construction and factories,
so it'll be difficult to narrow it down.
That's not exactly true.
If it's Actinolite,
it's an asbestos that's not really that common.
And because it can travel by air,
its use was made illegal in 2003.
For the number of people that are involved,
and to move without being seen,
there can't be too many places for them to operate out of.
I'm sure it would be a place where it once
processed or stored Actinolote.
They drew out our security team then used that opportunity
to penetrate NSS so based on that,
I don't believe they were too far from here.
So...
If we look for empty storage areas that fit that criteria,
I believe it's possible to find them.
Good.
Hurry up and pull that list up and report to me from the field.
Seung Hee,
I need to talk to you.
Did you confirm it with them?
Yes.
The Hungary Intelligence said
they never sent such information.
Then what does that mean?
You said you saw it for yourself!
I think someone...
created it and put it in the system.
Who could have done such a thing?
I can't think of who could have, myself.
I couldn't even make a guess.
Assembly?
It's possible.
I will tell you when and where.
Keep this confidential until then.
I understand.
What do you think of Kim Hyun Jun?
I've had no problems with him so far.
He was instrumental
in us getting into NSS.
Go on in.
I heard...
how useful you were in getting into NSS.
Since you've cooperated,
I will keep the promise I made to you.
Can you tell me what it was that we took from NSS?
It's not that I don't trust you,
but those are the circumstances.
In the near future,
in the middle of Seoul,
something will happen that you could never imagine.
To show my trust in you,
I will not have you watched or kept under guard.
As long as it's with Seon Hwa,
you may move about freely.
I heard that the explosive device,
that was in the R and D room is missing.
Doesn't that mean that a nuclear bomb
can go off in the middle of Seoul?
Yes.
What you and I have to do,
they are doing it for us.
Before it happens, they cannot be caught.
You,
control the areas of investigation.
Yes, sir.
Come in.
I have something to say to you.
Go ahead.
I will be leaving...
No,
you have to hear this.
Kim Hyun Jun is alive.
Which way?
I'm sure he'll be in the sanctuary.
Father!
Hyun Jun!
Father.
Father!
We need to get out of here.
I'm in Korea.
Can we meet?
I think Kim Hyun Jun got into my storage files.
It held the secret of his parents' death
and that I'm a part of IRIS.
It's moving along as planned.
What is to happen in South Korea,
how far along is it?
What are you searching for?
A storage facility.
Change of plans.
Take the team and go over there.
The location has been identified.