Where is the location the bomb was planted at?
Hyun Jun and Seon Hwa who arrived a
Kwang Hwa Mun with Chul Young's help,
after having a gunfight with the terrorists,
succeed in stopping the nuclear terrorism.
Not only was it an act of benefitting our
enemy, it was a betrayal to the country.
- Why did you do it?
- My only thoughts were of vengeance.
After these events and after Hyun Joon and Seon Hwa are
investigated by the NIS* (National Intelligence Service)
* National Intelligence Service.
Chul Young and the Blue House try their
best to find out the identity of IRIS...
The incomplete IRIS list...
I wish you would finish this task.
Episode 18
The thing I asked for...
Oh, I made it so that you could access it from my PC.
Access code.
Thanks.
I won't be returning to the NSS.
You...it must be because of what the director said,
but you don't need to care about that.
No. It's not because of that.
Then what is it?
I heard that the identity of the IRIS members
within our country weren't all revealed.
I heard that even the people from the Blue House asked you to find out about them.
I was able to fall into deep sleep
without having nightmares...
for the first time in two years.
I'm a little afraid to walk into that nightmare again.
Alright.
However,
don't decide so easily and think about it again after you...
get some rest.
Where's Mi Jeong?
Uhm...
What?
Did something happen?
Mi Jung didn't come in today.
What?
I haven't been able to reach her.
Sheesh, even though we're in a situation like this...
Hurry up and call her in.
Yes, sir.
There's a wind blowing inside my heart
Your image is being erased
While having a dream called regret,
I stand here here missing you.
I lasted a day because
you said you love me.
I lasted a month because
of that gaze staring at me.
I loved you,
but my wound has spread, so I can't go.
I can't stay true to these words, "I love you"
The day I leave you,
What are you thinking about?
I'm not thinking of anything.
And...
I feel comfortable because I'm able to do so.
Because...I only have to see and
feel the sea that's in front of me.
Me, too.
I'm happy because I can see and feel you,
without having any complicated thoughts.
I lasted a year because
of the smile you used to give me,
because of the one memory I shared with you,
which I believed was a dream
I loved you, I loved you,
but my wound has spread, so I can't go
I can't stay true to these words, "I love you"
The day I leave you,
I'll love you,
I'll wait for you
You remember all the times we spent together
The words I couldn't say, the words I wanted to say
are left in my heart and they flow out
Allow us just one thing out of this world
Where did you go?
Oh, I had to meet someone.
Who?
A friend from college who got married
to someone from here and they have a Permissions farm.
They already have two kids.
They're absolutely adorable.
"Terribly Noisy and...
Unbelievably Close"?
What kind of a book title is that?
It's about a 9-year-old kid,
who lost his father during the 9/11 incident,
and it seems like he's in the same situation that I'm in...
Should I say...
it works as medicine?
Why are you reading that and making your head
hurt when you've got a real medicine?
What is it?
Me.
Should I get started with the treatment?
How is it? Is it working?
A bit.
How can I forget you?
How can I let you go?
"I love you." Because I couldn't say that one line,
I bury you in my heart again today
...in my heart again today
Receiving call
Caller ID control
Hello?
Yes, it's me.
Where are you right now?
Alright.
Situation report.
We're moving towards a tunnel.
Nothing unusual so far.
S-sorry... I'm sorry sir.
I already know even if you don't tell me.
I'll carry out the mission successfully this time.
[Park Sang Hyun]
- Yes section chief.
- I think you should return to your position quickly.
I told you, I'm...
Director Baek San and Jin Sa Woo have escaped during transport!
We've called a copter, so come quickly.
Hello?
Section chief!
[Seung Hee]
Since the phone is turned off...
All of them with the exception of
Na Sung Shik have disappeared.
What about the transport personnel?
They all died when they were being
transported to the emergency room,
except for one.
Yeah, it's me.
Alright.
Even the one that was being transported
to the emergency room died.
I bet the attack on the transport vehicle
took no longer than ten minutes...
from when they started their attack to when they finished and disappeared.
The ones who attacked the transport vehicle
have received training for a small army.
How do you think they knew the exact
route and time of the transport?
The plans for this transport were only
known to the transport personnel,
not even to the federal government.
Even on our side, the only ones who knew
of the transport route and time were
Director Yoo Gwang Ho and me.
Don't you have any ideas on where they fled?
We haven't been able to find any clues to track them down so far.
What about Satellite tracking?
Since it's a mountainous area with a lot
of tunnels, satellite tracking isn't easy.
In order to prepare for when
they escape out of the country,
quickly do whatever you can.
Please have the NSS take care of this task.
I'll ask the national administration to cooperate.
Alright.
How did you get this place?
It was prepared by headquarters.
This is Baek San, sir.
Yes, sir.
I just arrived.
Alright, sir.
He's from Delta Force and a part of the civil military service
from the PMC that headquarters runs.
He was with his regiment in a conflict zone in Afghanistan,
supporting the American military until
we brought him here for the mission.
These men were the military instructors
at the secret military camp
where they train the best mercenaries.
From now on, Jin Sa Woo will be giving out all the orders.
I'm Jin Sa Woo.
You've had it rough.
There won't be anything troubling you,
since I've said you were just following
my orders in Japan and South Korea
to stop the coup d'état.
Thank you, sir.
Now you just need to return to the national guards.
If my opinion could be changed...
I do not wish to return...
to the national guards.
Tell me what you want.
I want to go back to my hometown.
Whether I start farming there,
or become a public teacher...
I want to live like that.
I think I'll be heading down South Korea again,
because of the summit.
I was wondering...
if you could help me...
I do not wish...
to go to South Korea again.
Kim Hyun Joon...
is it because of him?
I just...
I just wish it were...
something like a cold.
Even if it hurts a lot,
I just...
I wish I could just...
sleep a night,
and shake it off...
I...
wish for you to be happy.
I hope you don't stay hurt for much longer.
For the issue of going back to South Korea,
let's give it some more time.
For now,
rest.
Section chief!
Yeah. You came?
What happened?
The ones who attacked the transport vehicle
have received military training for a small army.
All the information including the time and route
of transportation were leaked beforehand...
and also...
Mi Jeong was found dead.
Sorry?
Go to the scientific investigations room.
What happened sir?
I never thought
there would be a day when
I'd have to do an autopsy on her with my own hands.
What's the cause of death?
Damage to the autonomic nervous system,
caused by a fracture to the cervical vertebrae.
It killed her in one blow.
Wasn't there anything else that came out?
There isn't.
The attacker didn't leave a single finger print.
I checked her possessions and her cell phone was gone
and her computer was seriously damaged.
- What about recovery?
- They're doing it right now,
but nothing can be guaranteed.
This... is the doing of a professional.
The recovery of Mi Jeong's computer hard drive is finished,
but...
In the recovered files, information about
director Baek San's convoy came up.
How can that be there?
I think someone hacked into Director Yoo
Kang Ho's terminal from the server,
and the information leaked out from there.
Who would do that?
I checked the server access records and...
it's Section Chief Oh Hyung Kyu.
M-me?
I-it, i-it isn't me.
It isn't me.
Even though it was in the server access records?
Uh, uh that, that is...
That's b-because...
I gave Mi Jeong the server access card...
Why?
After the new director was appointed,
he restricted my server access,
so I asked Mi Jeong to undo...
Do you think that makes any sense?
How can you give the server access card to a kid
who doesn't have the security level
to access it so thoughtlessly?
Even I...
didn't know it'd turn out like this...
Eh? Eh?
[Seung Hee]
Since the phone is turned off...
What are you planning to do with these men?
The president, is continuing to push on with the summit.
We have to put a stop to that.
Is it possible...
with these men?
I wonder...
How would you do it?
It'd be over if we get rid of the person
who wants to force the summit,
wouldn't it?
You mean...the president?
The result on the analysis of Mi Jeong's
cell phone call records have come out.
Most of them have been verified as family or friends,
but one number can't be identified.
There isn't a lot, but there's a
record with consecutive calls.
When is that from?
It's about four months ago.
I think this is him.
This is a secured folder in Mi Jung's blog.
When I unlocked the password and went in,
these pictures were in there.
It's been about four months since
the pictures were first posted.
Go back.
Zoom in on that part and get rid of the mosaic.
I think it'll be hard to recognize who it is.
Just a sec.
Nii- chan* (*older brother)
Yuki.
Although I don't know his name or nationality,
I suspect that he is a Korean
or a Korean living overseas since
he is able to understand Korean.
How did you get to know this guy?
He tried to kill me in Japan because
of Hong Seung Ryong's files,
and he murdered a friend named Yuki
who had helped me and her whole family.
A while ago,
he also murdered committeeman Yeon Gi Hoon.
He was even responsible for Yeon Gi Hoon?
I'm sure he's a professional killer who works for IRIS.
If it was four months ago that he met Mi Jeong,
then he must have approached her with a motive.
Currently,
he's the only surefire lead to Jin Sa Woo
and director Baek San's whereabouts.
Alright.
At least we've acquired a photo of him,
so it'll help in tracking him down.
Also, Section Chief..
What?
You have something more to say?
I can't contact team leader Choi Seung Hee.
Can't contact her...
What do you mean?
She was with me in Jeju Island and I returned ahead,
but I still can't contact her.
I have a bad feeling about this.
- We have to quickly find...
- Alright.
I'll send agents to Jeju Island,
so you focus on finding Jin Sa Woo and Baek San.
How come the criminals cannot be identified
even though the incident has happened who knows when,
their whereabouts unknown, no miscellaneous evidences,
unknown, cannot be identified...
just what exactly are the NSS and the NIS doing?
We're on it.
Since we're putting in all our efforts, we'll find them soon.
So far, we've found almost nothing about
the IRIS organization within the country.
Also from committeeman Yuhn Ki Hoon's assassination to now,
the fact that there's an information leak is a bigger problem.
That is why...
maybe you should let the north know of
this also and reconsider the summit...
Why, what do you mean reconsider?
Are you saying we should stop the
summit because of something like this?
I'm just saying that the dangers have
grown while we still haven't found
anything about the IRIS organizations within the country.
I heard that the north was finished in dealing with the
rebel forces who were responsible for the coup.
Even though the north's taken care of its situation,
we have yet to deal with ours.
I think that the fact that we're in this state of
confusion should not be known to the north.
We have come here after having gone through
even the dangers of a nuclear terror.
No matter what they do,
we're not changing anything.
Find Baek San's whereabouts with haste,
and reveal their identities.
Yes, sir.
When the third group infiltrates the target area first,
they will take over the security room first
and the installation of the biochemical weapon
in the ventilation room will be complete.
What kind of biochemical weapon will you be installing?
It's Soman* gas sir. (*aka nerve agent Soman)
Since Soman gas' LD50 is 2000 milligrams per 1 kilogram,
LD 50: the dosage of toxin that kills half the
test subjects when used in animal testing.
it is able to kill many with just a small amount.
I checked the target building's special arrangements
and ten minutes is enough to carry out this procedure.
When the operations at the security room
and the ventilation room are complete,
all the entrances and exits will be
blocked from the security room
and the team on stand-by will drive the
hostages into the center of the building.
- What about the estimated time that will be spent?
- Fifteen minutes will be enough, sir.
What do you think of this?
It's too much to handle.
The place we currently have as a target may seem easy to defend
because it has a simple structure and only a few entrances,
but it makes it that much harder to
escape after the operation is over.
Also, since it is separated from the surrounding buildings,
it makes it easier for the special forces and
the SWAT team to carry out their operations.
A building with more exits leading outside
and a complex structure is better for our side.
With our current forces,
it's impossible.
What we need right now isn't more men, but more time.
If we take over each spot at a certain time as planned
and install booby traps on each entrance
and install weapons in case of a forced
entry after that, then it's fully possible.
For now, I think we should change our target
and make a new plan for the attack.
Look through it again from the beginning.
Uhm.
Stay outside for a bit.
I looked into it,
and it seems like someone is being held
prisoner on the second basement level,
and only the director is going in and out of there.
You don't know who it is?
No, I couldn't get that far...
Alright. Good work.
Ah, yes.
All plans are being reassessed right now.
Yes.
I will find D-day again.
I will do as ordered for the Choi Seung Hee issue.
Yes, sir.
You won't have to worry.
Come in.
What is it?
I have something to say, sir.
Sit.
What is it that you wanted to say?
Honestly,
I'm very confused right now.
Why?
It's because of this situation,
where there are a lot of things that I'm
wondering about, but cannot find out.
Go on.
What is my position within the organization?
The fact that I can only be told
the true identity of the organization...
that I'm devoting my life to by you is frustrating.
And?
I'm also curious...
about the relationship between you and Choi Seung Hee.
Your treatment towards Choi Seung Hee
is sometimes something so special,
that it would risk the dangers of the organization.
What is the reason...
you're treating her and caring her for?
My answer is extremely clear and simple.
Knowing what you should know,
at your current position,
is what allows this huge organization to
continue its existence and maintain itself.
Unnecessary questions make you fall into danger.
Although I do understand what your concern is,
since you are already in the organization's core,
you don't have to be confused.
Also,
throw away all the questions you have about Choi Seung Hee.
This is not an advice, but a warning.
If you have Choi Seung Hee within your heart,
then that is the most dangerous thing of all.
[National Guard First Division]
Come in.
I'm sorry I called you in while you were resting.
It's alright sir.
Sit.
When I was investigating defense
commander Rhee Tae Jun a while ago,
I arrested someone who had a connection
between Rhee Tae Jun and IRIS.
In this, there is information that
was acquired during his investigation.
Although there isn't much we've figured out since
we couldn't get much from the investigation,
I'm pretty sure there's a new conspiracy
being prepared in South Korea.
This is a matter important enough to put a stop to the summit.
As a man responsible for security,
I cannot let comrade chairman go to South Korea
when I know there is a cause for danger there.
Seon Hwa, you should've found out a lot about
IRIS while you were with Kim Hyun Joon.
I was hoping you would analyze this information
before we discuss this matter with South Korea.
Alright sir.
Come in.
I think IRIS attempted to rescue director
Baek San associates with armed men.
Wasn't there any news from South Korea?
No, there wasn't.
Even if something like that happened,
they have no reason to let us know.
I will also...
go to South Korea.
Is there a reason you suddenly changed your mind?
Alright.
I'll arrange things for that, so get ready.
Section chief!
Oh! You came in at the right time.
- I was actually going to go to you.
- Did the results come out?
Ah. Here.
They were footprints left at the scene.
Although they're of different sizes,
the type of shoes were all the same.
They're special shoes manufactured by Temith in America for military use,
and they're usually used by foreign
dispatches or private militaries.
Good work.
Oh!
Check the immigration records of the
suspect for Yang Mi Jung's murder.
There is one strong potential, a Canadian national by the name of Harrison.
and there was a record of him entering
Canada using the name Harrisons.
Alright. I'll take care of this, so go
to section chief Oh Hyung Kyu right now.
Tell him I sent you for a more thorough i
investigation on the footprints.
Yes, sir.
- Sunbae.
- Just a second.
How far is the analysis on the satellite images?
This is all for the current satellite images.
There's one that shows them going into the tunnel,
but there isn't one going out.
That's why I checked,
and I think they used some sort of device
to disrupt the satellite signal.
At this point, it's impossible to
do any further data recovery.
There's no other way but to make a list of possible routes
and target locations by applying an algorithm for a Steiner tree.
Then please analyze this also.
What is it?
It's the immigration record of the suspect
for Yang Mi Jung's murder.
Because he might've used a forged passport,
please check to see if he has any
other additional immigration records,
and do a triangulation analysis on his period of immigration
and the countries he came from.
Alright.
What is it?
It came out during the analysis of the pictures on Mi Jung's blog.
Take a look.
It's wine.
So?
Mi Jung never drank wine.
Looking at the import tag, it must
have been imported legally,
and it's a limited edition sold for collectors.
Investigate the exporter and the buyer.
Yes, sir.
What happened? With even your cell phone turned off?
Everyone was worried something might've
also happened to you after Mi Jung died.
Mi Jung died?
She was attacked by a suspected IRIS killer.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I mean, what is it?
R-right now...
it's hard to say.
Nothing happened, and I came back safely.
Please just let it pass.
Choi Seung Hee!
What were you doing before showing up like this?
I'm sorry, sir.
I'll listen to your excuses later.
First off, analyze this and do some profiling.
Yes, sir.
There's no time. Finish it quickly.
For now, I'll take care of this first.
Is the director...
safe?
Yes.
Where is he right now?
I can't tell you that.
If you have anything to say to him, say it to me.
This is the data the director requested.
My answer is extremely clear and simple.
Knowing what you should know,
at your current position,
is what allows this huge organization to
continue its existence and maintain itself.
Unnecessary questions make you fall into danger.
Also,
throw away all the questions you have about Choi Seung Hee.
This is not an advice, but a warning.
If you have Choi Seung Hee within your heart,
then that is the most dangerous thing of all.
Don't move!
Try and shoot me!
Just like how you did it to Hyun Joon, shoot me!
Choi Seung Hee.
I've looked at the analysis
and I think I should first make a list of private
military companies by referencing the weapons
and communication devices they used.
- Talk with me for a bit.
- Let's have that conversation later.
Right now, I...
Pick up your call.
It's alright.
If you really don't want to say it,
I won't ask anymore.
However, I have one thing to ask.
When you were being held hostage,
Kang Do Chul, who was interrogating you,
received a call from somewhere and freed you.
Aren't you curious as to how you were freed?
I was also curious about that,
but I don't know why.
I'm only worried that something might happen to you,
after what happened to Mi Jung.
Even though our enemy is director Baek San and Sa Woo,
they might...
still want you as a target.
Continue your work.
Secretary Jeong Hyung Jun
and public relations officer Hong Soon Il have arrived.
Escort them here.
Yes, Kim Hyun Joon here.
It's me.
I'm in Seoul right now.
I came along with the summit administration.
I really need to meet up with you.
I heard that you've become the executive
of the summit administration.
Yes.
I was somehow handed an important task.
How are the investigations on
Baek San and Jin Sa Woo going?
Well we're still working on it,
but we haven't been able to obtain any leads yet.
From what I can see, they should be plotting
another scheme to stop the summit.
During the investigations on associated
individuals with the coup d'état on our side,
- someone who was connected with IRIS...
- Just a moment.
Will you leave us for a moment?
Sorry?
It's because I have something personal to say.
Yes, sir.
Please go on.
It's me, sir.
I'm sure Park Chul Young has figured out something.
He's telling that to the Presidential Secretary
Jung Hyung Joon right now.
Yes, sir.
And Presidential Secretary Jung Hyung Joon is suspecting me.
During the investigation of those who participated in the coup,
a file related to IRIS came up.
I analyzed that data
and it was talking about Choi Seung Hee.
Seung Hee?
I'm wondering if IRIS is looking at
Choi Seung Hee as a target to eliminate.
From what I think,
Choi Seung Hee is in danger.
For now, I'll report this to the president
and discuss it with him.
If we have to adjust the arrangements for the summit,
please contact me quickly.
I'll do that.
No!
He's the only possible lead we have on
Baek San and Jin Sa Woo's whereabouts.
We have to chase him.
How can we break apart?
How can we break apart,
I don't know what to say.
when my heart won't let you go?
Hug me.
When the only place I can go to rest is you
Is our love
Is our love finished just like this?
What is the reason you became a terrorist
even though you said you used to be an NSS agent?
I don't think I'll ever be able to come back to you.
Is this really the last time?
Erase me from all your memories, Seung Hee.
Is there no next time for us anymore?
Do we have to live our lives getting hurt by loneliness,
with it all buried in our hearts?
Please tell me. What happened?
If we could turn back time, go back to that day
Sorry.
I-I couldn't tell you that Seung Hee was alive.
and spend another day
Sa Woo.
How can we break apart?
How can we break apart,
when my heart won't let you go?
Why did you change like this?
When the only place I can go to rest is you
Couldn't we just
Love like this?
If you weren't here, I'd live in tears
Even though I want you so much...
I love you can't you come back to me?
I feel like I'm dying because I want to see you
I can't even feel pain because my heart is worn out
Please come back to me I love you
It feels like you'll come back I wait for you everyday
I cannot bear to hide my feelings
I'm sorry I hurt you a lot
I'll live protecting you by your side forever
My love can't stop since my heart is hurt
I guess I can't do without you
Please come back to me I love you