IRIS
Chul Young, kidnapped by Hyun Jun,
comes to the decision to help Hyun Jun stop the war.
Seon Hwa and Hyun Jun
run into Seung Hee at the bunker,
where the bomb was assembled.
With Seung Hee's help in holding Sa Woo back,
Seon Hwa and Hyun Jun make their escape.
Don't come any closer.
What made you change like that?
Chul Young agrees to Secretary Jeong appeal,
for help to arrest Yeon Gi Hoon,
who ends up being assassinated by another secret plan.
Jo Myung Ho has Baek San and Sa Woo arrested,
in the hopes that they would be of help in locating the bomb.
Where is the bomb located?
With Chul Young's help,
Seon Hwa and Hyun Jun figure out
the bomb is planned to explode
at Kwang Hwa Mun and head there...
Episode 17
This is the spot that overlaps
from all the locations they've visited,
per their navigation system.
Kwang Hwa Mun, Deoksukung,
NamDaemun Market, Seoul Station,
USO,
Yong San Station,
Central Public Museum,
War Memorial, US military base Yong San...
Kwang Hwa Mun.
Come with me!
Look in the cargo area!
The cargo!
I need everybody to please exit the bus now.
Exit the bus now!
It's not in the luggage area.
Run!
Ongoing crisis situation.
In the Kwang Hwa Mun Plaza...
[Live Gunfire battle breaks out in Kwang Hwa Mun Plaza]
...a gunfire battle has broken out,
and many have been killed.
The shots are continuous,
and the authorities have yet arrive.
[Police action delayed as number of fatalities continue to rise]
The area surrounding Kwang Hwa Mun has no communication signals
and the reason has not yet been confirmed.
However...
We're...
going to Kwang Hwa Mun.
This is happening live.
I'll go with you to the end.
Cap, I will also go with you to the end.
Get down!
Hwang Soo!
Get out of the way!
I'll cover you,
the two of you get away!
Run!
Get away!
For people...
of Joseon...
The President is entering.
I'm sure you were all shocked
by the Kwang Hwa Mun incident,
and probably have many questions.
I will now tell you,
all that you want to know.
Who were the people involved?
They were,
extremists of...
the Labor Party of North Korea.
They'd planned...
the terroristic act of blowing up
a bomb at Kwang Hwa Mun,
but our security knew about it,
and was able to block the act,
and all the terrorist members have been killed.
If extremists from the North,
can enter our country and plan such an act
in a public place such as Kwang Hwa Mun,
shouldn't there be,
further investigation to determine
if their party has reinforcements here?
It is true that the terrorists were members
of the Labor Party of North Korea,
but we've confirmed,
that the Minister of Defense was not involved.
Those terrorists came here to create chaos,
with plans to use that as an excuse to start a war.
Their true intention was to carry
out a coup dՎtat in the North,
at the moment of the bomb explosion in Seoul.
I had been planning a summit conference with the North.
To ensure the success of the plan,
I had no choice but to keep it a secret,
and I ask for your understanding in why I did so.
In light of what happened,
are you planning to go through with the summit?
Yes.
It may be delayed a little from the original schedule,
but I'm going to make certain this summit does,
indeed, take place.
It's me.
The President has not changed his mind.
Yes.
He is planning to go through
with the summit as planned.
With the latest incident, the NSS organization,
as it currently operates,
has lost the confidence of the National Assembly,
and even the authority to continue
operating in the current mode.
The President has taken this
to heart and desires special conditions
be placed on the organization if it is to continue operating.
There was no check and balance system
to oversee the activities,
and as such, it has rotted to the core.
The NSS whose head turned out
to be a traitor,
the NSS who was powerless
to stop the terrorists and instead,
opened the doors to them...
I will not,
allow that to continue.
We will take strong action to cut off the rotten parts,
and anyone who gets in the way of formation of
a new organization will also be cut off..
Now, get back to your work.
How dare he come in here spouting off his threats?
Even the Director turned out to be a traitor.
So what is there that they won't do now?
Did I...
say something wrong?
Everything he said in there,
was right.
You know,
stagnant water stinks.
We went along with...
Are you saying we stink?
Are you already calculating which rope to climb?
You must think that person in there is a strong rope,
but to me,
he looks pretty tattered.
You...
don't know when your rope will break,
so be careful as you...
Oh goodness,
I got poked!
Oh man,
he drives me crazy.
Hoo boy, it's not going to be easy around here.
It's me.
What?
Okay.
We found out where Hyun Jun is being held.
Where?
The National Assembly investigation facilities.
Director Baek San and Jin Sa Woo
are also being interrogated there.
Do you think...
I could see Hyun Jun?
Let's wait a little.
I hear the Blue House has showed
continued interest in Hyun Jun,
so we should hear something soon.
How is the investigation of IRIS going?
To identify who in the Blue House,
and our government are members of IRIS,
we need Baek San's cooperation,
but thus far, we've had no luck.
Getting to the true core of IRIS,
and how far its influence reaches,
have not been determined yet.
If we can't find out who's giving orders to Baek San,
they will continue to interfere with the summit.
We must find out who that is.
Yes, sir.
Oh by the way, where is Kim Hyun Jun?
He's being interrogated by the National Assembly.
You assassinated Yoon Sung Chul,
then escaped from Hungary,
passed through Russia, then went to Japan.
In Akita, Japan, you met up with Kim Seon Hwa,
then through her, you hooked up
with terrorist Park Chul Young.
Is that correct?
Yes.
That you knew they were North
Koreans working underground,
and still aligned yourself with them
was to alienate yourself,
from your country and you sought
to take revenge against it.
Why did you do that?
The only thoughts I had were to take revenge against
the country and Director Baek San who threw me away.
After failing to protect Yoon Sung Chul,
I was called back to North Korea,
and subsequently, incarcerated.
Then you received orders to kill Kim Hyun Jun,
so you went to Japan?
Yes.
You stated that you failed to kill Kim Hyun Jun,
and ended up staying in the same house.
Can you tell me how that could have been possible?
Furthermore, you stated that you worked with Kim Hyun Jun,
to stop the planned nuclear terrorism.
What reasons would cause you to point
a gun at your fellow countrymen?
Tell me.
Now, let's talk about Jin Sa Woo.
Weren't you two,
best friends from the time you were in the Special Forces?
Yes.
But he tried to kill you.
When do you think Jin Sa Woo became a part of  IRIS?
I don't know.
Was he really your friend?
What do you know about Jin Sa Woo?
Tell me whatever you know.
You were always like that.
You never knew anything about me.
Because of you,
do you know how much pain I've suffered?
do you know what I had to give up?
You never had any idea.
What difference does it make for you to know since when?
How could that mean anything at this point?
I went to kill you,
and from that moment,
you ceased to exist in my heart!
She's an employee at the company
of my hometown friend.
I can't talk because I'm trembling so much.
She's completely my style.
She's a killer.
Why are you doing this to us?
Your pain during that brief time,
was probably quite extreme.
Just think of it,
as a rite of passage to becoming NSS agents.
There's already someone that you've avowed
your love for, for the rest of your life.
The one you met in graduate school a while back.
That was Seung Hee.
It wasn't until the day we went
to Vice Director's house for dinner,
after Hyun Jun joined the NSS,
that we became close.
That day...
It's because that was the day of our first kiss.
I'm sorry.
This was an order.
If you were me, you would've...
Do you know what I'm really afraid of?
The fact that I pulled you into NSS.
I thought of you as more than a hometown friend,
I thought of you as my younger brother.
Please don't say any more.
Tell me.
Why are you doing this?
For whom,
for what are you doing this?!
Hurry up and tell me,
since when.
When you pulled the gun on me in Hungary,
what were you then?
Were you a member of IRIS...
or were you my friend?
You spilling your heart now,
what would that change?
If I understand the reasons for your actions,
Even if Hyun Jun forgives you,
I will never forgive you.
It's so peaceful, as if nothing ever happened here.
If that nuclear bomb did explode...
I don't even want to imagine it.
You've done far more than your duty,
in blocking that terroristic act.
If you're,
holding on to any feelings of guilt
over the assassination of Yoon Sung Chul
or attacking NSS with the terrorists,
it'll be good for you to shake it off.
Oh, right.
I now owe you twice for my life.
Let's sit.
We've crossed a major hurdle,
but there is still much work to be done.
The list you mentioned,
of the IRIS members that are not complete,
trying to get the information out of Baek San has not been successful.
I'm hoping you can get it done.
To ask you to relive the nightmare you've
suffered might be asking for too much.
But if we can't identify all the members of IRIS,
it may make it difficult for me to accomplish what I have planned.
Currently,
you're the best candidate to get the job done.
I would like to ask you to do this.
I have a request to make of you.
What is it?
Tell me whatever it is you want.
Please sit.
Should you need my help with anything,
press the button underneath the desk.
I'm sure there's a lot you want to say.
Don't beat around the bush and let's get started.
Do you want me to start?
I'm sure you've met Dr. Yoo Jeong Hoon,
and since you've looked at the file in my NSS storage,
you must know as much as you could about me.
As you already know,
I killed your parents.
I wasn't given the reason for why I had to kill them,
just the order itself.
Was it IRIS that gave you the order?
It turned out to be so,
but, at the time,
I didn't know anything about IRIS.
Just like when you received
your order to kill Yoon Sung Chul,
I also thought,
it was for my country and NSS.
But...
the order I received,
was to kill you as well.
I disobeyed that order,
and saved your life.
Why did you?
Why did you save my life?
I'm not sure.
As you live life, there are times,
when you just want to do something
without any special reason for it.
Your life became
as I had designed.
Your life should have ended already,
but the fact that you're here now,
is because of me.
If you were responsible for my life,
why did you throw me away?
Asking me that,
is the same as,
asking me to tell you
everything about the organization I serve.
That is,
a secret that I must take,
to my grave.
Tell me!
Tell me why you saved my life then threw me away!
Tell me quickly!
Take him away.
Ah,
I will tell you one thing.
You were being punished for eating,
the forbidden fruit.
The life I designed for you,
did not allow for you to do that.
In your current emotional state,
I don't think you'll be able to meet with Jin Sa Woo.
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Bring Jin Sa Woo.
What is this about?
Kim Hyun Jun wanted to see you.
I have nothing to say.
Let's go.
Sa Woo.
If you believe that,
our relationship was real for even one second,
please don't make me more pathetic than I already am.
Please.
It's okay to let him sit.
These are the results of the interrogation up to now.
In 1995,
when the 6th Corp of Army,
attempted the coup dՎtat,
I recall you to be the person to lead
the army in that attempt
as well as,
being the person, who initiated the act in the first place.
This latest coup attempt,
no one caught on until the very last moment.
What do you believe to be the reason for that?
Could it be because you,
as the Supreme Commander of Security,
were working with Minister Yeon Gi Hoon?
I will ask you for the record,
are you a part of IRIS?
I don't know anything about,
what you've just stated.
Let me ask you again,
in our Party, who else are receiving orders from IRIS?
I don't know what you're talking about.
The way you're trembling,
you look like a rain-drenched puppy.
You're going to die anyway.
Isn't it humiliating for you to be so stubborn to the end?
You...
If I were you, I would,
act like the soldier that I am
and die upholding the code of honor.
I will ask for the final time,
who in our Party receives orders from IRIS?
What's happening with Kim Seon Hwa?
With the support of the South Korean President,
I believe she will be released shortly.
But when she returns here,
surely she can't avoid the due process?
We'll have to do what we can to stop it.
May we have some time alone?
We have to leave soon.
Please make it short.
You could have stayed here...
or have chosen to go to another country.
I know that you've made a special request
to the President on my behalf.
But,
I'm going home.
You don't have anyone there...
Not your mother,
not your brother.
Isn't that the same for me here?
Chasing you through,
the snow storm in Akita,
seems like just yesterday.
That day...
In that mountain cabin,
the butter coffee you made for me...
I don't think I'll ever forget the taste of it.
I...
Would it be okay for me to ask for a favor?
Thinking about it, I realized,
that you've never called me,
by my name.
If it weren't for you,
I would never have made it to this point.
Thank you for being with me.
Seon Hwa.
It's time to leave.
I love you still
I miss you much
Is it not possible for you to come to me?
}I love you, can't you come to me?
I miss you so much that I think I might die
I don't have the strength to cast off this pain
Please come to me.
This is your final chance.
I love you.
He's in Japan right now.
Go get him.
What is the reason you're doing this for me?
I came here to kill you.
So,
why...?
What is your reason?
Why do you have to do this?
I'm sorry for causing you pain
I will live, keep your heart safe forever
I can't stop the love from flowing from my heart
Don't try so hard for me anymore.
I don't think it's possible for me to be without you.
Please come to me. I love you.
You are now free to go.
When your parents died,
they were cremated,
and their ashes scattered in the Buk Han River.
This should,
tell you the location of that spot.
Director Baek San asked to,
pass this on to you.
Director.
Is there something wrong?
You didn't even attend the meeting.
You're really acting strange today.
What's wrong with you?
Hey, Mi Jeong...
That...
Minister of National Security or whatever...
I don't think I can work with him.
I mean... "don't do this, don't do that"...
what am I supposed to do?
What is he not allowing you to do?
Monitoring my stocks.
He just blocked all access to it.
Do you know how far down I am on my stocks?
Just give me the report on the analysis.
Oh!
Mi Jeong!
You can unblock me on the server, right?
No, I can't.
From now on, I'm not going to do
anything that I'm not permitted.
Hey, Mi Jeong.
Mi Jeong.
Just this once.
Hey, Mi Jeong!
Just this one time.
No, I can't.
Mi Jeong!
- No, I can't.
Come on, just this...
You!
You really did come back alive.
Have you been well?
Me? What's there to well about?
I'm just getting along.
Have you been well?
Yes.
I knew your life wouldn't be easy
just by the shape of your face but...
Wow, who knew you'd go through all that!
He's here.
Hyun Jun sunbae is here.
Sunbae!
You've been good?
You're here?
Okay.
Then good luck to all of you.
I've got things to do.
How have you all been?
Let's save the greetings for later,
and take care of business first.
How can an NSS agent such as yourself,
not be able to conceal your emotions?
What's wrong with me?
It's written all over your face,
I - Love - You - Kim - Hyun - Jun!
Regardless, it's been a long time since I've seen
such a happy expression on your face.
Hello.
I don't know the reason for
the President's special favor with you,
but personally, I,
find it hard to understand your previous actions.
If you have any
thoughts to attack NSS,
know that I will not stand for it.
Kim Hyun Jun was,
NSS' top agent.
Additionally, during the recent terrorist attack...
Isn't it a fact,
that you were a part of the team,
that planned it?
That's a situation,
you should examine once again.
His views are a bit cynical.
Everyone's suffering under him so try,
and be understanding.
There's a lot I'm curious about,
and I have a million things to say,
but we'll take our time with it.
For now, get some rest.
I'll let the others know as much.
Yes, sir.
Section Chief,
do you know of the dead spot that our close-circuit
monitoring system doesn't cover?
No.
Well, I think Kim Hyun Jun sunbae knows where.
Team Leader Choi Seung Hee
asked you to meet her there.
Oh, these two...
What are you going to do there?
I'd like to know that myself.
You don't have to worry about your surroundings.
This is the only area within NSS,
that isn't monitored by CCTV.
Ahh, yes.
So is there,
something you have to tell me in secret?
Kim Hyun Jun.
Do I seem easy to you?
Or, does the NSS organization seem like a joke to you?
I'm your superior,
and the NSS absolutely will not tolerate
personal relationships between agents.
Keep that in mind.
Do you know why I entered the NSS?
The reason I entered NSS was...
I looked at this dangerous and complicated
organization quite simply.
I thought, "So if I just risk my life,
I can continue doing something I find exciting,
something that feels like my destiny.
I...
From the very first moment I met you in the lecture hall,
I've never once thought you were easy.
And...
This...
is not a joke to me.
Is there something you need to tell me in secret?
What were you thinking?
About that time,
when I brought you here
for the first time.
You said, "The reason I entered NSS was..."
"I looked at this dangerous and complicated
organization quite simply."
"So if I just,"
"...risk my life,"
"I can continue doing something I find exciting,"
"something that feels like my destiny."
You said those words to me.
Do you remember?
Yes.
Do you still feel the same way?
I don't know.
I'm saying things that are unnecessary.
I heard you were interrogated by the Assembly.
Let's just rest for now
You look really tired.
I lasted a day because
you said you loved me.
I lasted a month because
Of that gaze staring at me.
I'll love you, I'll wait for you.
The house is a total mess.
The words I couldn't say, the words I wanted to say
I'll say them now.
I love you.
Why are you standing there so awkwardly?
You act like you've never been here before.
Let's think about dinner first.
What should we have for dinner?
Oh, squash patties.
We can do that.
And Soybean paste stew.
We have toasted seaweed and,
oh, we can make egg custard...
That I can have moments like this again,
I could never have imagined it.
I keep thinking it's a dream that I'll wake from,
and that scares me.
The dream,
is what you went through.
And this is the absolute reality.
It won't vanish so you can rest easy.
If we had met and loved
during different times, different place
would we be happy right now?
For the rest of my life
It should have been you
But now it will only be my staggering figure
Since I can't hate you
Or forget you
I guess
There's nothing left for me to do,
Hyun Jun, dinner's ready.
Other than to love you.
Hyun Jun.
If I can for just one day
let my heart rest,
Forget you and breathe a little easier.
For the rest of my life
it should have been you,
I guess there's nothing left for me to do,
other than to love you.
You're really not going to tell me what happened to you?
Forget it if you don't want to.
What are you doing?
You'll break open your wounds.
I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
Tell me.
There is still no progress from interviewing Baek San.
So we haven't been able to
identify any more members?
That's correct.
What about from anyone on the list,
from Kim Hyun Jun?
They've all left the country.
I believe,
perhaps we need to change the focus of our investigation.
We will focus on areas other than the government
and,
look for people that worked with Baek San.
By other areas,
what do you mean specifically?
Well, I suppose we'll have to look at
other people with security clearances.
I understand the officials from the North will be returning.
Yes.
We're currently looking at the middle
of next month for the summit.
Please take special care to not allow
anything to change our plans.
Yes, sir.
You're acting strange.
What?
How?
You're acting like a person being chased.
Is something wrong?
No.
Section Chief!
Eh?
Oh?
I'll unblock your access on the server.
What did you just say?
Really?
Okay, so if you do that,
I'll give you a great stock tip.
I'll help you make a lot of money, I will.
I don't have any interest in that.
Just give me your key card for the main server.
Why?
Because I don't have the authority
to access the main server.
Oh, right.
That's right.
Keep this a secret just between us!
The Assembly sent the transport plans
for Baek San and Jin Sa Woo.
The convoy will have top level security.
Is there anything we should do?
Until the transport is successfully completed,
NSS won't have to do anything.
By the way,
where is Kim Hyun Jun?
Why are you asking for him?
There was a request,
to include him on the transport security team.
I think that might be difficult.
I believe it would be better
to leave him alone for the time being.
I didn't really like the idea of it anyway.
Okay, let him do that.
When did you get up?
Just now.
Do you know how many hours you've slept?
Exactly,
33 hours.
I kept thinking there was something wrong.
You just wouldn't wake up.
Aren't you hungry?
I'm hungry.
Very.
Wait just a bit.
I'll make something good for you.
How could you sleep for so long?
It must be because there were no nightmares.
Ever since I left Hungary,
it was hard to sleep even for 2 hours.
Even if I did sleep,
I kept having these dreadful nightmares.
That's all because of me.
I prayed that you wouldn't have any nightmares.
I just got some vacation time.
Do you want to go somewhere?
Where?
Anywhere as long as it's a place, you can rest at.
Before we go, there's someplace we need to stop by.
Where is that?
I was waiting for you.
What is all this?
Reward for accepting, my request.
Sit.
Okay.
When your parents died,
they were cremated,
and their ashes scattered in the Buk Han River.
What is your name?
Kim Hyun Jun.
The...
the thing I asked for.
I set it up so you can get to it from my PC.
I saved the code on this.
Thank you.
Mommy!
When you were captured,
you were released with just one phone call.
Aren't you curious as to why you were released?
I don't want to return...
to South Korea.
Is it because of Kim Hyun Jun?
Peggy is waiting for you.
You must go,
with me.