IRIS
Episode 9
Hyun Jun carries out an assassination
per the deal he made with Japanese Intelligence,
and then safely escapes.
The demands of the Yuki's kidnapper
puts Hong Seung Ryong's necklace in his hands.
The South Korean President,
excluding NSS in the plans,
invites a high official of North Korea to meet.
Hyun Jun and Seon Hwa retrieve information
from Hong Seung Ryong's necklace,
and they see Baek San's name in the member list of IRIS.
They go to Shanghai, China to meet Chul Young…
Please sit down.
Episode 9
I believed and trusted to the end
that you'd return.
I said I believed and trusted in you.
So what is this about?
Did you already forget
what I ordered you to do?
I asked her to arrange this meeting.
I need your help.
You're a person that killed
our meritorious Prime Minister.
And you're asking for a favor...
from the person who was in charge of protecting him?
Do you really think that makes sense?
You and I both do as we're ordered.
I just followed the order I was given,
and you were following your orders to stop me.
In the end,
you are safe...
but I was abandoned.
I want revenge against
those that used me,
and then discarded me.
How can I trust you?
I lost everything.
Even the woman I loved.
The only thing I have left is...
this miserable life.
If I put my life in your hands,
would you then trust me?
[Taeryun Port, China]
Bring it in straight.
Prepare to leave port.
We leave in 5 minutes.
Sun Soo, Sun Mi, anchor up!
You, over there!
Come here.
Who's in charge of this boat?
He's in the control room.
What's the problem?
We received a report that someone on this
boat has been infected with a very serious virus.
What?
This boat is forbidden to leave,
until we've completed our investigation.
Is this everybody?
Yes, everyone is here.
What are you doing?
I sent all the e-mails with information
about the overseas offices.
I organized them for you.
Please check them.
Oh, okay.
Good job.
By the way,
were you able to identify the person
the Japanese Intelligence Office asked about?
Oh...  I did check it out.
He is of no interest to us,
and I reported as such.
Okay... I understand.
Oh, it's Hyun Jun sunbae!
This is Hyun Jun sunbae, isn't it?
When is that from?
Oh!
It's from our initiation test.
Oh, I see.
But you shouldn't have this in your possession.
We were supposed to delete or hand over
everything we had on Hyun Jun sunbae.
If the Internal Investigation office finds out
you still have this, it'll be bad.
Oh, it was the last thing I had on him,
so it was hard for me let it go.
I was just about to erase it.
Was there something else?
Oh yeah, we're going on an MT (Meeting Trip)
to celebrate Team Leader Choi Seung Hee's return.
Oh really?
When?
The day after tomorrow.
Jin Sa Woo has been covering your duties.
Go over with him what you need
for the hand off.
Yes.
It's possible that a major
event is about to take place.
I'm relieved to have you back for that.
What are you talking about?
We may be receiving a visit by a
very important guest from North Korea.
Didn't the Director say anything to you?
No.
Yeah, I guess the Director isn't himself these days.
Why is that?
The underlings don't know,
so keep it to yourself.
A month ago, a high official came
and met with our President.
But we were excluded from that whole event.
Since the organization's inception,
this is the first time that's happened.
The Director is very nervous about the situation.
Anyway, you just returned and
your work is being loaded on you.
After the MT, get started right away.
Okay.
Who are you?
NSS Terrorist Team agent, Kim Hyun Jun.
What is NSS?
An organization to protect the country
and the President in secret service.
Your responsibilities?
Working against terrorism and…
any order received.
Did you assassinate Yoon Sung Chul?
That was my final mission.
Was the order to assassinate
Yoon Sung Chul from NSS?
Answer the question.
I don't know.
I carried out the mission believing so,
but now I'm not sure.
What was the reason you came
here looking for Park Chul Young?
I needed help for my revenge.
Who is the target of your revenge?
Baek San, the Vice Director of NSS.
And…
the nation of Korea,
which used me and then threw me away.
Just because you passed this test
doesn't mean I can trust you.
This is the true beginning.
If you pass all the tests
and make me trust in you,
only then will I help you.
He was member of our security team
who defected to South Korea.
He's now on our blacklist.
You must take care of him.
Will you do it?
We'll be arriving soon.
Go down to the freezer locker
and recruit a few people.
What is it?
We need a few people
to help with our entry.
Select ones that are married with children.
Hallelujah, I'm fallin', I'm fallin', fallin'
To a fallen building, hey
Hallelujah (yes) I'm fallin‘ (yes)
I'm fallin' fallin‘
shimmy shimmy yo 1, 2 step action
mission complete (no doubt)
The empty streets at dawn
I'm a "die-alone",
if not cold-blooded I fail
I, to my changing commands,
my soldier type
Don't touch me Big Bang is dynamite
Boom! Throw my life
away along with the sound
The mission that's begun,
dealing with the situation is thumbs up
To us, love is a luxury
There's no blood or tears here,
this is the rule
I shout out yet again today
I give a small prayer,
Yes?
We're approaching.
We'll be going through customs soon.
up there
Everything ready?
The miracle that'll happen to me,
We're all set.
Initiate.
push me to the waves, I hate it,
I understand.
I lost myself
Hallelujah (yes), I'm fallin',
I'm fallin', fallin'
To a fallen building
(Taeyang in the boom) Hallelujah
[Pusan - Kam Chun Port]
I'm fallin' (yes) I'm fallin' (yes) fallin'
shimmy shimmy yo 1,2 step action
mission complete (no doubt)
- Hello.
- Ah...
Welcome back from your hard working trip.
The boats we saw yesterday
didn't fare very well.
Did you catch a lot of fish?
We didn't get to fill the boat this time.
Oh, really?
Let's go have a look.
Is there anything special you need to declare?
Such as explosives, illegal
weapons, perfumes, electronics?
No, we don't.
Yes, let's go take a look in the storage.
Excuse us while you work.
Nothing unusual, right?
Keep up the good work.
Pull it up.
Okay, on to the next one.
Let's take a look over there.
Why is this one empty?
As I told you, the fishing wasn't good
so we had none to put in here.
Tsk, tsk, tsk. That's a big problem.
We're not seeing very many workers.
I'm sure this is the right boat.
I have a hometown friend named Ahn Ki Nam,
and I'm sure this was the boat he was on.
I don't see him anywhere.
Ahn Ki Nam?
- Yes.  Isn't this the boat?
- Yes, yes.
He got sick when we were setting out,
running a fever over 40 C.
He's recovering in a hospital
in Kee Li Bas right now.
Oh, is that so?
Is he all right?
I'm sure he'll be fine.
Everything seems to be in order.
Go ahead and begin your unloading procedures.
All right.
Reporting inspection of SL boat, complete.
- They are proceeding with unloading.
- Yes.
Continue your good work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Close Circuit TV recording erased.
Okay.
Hello and welcome to the jewelry
store that can express your love.
I see.
Are you looking for a wedding gift?
Ah! No, not exactly.
I'd like something that won't make
the recipient too uncomfortable.
Are you going to propose?
Yes… something like…
Do you know your girlfriend's size?
I'm sorry?
I meant her ring size.
Oh, I see.
I don't think I know.
Then how about this?
It's a pendant that's said to
make fateful love possible.
Ah, the weather is so great.
I don't care e e e e e e.
- I don't care e e e e e e.
Are you okay now?
I'm not laughing because I'm happy.
But if I do laugh, I can become happy.
I've been too sensitive with you lately,
haven't I?
As long as you're okay,
I can take much more.
So get angry, throw tantrums,
throw hissy fits… do it all.
I never threw hissy fits.
Just… don't cry.
That's something I just couldn't handle.
- You guys stop working and eat something.
- Yes. The meat…
Is something wrong?
Why do you look so down?
Hey you,
did you by any chance have your heart
set on the Team Leader position,
and now you're disappointed
because Choi Seung Hee came back?
Wow, Manager Hwang, you're pretty sharp.
- You… really…
- I…
But he's saying this just to be funny.
Aissh...
I wasn't trying to be…
You!
Why are you here so late?
- ... you're here…?
- Sorry.
Choi Seung Hee, why are you so late?
What is this…
- What did you bring?
- Seung Hee, come over here.
Okay.
These drinks won't do.
- Why don't you make us some bombs?
- All right.
Ah… this is nice.
Keep pouring.
Pour...Pour...Pour...
- Manager, will you be okay?
- Keep going...
- Good....
- I've had enough.
Good.
This is the best.
Tae Hyung, pass these on.
- All right.
- I'm fine. You go ahead.
I announce the return of Choi Seung Hee!
How many times do you
have to announce that?
Forget it…
Uh, for Yang Jeong In and…
Choi Seung Hee, this is to hope that we can...
get these wrinkled old maids married off!
- Oh, Manager.
Here, here!
Ahhh, there's no question that Choi Seung Hee is...
the best at making the bombs.
I am the best, aren't I?
- Oh...
- Give me one.
Give me one.
You can never quit.
Where else can we go have these drinks?
I'll make them for you often.
Make one more for me.
Me, too.
- You...
- Me, too.
One!
Two!
- Three!
Love shot!
Kiss!
Okay, second round… start!
One!
- Two!
Love shot!
Kiss!
- Kiss!
- Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss!
Stop!
Yah yah...
This is really unfair.
It's fine to do a love shot if you get a girl,
but what's this with a guy?
Oh, really.
Manager!
I'll do it for you.
That's fine, just fine.
- Hey Mi Jeong,…
- Yes?
You sing us a song.
A song!
I'm feeling a little depressed,
so I'm going to turn the mood here
upside down.
If I say I hurt, it really might be painful.
If I say I'm sad,
I'm afraid the tears will come.
So I just smile.
But why do people keep
asking why I'm crying?
I don't have a heart.
So it's not possible for me to hurt.
I talk to myself.
I ask myself.
But the tears keep coming.
If I say I hurt, it really might be painful.
If I say I'm sad, I'm afraid the tears will come.
That's enough.
So I just smile.
Hey, Mi Jeong…
But why do people keep asking why I'm crying?
That's enough!
That's enough.
- Wow, that was really…
- Yeah..
Now that it's dark, it's getting cold.
- Do you want my jacket?
- No, I'm fine.
Thank you.
For what?
Just because.
For a lot of things.
Even if I'm smiling, I struggle inside still.
But thanks to you, I'm a lot better.
You'll continue to be my friend?
You are my love,
You're the love given to me,
But you're trying to leave.
What shall I do?
Shall I just wait for you?
Shall I just live on alone?
I'm standing here alone.
Is this love?
We finally got to this point.
Are you okay?
Hey, once we get into action,
don't ever stand in front of him.
You never know when a bullet
might come at you from behind.
Even betrayal becomes a habit.
You really want to say
those useless things?
Oh, you have to be even
more careful of this bitch.
She already has a history
of betraying her people.
You bastard!
Have you gone crazy?
If you don't want to die,
get back to working on the guns.
Enough!
From this moment forward,
I will not allow this kind of conflict.
Everyone back to their own work.
- Are you okay…?
- Just leave me alone for a bit.
Don't try so hard for me anymore.
Team Leader!
It's Code Red.
Hurry up and go to the conference room.
A blacklisted defectee from North Korea
was found murdered in Shanghai.
The defecting routes are different,
but we found something in
common with the others.
It's a precursor to a major terrorist act
directed at Korea.
We don't yet know exactly how or when.
Seung Hee, you and Jeong In
gather additional information
from our international allies.
And Sa Woo…
We just received a report that the crew members
of a fishing boat in Pusan were kidnapped.
They were all erased?
Yes. We checked every closed circuit TV system,
but there are no recordings left.
Did you check that?
Take a look at this.
Oh, a cross shaped USB drive.
There's one folder that we can't open.
I think it's locked with a secret code.
It's a 4 kilobyte code.
You can't open it here.
You need a special program to open it,
as well as a system able to support it.
Perhaps the Pentagon's system might or…
even NSS's system will be able to support it.
So what is this?
I know you were upset by that last incident
with the visitor from the North.
Were you curious as to what I wanted to accomplish
that I would even exclude NSS from the process?
I requested a summit conference.
What I want from it is to create a road map
to the unification of the Korean peninsula.
It's looking hopeful thus far,
but now I need your assistance.
I would first like to hear the
reason why you excluded NSS.
In all sincerity, I do not trust
the operation of NSS 100%.
There is the possibility that you can use information
you gather for reasons other than intended.
But now I've laid out my intentions and
if I am to succeed in what I want,
I need the experience
and information from NSS.
This is our complete procedural and
intelligence manual on summit conferences,
plus information on various other situations.
I've spent 20 years with NSS.
I beg your pardon, but I also have a request.
Please consider carefully again
on the need for NSS.
What you want to do for the country,
to help resolve problems and
to make it possible for you to do so
is our mission and the reason for our existence.
The President's hidden card is nukes.
What are you saying?
If the North doesn't give
up developing nuclear arms,
the South will also develop them.
I heard that during Park Chung Hee's administration,
nuclear weapons were being developed.
How far did we get with the technology?
From what I know, nuclear weapons
were developed to final completion.
Is that true?
I understand that to be true.
Where is it?
The information to build
nuclear arms to completion?
The program to develop them
may have been abandoned,
but the knowledge couldn't have disappeared.
Were you on friendly terms
with Director Baek San before?
No.
It looks to me to be the case.
Our Great Leader accepted
the request from South Korea.
There will be a summit conference.
We don't have much time left.
What's going on with
the team you're building?
I've already started.
There is no need for you to worry.
I understand you will be
putting together a panel,
to decide on the team to attend the conference.
Please include me in that panel.
The operation takes place in two days.
We will make our final preparations.
Dae Hyun and Young Bum,
you two take the conference venue.
Yes, sir.
Hyun Seok, finish up what you're working on.
I just have the police department left,
so I'll finish today.
Don't worry.
Seon Hwa, you go with him
and check out the VIP route.
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's begin.
Where are we going?
The NSS network may open that file
we couldn't open.
How are we going to
access the NSS network?
What is this place?
Where I used to live.
Are you going somewhere?
Hyun Jun!
I said I was trying to get you off.
What do you mean get me off?
Look what you've gotten me into!
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
It's an order.
What's wrong?
Team Leader!
Yeah.
Sa Woo sunbae is in Pusan now, isn't he?
Yes. I was just on the phone with him.
Why?
Then who's in his house right now?
I think we've got something.
He's looking for something
on our main server.
I think they know we're there.
I'll try the webcam.
Who are you?
Show us your face.
What should we do?
- Let security know.
- Okay.
Security?
They know we're in there.
- They might shut us down.
- Keep going.
I don't think we should continue.
Let's do this next time…
We won't have another chance.
What's the current situation?
He's still searching.
He is still in the house.
It wasn't a file in that locked folder,
but the location of the file at NSS...
section NSSB3003001-1
Within NSS, there is a storage area
with top secret information.
The storage area is divided into sections,
for control of the information.
That section belongs to Vice Director Baek San.
There were 260 registered trucks
that hauled out cargo that day.
But none of those were refrigerated trucks
loaded with frozen tuna.
Why are we focusing on tuna?
We're looking for terrorists, not tuna.
We have reports that someone on the boat
said something about...
hiding weapons in the tuna.
We're working on the assumption that those
weapons may be used for terrorist activities.
Then, the tuna unloaded from the boat,
where did it disappear to?
There are two possibilities.
The first is that it's still in storage on the dock.
The second is that it was
loaded on an unregistered truck
and has already left the area.
What about the terrorists?
We believe they used fake passports
and are still in the country.
We're in the process of studying each
person that passed through customs.
That may take some time.
Oh! Were you able to do what I asked for?
I did but because it was analog format,
there was a limit to what can be done.
What is it?
It's a closed circuit TV recording
that caught the suspects.
I thought all the recordings were erased.
This recording was by a security
camera at a restaurant.
It wasn't in digital but tape format,
so we were able to recover it.
Let's watch.
You can't make out the faces.
With something like this,
even a montage isn't possible.
Fine.
At any rate, we are now certain
that the terrorists are here.
And consider the truck with the frozen tuna
to be here also.
When can we expect the list of
people that passed through customs?
Uh, I believe it will take another 20 hours.
Get it done in 12 hours.
Why are they here,
what do they want,
and where did they go…
find out as much as you can.
Understand?
What are you doing?
Get out of here.
Ah... ah..
Jin Sa Woo.
I'd like to talk to you for a moment.
The person that was in your house,
you know the webcam was on.
I took a close look at it…
Oh my… uh, I don't know if it's okay to say it…
What is it?
Oh, this is completely my personal opinion,
but I think it might be...
Hyun Jun.
Did you just say "Hyun Jun"?
You'll notice, when you take a look on here,
you can't see who it is.
Now, this version was developed in our lab,
and it uses an infrared system
to create a skeletal image.
When compared to the skeletal database
in our system,
it matches to Kim Hyun Jun at 74% probability.
Of course, everything on Kim Hyun Jun
was destroyed,
but this database must have been spared
as it was in a separate system.
There must be many people with
similar skeletal build.
Of course.
The build can be an identifying point.
The frame can be similar but not identical.
I think it's pushing it to say that
it's Hyun Jun based on 74% possibility.
The death of Hyun Jun has already been confirmed
by the information we received from Hungary.
Yes, you're right.
There are many people here that are
still struggling with Hyun Jun's death.
I hope this latest information dies in your hands.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
I brought up some nonsense
and got you all confused.
You didn't.
I knew it might not be a possibility,
but I really hoped he was still alive.
That's something I've imagined hundreds
of times, thousands of times myself.
Okay, let's stop talking about things like that.
Here.
What is that?
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm finished.
All the photos of the building, the VIP route,
and expected positions of the police officers.
Won't this do it?
Good job.
The operation starts now.
The uranium capsule is ready.
It took longer that I thought.
It's enclosed,
so it's safe for you to open.
It is stabilized to pass the Geiger counter,
so you'll have no problem  getting it into the South.
These are the Blue House files.
Good job. Okay.
Director.
I have something to tell you, sir.
What is it?
Director!
We found it.
Among the trucks that left the docks,
we found a truck that was not registered.
We've confirmed it came to Sung Nam Buk.
After that?
A closed circuit system caught it going
into Ya San, via East Geum Kang,
and identified the storage facility
where it's been for a week.
Send the tactical unit quickly.
Yes, sir.
Group 2, ready to charge in.
Group 3, ready to charge in.
Charge in.
I think I know what their target is.
You go back to the agency and provide support.
Our target is the NSS.
How do we enter?
There's no other way.
The NSS is under attack right now.
The agency was taken over by the enemy.
…they enabled a wire connection…
Where is it?
…south sector…
Go.
- Update me.
- We don't know the situation in there.
It's risky to enter now.
Do it.
So I can tell you now...
my reason for joining NSS?
Just do your job.