Hyun Jun meets Jo Myung Ho and informs him of
IRIS's identity and the nuclear terrorist attack.
Chul Young, who was kidnapped by Hyun Jun,
decides to help Hyun Jun in order to stop the war.
We have to prevent the war between the North and South.
It's up to you and Hyun Jun now.
I'll be arresting you for treason.
Sang Hyun, with Seung Hee's help,
tries to track down the terrorists,
but is held back by Baek San and Sa Woo.
Team Leader Choi!
What's the reason you're doing all this?
We're arresting Team Leader Choi immediately.
Jo Myung Ho, who learns that
Hyun Jun has lost the terrorists,
tries to arrest Yeon Gi Hoon
in order to stop the nuclear threat.
Find out Yeon Gi Hoon's whereabouts right now.
Hyun Jun, using the terrorists'
vehicle records, finds the bunker.
Episode 16
I think they assembled the saturated
uranium and the detonator here.
I don't know where to begin...
or what to say.
Hold me.
In front of the Budapest train station, the
moment your car exploded in front of me,
I thought you were dead.
I left the car after receiving a call from Sa Woo.
The North's security officers were
gathering in the station at the time.
I lost the people from the North
who were chasing after me,
and I went to the place where
we left Hong Seung Ryong.
I was trying to steal a plane from
there to escape Hungary, but...
the plane crashed from Sa Woo's gunfire.
What did you just say? Are you
saying Sa Woo tried to kill you?
How can that...
I thought this it could happen,
because if I, who killed Yoon Sung Chul,
were captured and my identity was exposed,
a war could've started between the North and South.
Since it was Sa Woo's and my fate
to carry out orders of the state,
I did think that...
I would've done the same
thing if I received such orders.
However,
the assassination of Yoon Sung Chul
wasn't an order from the state,
but instead, an order from an organization
called IRIS which Baek San belongs to.
Sa Woo, who aimed a gun
at me, is also a part of IRIS.
IRIS?
What is that?
You really don't know?
I don't know.
This is the first time I've ever thought that
all the suspicious activities within the NSS
had something to do with the director and Sa Woo.
What exactly is IRIS?
Be sure to secure the area.
Then why are you with the terrorists?
Who are they?
Jin Sa Woo is coming.
There's nine that I've confirmed just
with my eyes, and they are all armed.
Leave quickly.
-I'll stop Sa Woo.
-Don't, Seung Hee.
Don't worry, he won't be able to shoot me.
Go quickly.
Hyun Jun.
Don't move.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you being stupid like this?
Try and shoot me.
Just like what you did to Hyun Jun.
Shoot me also!
Choi Seung Hee.
Why did you change like that?
I'm... sorry.
I...
knew that Choi Seung Hee was alive...
a long time ago.
When I suddenly disappeared in Akita,
I was in Korea.
I thought that the only way I,
having failed to kill you and having cut off
all contacts with the security department,
could return to the North...
was to kill Director Baek San,
since I could've also given you your vengeance.
However, I was dumbfounded when
I got caught on my way to Seoul.
When I was being transferred to the
NSS after having my identity exposed,
the person who came to interrogate me was...
Seung Hee.
Seung Hee's objective wasn't to interrogate me,
but she wanted to know if you were alive.
I... finally confessed, and with the help of
Seung Hee, who tried to find you through me,
I escaped the NSS and went back to Akita.
I met you again...
but I couldn't tell you that Seung Hee was alive.
Why?
Why did you do that?
What's the matter all of a sudden?
The president has issued an arrest on Yeon Gi Hoon.
You know that even if we arrest him,
it won't put a stop to this matter.
Committeeman Yeon Gi Hoon won't talk.
I know that.
However, there's no other way, is there?
We know that Kim Hyun Jun has lost the terrorists.
Symbolically, he's responsible for the
North and South camps for the summit.
If we don't have a logical
reason, it'll be hard to arrest him.
That is why we need your help.
Does Kim Hyun Jun know of this?
We cannot contact him.
There is no time.
Please cooperate with us.
It's me.
The people from the Blue House have come
to take Committeeman Yeon Gi Hoon away.
They're asking me to help with the arrest.
You know that it can't happen right now.
The people in the Blue House know that
you have lost the terrorist operations team.
I don't think I can stop them anymore.
I'll be heading there right now.
You were looking for me, sir?
The South Korean government has come
to arrest Committeeman Yeon Gi Hoon.
We have to make sure it ends
without too much trouble.
Are you saying you're going to turn over
Committeeman Yeon Gi Hoon to South Korea?
Committeeman Yeon is a traitor,
but we can't turn over a member of the
Workers' Party to South Korea.
Yeon Gi Hoon is no longer a part of the republic.
If he was a part of the republic, he wouldn't
have insisted on sacrificing numerous citizens.
-The committeeman is inside, right?
-Yes.
It's been verified, sir.
Our members who stayed behind to take
care of Kim Hyun Jun were attacked.
This wouldn't have happened
if you had followed my orders!
I'm sorry, sir.
Don't relax until tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Tomorrow at 5:00 P.M.
after you have confirmed the explosion,
you will escape using the planned route.
Come in.
What is it?
Chief Secretary Jeong Hyung Jun is here.
Jeong Hyung Jun?
Why is he here without even a call?
He says it's an urgent matter, so he will
talk to you about it when he meets you.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, sir.
I've given it a lot of thought,
but I cannot allow citizens to be sacrificed
as a cause for the North-South war.
I believed you until the end...
and you're betraying me like this?
Compared to your betrayal to the country
and its citizens, my betrayal is nothing.
Nothing will change because of this.
When dawn breaks,
the nuke will have exploded in Seoul,
and using that as a starting point,
the republic will change into a new world.
There's a lot of time before dawn breaks.
Let's get going.
Is this the reason you pointed a gun at me?
You were going on about a country and its people
and your scheme was to sell me off to South Korea?
You're mistaken, Committeeman.
The reason we're taking you away,
is because we know that you are a member of IRIS
before you are a member of the Workers' Party.
Take him.
Go on in.
Take a seat.
Right now,
because of the trouble you've caused,
I don't have any emotion left in me to spend.
If you keep on going like this,
I can't protect you any longer.
I never wanted you to protect me.
Seung Hee.
What is IRIS?
I heard that you and Sa Woo are part of IRIS.
What is IRIS to you, that you tried to kill Hyun Jun?
What is it to you, that you betrayed the NSS and this country?
If Kim Hyun Jun was the one who spouted such crap,
then it is just nonsense created by his illusions.
There's nothing like that.
I don't know what you have heard from others,
but the one you should trust right now is me.
Then... from what you said, Jin Sa Woo is...
You should keep it to yourself,
sir. Even I'll be taken away.
Just now, even Team Leader
Choi Seung Hee was taken away.
Even Choi Seung Hee?
Augh, we're in a state of emergency
right now because of the nuclear terror...
What do they want to do after taking away
team leaders, section chiefs, and everyone?
Where are you going, sir?
You, don't blabber around.
Whatever you are suspicious of...
ask me. I'll tell you everything.
I no longer want to hear, or believe that.
No.
I need to do it.
Why do you need to do that?
Because the beginning of all this was you.
Because the reason I'm here right now,
is because of you, Choi Seung Hee.
So,
is that why you were trying
to kill Hyun Jun in Hungary?
Why can't you say anything?
Try to make up some excuse.
Because Hyun Jun...
was better off dying by my hands.
What do you mean by that?
I can't do it.
If you can't do it, then I guess I'll
have to find someone else to do it.
Tell Choi Seung Hee to come.
Why are you...
Even if you were me...
Because if it wasn't me,
you would've had to do it.
Because I couldn't have you kill Hyun Jun,
whom you love, with your own hands.
After the moment
you had entered my heart,
I was always standing on the edge of a cliff.
What difference does it make
now, having this emotional rant?
So,
how does it make a difference
if I came to understand you?
Even if Hyun Jun forgives you,
I can never forgive you.
Seung Hee...
Well, what happened?
Yeon Gi Hoon is dead.
He was shot during the arrest.
What do you mean, shot?
Are you saying they knew that we
were going to arrest Yeon Gi Hoon?
I think so, sir.
Arresting Yeon Gi Hoon is something you and
I, just the two of us, decided on, isn't it?
How could something like this be exposed?
I think that they are in much
deeper than we suspected.
He is waiting.
Committeeman Yeon Gi Hoon has announced
that the nuke will go off as dawn breaks,
and that the coup dՎtat will go on as planned.
Even if the nuke goes off, we have to stop the war.
I will call Leader Kim.
I will expose all the secrets
in order to stop the coup dՎtat.
Please go back to the North right now
and use your best efforts to stop the coup dՎtat.
I'm planning on doing whatever I can.
I'm going back to the republic
in order to stop the coup dՎtat.
I know these are difficult circumstances,
but please stop the nuclear terror.
I have no clues on the target of explosion
or Kang Do Cheol's whereabouts.
If you happen to find any clues from anyone
related to Kang Do Cheol, give me a call.
How have been, sir?
A nuke is supposedly going to
explode in the middle of Seoul,
and it's frustrating that I can't do anything about it.
It's too early to give up.
It's not that I'm giving up.
The only one I can still trust now... is you.
Did something happen, sir?
Committeeman Yeon Gi Hoon is dead.
Does that mean we have to stop the operation?
No. We'll go on as planned.
The nuke will explode at its target, Kwang Hwa Mun*
(*The main gate of Gyeongbok Palace, located in northern Seoul)
at five in the afternoon.
Who's going to plant the nuke?
It's already been finished.
It should be heading towards
Kwang Hwa Mun right about now.
What do you mean?
Tell me in detail.
The nuke is currently planted on a
city tour bus that goes around Seoul.
When the city tour bus stops in front
of Kwang Hwa Mun at five o'clock,
we'll use this detonator to make it explode.
After the explosion has been confirmed,
we'll head down to Jung Bok River
and, taking a boat there, we'll escape South Korea.
Yes, this is Baek San, sir.
Yes, sir.
I will prepare it as you have said.
Come to my room.
-Who are you guys?
-Please do not move.
We're from the Presidential
Security Office. Please cooperate.
There's no time.
While Oh Sung Shik is incinerating
the files, you buy some time.
We can't end it like this. I'll stop them.
Listen carefully.
Yeon Gi Hoon has been eliminated.
We'll be arrested.
That cannot be stopped.
Right now, we can only trust the
headquarters and follow their orders.
-I've gathered everything.
-Incinerate it all.
Since you only need to buy time,
don't make any unnecessary casualties.
Yes, sir.
-We'll stop them here.
-Yes, sir.
Since we have confirmed that the
director is in his room, find the others.
Yes, sir.
This is Yoo Kwang Ho. Open the door.
Director Baek!
This isn't something that can be dealt with by doing this!
Open the door willingly!
We've found them. They're on the roof.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Hurry.
This door, isn't there a way to open it?
If it's not from the inside, there's no other way.
He's the Chief of National Security.
Until the situation is taken care of,
I will be taking charge of the NSS.
- I'll be asking for your cooperation.
- Yes.
Where is Jin Sa Woo?
He's confronting the guards on the roof right now.
Stop this!
We do not want anymore casualties!
Clip.
This is the last one sir.
Team Leader.
An order has been issued to arrest
the director and Jin Sa Woo.
It's me. We've destroyed everything.
Surrender now.
Yes.
They've both been arrested.
As of this moment,
you have been removed from
the position of Director of the NSS.
These are the locations they've visited based
on the information from their navigation system.
Park Chul Young said he brought
in six kilograms of enriched uranium.
That would equate to 21 kilotons of TNT*.
(*trinitrotoluene, used to measure the strength of bombs)
Then the area affected by the explosion
would be a two kilometer radius.
If we assumed any of these spots to be Ground Zero...
Their objective isn't to hurt people, but to start a war.
To do that, they will pick a spot that holds significant meaning.
Husband!
Where is the bomb installed?
Even if you tell us now,
you will still be executed.
But we will spare your family members.
I will ask you one more time,
where has the bomb been installed?
Mother!
Father!
Your son's next.
Where is it?
Stop!
Their targets are the Federal Building Complex,
the U.S. Embassy, and the Blue House.
The 21 kilotons of explosive power
will affect a two kilometer radius,
so the place that could affect those three targets?
there's only one place.
What happened?
What?
I understand.
They said the nuclear bomb is in Kwang Hwa Mun.
We need to get you to the
bunker as quickly as possible.
Please send me the complete
file on detonation devices.
Yes, I got it.
They've found out the location.
It's Kwang Hwa Mun.
-What about the exact bomb location?
-We don't know the exact spot or the time.
Kwang Hwa Mun is considered the heart of Seoul,
with all the government official concentrated there.
And a plaza was built there recently, which draws a lot of people.
Without knowing the exact location,
it'll be impossible to avoid a disaster.
If they used the detonation device they took from NSS,
they will probably use a remote
control to detonate the bomb.
We need to jam the signals around Kwang Hwa Mun.
The remote control device can
be anything that uses satellite signal,
from a shortwave receiver to a cell phone.
We need to jam the signals for all of those possibilities.
They could have modified it to detonate in another way.
We will just have to hope they didn't.
With Kwang Hwa Mun as the center, jam
the signals in a four kilometer radius of it.
All right.
How long will that take?
About... twenty minutes.
-Get is done as quickly as you possible can.
-Okay.
What is the source of this intelligence?
I think Hyun Jun informed the Blue House.
Where are you going?
Five minutes to go.
Jamming has been completed.
(*Explosive Ordinance Disposal)
Mobilize the tactical and EOD* teams to Kwang Hwa Mun.
Why didn't it go off? Did something go wrong?
That's not possible.
I agree. I also checked it several times.
We'll go to Kwang Hwa Mun and set if off ourselves.
Are you saying let's all go and kill ourselves?
If we have to go there and set it off, that's the only way.
What are you talking about?
We didn't come here to die.
Shut up and listen to me!
If by our deaths, we can carry
out our mission successfully,
we will be remembered by
our country and our people.
Tae Yung, Gwang Su, Chae Hyun,
You guys stay behind and be
prepared to back up if we fail.
What's the current situation?
After the word, that the bomb
was at Kwang Hwa Mun, came,
we jammed all the signals in the surrounding area.
What do you mean jamming the signals? How
will that help to stop the nuclear bomb attack?
The nuclear bomb is set up to be
detonated by a wireless remote.
If that bomb is within the Kwang
Hwa Mun area with jammed signals,
it won't explode.
This is the spot that overlaps from all the locations
they've visited, according to their navigation system.
I'm sure the location was
decided from the beginning.
Our mission is to stop the upcoming summit meeting.
Take a look at the dates.
For three days, they've been
roaming this area every day.
Why do you think this is?
Follow me!
Look in the cargo area! The cargo!
I need everybody to please exit the bus now.
Exit the bus now!
It's not in the luggage area.