IRIS
Hyun Jun and Seon Hwa who find out about IRIS,
and Baek San with Hong Seung Ryong's necklace,
meet with Chul Young in China and head to Korea,
after becoming a part of Chul Young's terrorist team.
The NSS and Sa Woo start an investigation,
after finding data on terrorist activities.
Sa Woo finds clues that Hyun Jun left in his house,
and has a hunch that Hyun Jun
is a part of the terrorist team.
Episode 10
Squad 2, ready to attack.
Squad 8!
Ready!
Move in.
There is no one here.
Squad 1, clean!
Squad 2, clean!
It's ready sir.
When do we start, sir?
It's done!
The NSS guys have infiltrated.
There's something here, sir!
[East Asia Foreign Affairs Conference Schedule]
The storage is empty, sir.
However, I think I know where their target is.
Good job.
I'll be taking the tactical assault team from here,
so you go over there directly.
All right, sir.
Let's go.
Their target is the place where the East
Asia Foreign Affairs Conference will be held.
All right. Everyone get ready.
Yes, sir.
Our target is not the conference.
It's the South Chosun's National Security Services,
(*Korea's ancient name)
the NSS.
Is that possible?
With our current forces, it's impossible.
They will believe our target is the conference,
and focus all their forces there.
Also,
the preliminary inspection team,
arrives for the North-South conference today.
They will also place their men there.
Therefore, the NSS will be in a state of zero defense.
Even so,
it's a national intelligence agency.
It'll be hard to get through the security system.
We already have a full understanding of the NSS's
security system through this ex-agent's confession.
The infiltration will be led by this guy and...
How do we enter?
Waste disposal vehicle.
In the NSS, even garbage is something to protect,
since even a used paper cup may be used
by the enemy to acquire information.
That's why,
only special waste removal services can remove them.
We're using exactly that.
What's the reason we're going into the NSS?
It's me, sir.
Yes.
I just told him now.
Hear it for yourself.
It's me, Park Chul Young.
Keep in mind that the reason you're infiltrating the
NSS is not to get your revenge against Baek San.
If you serve your purpose,
and complete the mission this time around,
I promise you an opportunity for revenge.
Then what's the reason you're trying to seize the NSS?
I can't tell you that yet.
You just need to listen to Kang Do Chul's orders.
What I want to know isn't why you're here.
The man who was in Budapest at that time.
I want to know if he's alive or not.
Is he alive?
I don't know.
If our target is the NSS,
then we have to exclude Kim Hyun Jun.
Why?
They were all his comrades and friends.
He may falter.
If that's the case, then we definitely need to bring him along,
because it's a chance for us to find out,
if he's truly working together with us.
We're entering South Chosun.
What do you think is the reason?
It's actually better this way.
It's our last chance to unlock the files of
Director Baek San that we haven't unlocked yet.
I'm entering South Chosun.
Execute the plan.
We're starting.
Team Leader Choi, from here on,
you take care of the matters regarding
the North-South Conference inspection team that's arriving today.
Yes.
And report to me directly about related matters.
Yes, sir.
It's me.
I found the target of terrorism.
It's the U.S. Secretary of State,
who's taking part in today's East
Asia Foreign Affairs Conference.
Their target is there.
Mobilize all possible battle personnel we can utilize to that site.
Yes, sir.
Ready all able tactical assault teams for emergency response.
Stop the car.
Yes, sir.
The target of the terrorists who
came in through Busan has changed.
Where is it, sir?
The site of the East Asia Foreign Affairs Conference.
Today, the U.S. Secretary of State will also be there.
The target is the U.S. Secretary of State.
You go back to the agency,
and provide support.
Yes, I understand.
Yes.
Where are you right now?
I'm on my way back to the agency.
I was informed.
Hurry back and provide us with support.
Yes, I understand.
We came here for the waste removal.
Now.
It's done.
Good job.
Come to the target location to assist.
Yes, sir.
I got it.
Man, what are they doing instead of coming in?
I'll go out and see.
No. Wait.
They're coming in right now.
Working hard I see.
I haven't seen you guys before.
We're new.
We never received news of that...
Just a second.
Huh?
Why isn't this working?
Send me a list of the VIPs participating in today's event please.
Yes. I'll send you it right now.
The only way into the NSS is the elevator,
but that's impossible.
I know.
You have to go through a bio scan.
We...
aren't going on the elevator.
There's no other way.
You find out how.
Show him.
Follow me.
Hallelujah~ I'm fallin', I'm fallin', fallin'
To a fallen building, yeah
Hallelujah (yes) I'm fallin' (yes) I'm fallin', fallin'
Shimmy, shimmy, yo, one two, step action
Mission complete (no doubt)
The empty streets at dawn
I'm a "die-alone", if not cold-blooded, I fail
I, to my changing commands, my soldier type
Don't touch me, Big Bang is dynamite
Boom! Throw my life away along with the sound
The mission that's begun,
with the situation is thumbs up
It's here.
To us, love is a luxury
Mission complete (no doubt)
What the?
What is it?
The fire alarm went off in the lower floor.
Where's it coming from?
Quickly check which sector it is!
There. Check over there!
What about here?
There's no problem here, sir.
Install the motion detectors.
Turn off the alarm.
What is that?
Damn it.
Sound the emergency alarm,
and quickly report this to the control room!
Yes, sir!
Cut off communications with the outside first.
Control room!
We can't contact the control room!
The alarm isn't working either!
The alarm was turned off.
Something's weird.
Communications with the outside were cut off.
Cell phones don't work either.
The transfer was stopped,
please send it again.
Put up all the security camera images onto the main screen.
What happened?
You guys...
What are you doing, not getting out of here quickly?
I can't just leave the server like this!
We have no time, hurry and come.
If all of you do as I say, I won't kill you.
Respond.
Control room.
Respond, control room.
Respond.
It's not working?
Yes.
Control room.
Control room, respond.
It could be a temporary communication error,
so keep trying.
Control room, respond.
It's the president.
This is Baek San.
I heard that the terrorists' target,
was the Foreign Affairs Conference.
Wouldn't it be better to cancel the conference right now?
Don't worry so much, sir.
The entire NSS counter terrorist team has been dispatched.
If you cancel the conference right now,
there will be mass confusion,
and that will also affect the conference between the North and South.
Then I'll trust you, Director Baek,
and carry out the conference as planned.
What happened with the guests from the North?
Ah.
They're just about to arrive right now.
He says the officer commissioned by the North arrived.
What should I do about that Foreign Affairs Conference?
Carry it out as planned.
Yes, sir.
It's must've been hard getting here.
The president told me to take special care of you.
Thank you.
He's from one of our government institutions,
brought here to take part in the inspection.
Welcome.
Nice to meet you.
I think we need to do an inspection.
Allow him to pass.
[Firearms Prohibited]
Put your head down!
Come here.
There could be other remaining agents.
Look around every corner,
and make sure to lock them up.
Follow me.
What are you doing?
Maintain your position.
You rat-like bastards. Go quickly!
Is this all the personnel here?
Currently, yes.
We're dealing with them right now.
If you find all of them, contact me first.
Why?
Do as you're told.
There's a wind blowing inside my heart.
Your image is being erased
It was a necessary procedure in
creating Mr. Kim Hyun Jun's profile.
While having a dream called regret,
Try being an actress.
I'll grab you a manager.
I stand here here missing you.
I think you'll earn quite a bit of money.
Depending on the mission,
I lasted a day because
I do become an actress sometimes.
you said you love me
I lasted a month because
of that gaze staring at me.
I loved you, I loved you,
but my wound has spread, so I can't go
I can't stay true to these words, "I love you"
When are you going to open the file?
In order to get to the classified information
storage facility on the third level basement and
get close to Baek San's storage,
I need to get through a fingerprint detection.
I'm going to look for an opportunity to extract his fingerprints first.
[Counter-Terrorist Team 1: Leader Choi Seung Hee]
Jeez, these guys...
What is it?
The server shut down when I was working.
Someone put up a trap.
Who was it?
It was you, wasn't it?
You were doing something earlier!
Open up the server.
Open it!
The server protection protocol was activated.
You can't unlock it,
without an administrator's password.
Then...
tell me the password.
We don't know.
There's no one here of a high rank like that.
What was that?
It's not a lie.
There's no one with the admin's password among them.
What should we do sir?
If we don't put the server back on,
we can't unlock the R&D room inside the storage facility.
R&D room?
Can you turn the server back on?
I'm sure I can,
but it'll take some time, sir.
How long?
About thirty minutes.
No.
That's too late.
What are you doing?
Now no one can enter or leave out for an hour.
I closed off the entire NSS.
Get started since I bought some time.
Go.
It's about time you tell me,
the reason for coming to the NSS.
What are you trying to take out of the
R&D room inside the storage facility?
Get rid of that useless curiosity,
and just do your own job.
Please...
What happened?
We still haven't connected yet.
Check to see if there's a signal interference.
This is Jin Sa Woo.
It's me.
The NSS is under attack right now.
Team Leader, are you all right?
Cap!
*short for captain*
What is it?
Is it finished?
We disabled everything except for
our team's cell phones, right, sir?
Then...
Someone among us...
No.
I think someone enabled a wired
connection that wasn't being used.
Where is it?
A floor below, in the south sector.
You two go.
Disable it.
The situation here is bad.
Come quickly--
Team Leader. Team Leader!
Hello? TK2.
Section Chief, we have a code black situation.
The agency was taken over by an enemy.
We're closer to the agency. We'll go.
Section Chief,
please take care of the situation there.
It's code black.
We're going back to the agency.
Yes, sir.
Place the vehicles at each position in a line.
Right now,
a code black situation has occurred.
Vehicle 2, go back to the agency,
and follow Team Leader Jin Sa Woo's commands.
Over.
Even though the server is down,
you can turn on the internal security cameras, right?
Since it's a separate system, it's possible.
Why?
We lost the one who made the call.
We should get him.
Did Cap give permission to do so?
Why should I get permission for something so obvious?
There's no time.
Do it quickly.
[Danger - Firearms Prohibited]
Argh!
What happened?
I still haven't...
Is it impossible?
No. I can do it.
How long do you think it'll take?
An hour?
No. That's too late!
If someone communicated with the outside,
then their backup should be arriving soon.
Pack the tools and follow me.
Come to the control room right now.
We have to give up on opening the safe right now.
Then what do we do, sir?
We have to go open it directly.
The security system will be tough.
It's dangerous.
Follow me.
You two, guard this spot.
Now's our chance.
Keep a lookout for me here.
Hide!
Section Chief. Section Chief.
Section Chief, are you all right?
Section Chief.
Hey. What's going on?
I requested for a rescue,
so our backup team should be coming soon.
Stay here until then.
What? Where are you going?
You stay here too until the backup team comes here.
Hide well until then.
It might be Hyun Jun.
Did you just say Hyun Jun?
Over there.
Did you go?
I'll go right now.
Let's go together.
All right.
I'll turn it on for Channel 2.
Contact me if you need to.
It's done.
Wait!
This is why we should've turned
the control room server back on.
Just what exactly is in there?
Keep going.
It's done.
Are you sure?
Maybe.
All right.
Carry it out.
Why is it like this?
The emergency security system was activated,
so all the doors were shut down.
Disable the system.
Requesting backup.
What is it?
I found the one who contacted the outside.
It's the third level of the basement.
I'm pursuing him with A1.
If it's shut down like this,
we can't disable it from here.
We have to get inside somehow.
If we don't blow up the wall,
it's impossible.
Blow it up.
The backup team's arriving soon.
Shouldn't we wait, sir?
We have no time. Blow it up!
Entering like this when we don't even
know the situation on the inside...
is reckless, sir!
Blow it up right now.
Yes, sir. I'll do that.
Don't move.
Turn around.
Throw your gun away.
Throw your gun away!
Don't move.
Hurry and throw your gun away!
What exactly did you do to Seung Hee?
No one will believe what you say.
Think about what you came here for.
What about Team Leader Choi Seung Hee?
It's just us here.
I think that person... is Hyun Jun.
It's the file that was in Baek San's storage.
It has all the information.
It also had information about your parents...
There's a problem in the report.
Tell us first what it is that you pulled out of the NSS.
Something you'd never be able to imagine
will take place in the middle of Seoul.
I loved you, I loved you,
but my wound has spread, so I can't go
I can't stay true to these words, "I love you"
The day I leave you,
I'll love you, I'll wait for you
You remember all the times we spent together
The words I couldn't say,
the words I wanted to say
are left in my heart and they flow out
Allow us just one thing out of this world